This little light
I've found
Take it in,
breathe it out
A little drum
that's beating loud
In my chest,
I hear the sound
I can feel
Feel you now
I can feel you now
I can feel
Mead Cameras
Where am I?
Ow...
Hey! What the hell?
What did you do to me?
Saved your life.
You shot me with a stun gun.
You killed Bannister, didn't you?
Don't worry.
I won't turn you in.
You were out of control.
I did what I had to do.
My device.
I always finish a job.
How did you know you'd find me there?
AS-08 reporting.
Returning to scene. Over.
Roger that.
Report of multiple gunshots
heard near the Quail building.
I was tuned
into the police frequency.
Picked up chatter about
Senator Bannister's murder.
Just put two and two together.
I guess I'm supposed to say thank you.
Here. Drink this.
Don't blame you.
No booze has tasted right
since the Blackout.
Blackout?
The Blackout of 2022.
You really don't remember a thing.
It was a total data wipe.
Changed everything.
I told you I can't remember anything.
But maybe I never had
any memories to begin with.
Why would you think that?
We know where to find it. They don't.
So if that little worm
comes around again,
we slit his throat.
That'll send a message to the--
Drove, right?
Wanna talk with you.
You gotta be kidding.
What do you want, little piggy?
You ain't got nothing on me.
Whoa--ow!
Heard you had a run-in
with a young woman.
Bad attitude, tattoo of a black lotus.
Why would I help
a pretty, little piggy like you?
Ah! Geez!
Okay, okay! Ow!
Maybe I should
slice myself off a piece.
Son of a bitch!
Police business.
Now, move along.
To hell with this!
Finally, a little peace and quiet.
Tell me about the girl.
You want me to slice your arm off?
The other one?
She cut the boss up.
She's nuts.
Carried a damn samurai sword.
You better give me
more than that.
All right. All right.
You win.
She had this...tech.
We tried to take it from her.
We was just messing around.
Then she comes back to kill us.
Neuro-stims must've messed her brain up!
It'd be a good idea to cooperate
with local law enforcement.
Next time, I won't be so nice.
Won't be a next time for you, piggy!
LAPD investigators have refused to comment
on reports that Senator Bannister
was attending an unlicensed boxing match
when he was killed by an unknown assailant.
Accolades for the senator came in from
as far away as the off-world colonies.
In a long and distinguished career,
Senator Bannister was seen
as a non-partisan defender of basic human
rights and was hailed as a true patriot.
He was a piece of shit.
Did you find out what's on my device?
Not yet.
Listen, what's a replicant?
A replicant?
Is it a machine?
Not exactly.
Then what?
Why do you even care about this?
Bannister told me.
That I'm one of...them.
And you believe what that scum told you?
But what if...
20 years ago, a corporation
made artificial people.
Called them replicants.
The idea was for them to do hard labor
without complaining, like slaves.
Hold still.
Look at me.
I'll tell you if you're a replicant.
Look up and to the left.
Don't blink.
You're not a replicant.
If you were a Nexus 8,
you'd have a serial number.
6, you'd be long dead.
Then how was I able to do all that?
How did I...
kill people so easily?
If you're still worried,
there's only one way to tell for sure.
Have a seat.
It's called the Voight-Kampff test.
Tells if you're human or replicant.
Replicants are tough as nails,
but they look just like everybody else.
What's it going to do to me?
Don't worry.
I'm just gonna ask you some questions.
I don't have any memories.
Feelings can tell more than memories.
They're deeper.
If you're a replicant, your emotions
will be marked by contradictions.
Picture your mother.
In the house you grew up in.
She looks at you, disappointed,
and tells you that she doesn't love you.
She's never loved you,
and she regrets ever having you.
A mother would never say that.
You're passing a busy street corner
on the way to a friend's apartment,
and you see a small cardboard
box next to a dumpster.
Inside is a tabby cat, a kitten, a real one
with green eyes and a white spot
on her nose, meowing for food.
I'd take it home and feed it.
I like cats.
Why do you like cats?
Hmm...
They're cute and fluffy.
Can you remember being in love?
How did it make you feel?
That's easy.
The way he'd look at me...
I thought my heart was going to burst.
It felt like... something wonderful.
Make it pretty.
Stay still.
It's done.
That is so cool.
It's beautiful.
It's a gift.
To mark your new beginning.
Don't you mean our new beginning?
Don't forget me, Elle.
How old were you?
It's coming back.
That was when we first met.
He knew so many things.
He told me that the lotus represents purity.
So he gave me this tattoo.
But only the white lotus is said to be pure.
No.
That depends on perception.
Don't worry.
You're not a replicant.
Just a girl with amnesia.
Your emotions don't exhibit
any contradictions.
Get some rest.
I'm going out for a drink.
I'll grab you some food.
Senator Bannister is the reason
California still has an economy
despite devastating climate
change. A hero to the people.
A hero?
There wasn't a heroic bone in his body.
Now that he's gone, it's going to be
harder to remove the ban on replicants.
I still have plenty of
friends who can help me.
Friends made with money?
Is that why you came up here? To insult me?
Or is this another talk about your pride?
I admit, humanity would
have starved without you.
It was your research that
led to synthetic proteins,
but ideas mean nothing without the
money and power to actualize them.
I gave the people manna when
heaven would not oblige.
If a man is capable of stealing the
credit for a feat of such enormity,
it will only be a matter of time.
No amount of wealth will save him.
And yet you need my wealth to remove
the ban on those replicants.
Everything intended will happen.
A god makes it so.
Listen to yourself.
Do you know who you're
starting to sound like?
Doc Badger.
Officer Davis, LAPD.
Got a few questions.
Whatever it is, I didn't do it.
You seen a young lady with a black lotus tattoo?
You think I spend all day looking?
Looking at people's tattoos?
Well, she was carrying a data drive
and swinging around a sword.
A samurai sword.
Right around here.
Everyone says you're the man to see about
these kinds of things in this part of town.
It's time for me to close the store.
If you're not arresting me,
go bother other people.
I'll be in touch, Doc.
Dammit...
What?
Get off your asses and
run, you two-bit dolls!
What are you doing?
You know the rules.
Hey, I'm a journalist.
If you don't document it,
did it really happen?
Finished already?
There's no challenge just
picking 'em off from this far.
If they really are dangerous,
we could be hunting 'em up close.
Sounds like fun.
These replicants are hardwired
to be fully submissive to humans.
Replicants...
hard-wired...
to be fully...
submissive...
Oh, these things are helpless.
Whatever we want, we do.
It's too easy.
Why?
I'm so tired,
oh, so tired
All these voices
in my brain
Living through my normal,
oh, so formal
I swear
they're driving me insane
Can't tell who's a liar
come hell or high water
I'm not listening
Whoa
I'm getting out of here
Oh, no
I won't let go
till you say so
I'm tired of being lost
Show me the way
to get back
Home
To get back home