* *
-(men clamoring)
-(grunts)
Please. Please, don't.
(sobbing)
(screaming)
(screaming continues)
LANGDON:
When it comes to symbols
of the past,
what was relevant then
is relevant now.
-(door closes)
-Sure, there are
a lot less people
who think they can
change the weather with runes
or summon the devil
with a pentagram.
-Looking at you, Clark.
-(students chuckle)
But there are still
a lot of people
who ascribe
extranatural powers to symbols.
The sign of the cross.
The number 13.
Four-leaf clover.
Luck symbols.
Bad luck symbols.
Symbols that cure
or curse or protect.
It's all superstition,
but people can believe
what they want.
Right?
It's a free country.
At what point, though...
...do their convictions
and your pursuit of happiness
become mutually exclusive?
When do benign symbols
become malignant?
What was relevant then
is relevant now.
The difference is
that now people can push symbols
out to millions
with the click of a button.
Promoting myths as fact.
And in this post-truth world,
where does that leave us?
Where do we draw the line
between respecting
the beliefs of others
-and calling bullsh...
-(phone vibrates)
-MAN: Professor Langdon? Hello?
-Hi.
I-I was expecting Peter.
Yes, sorry,
I'm his new assistant.
He asked me to jump on
and let you know
about a kind of urgent
situation.
He could use your help.
What, the secretary
of the Smithsonian
can't ask his own favors?
It's last-minute, I-I know,
but he said he can count on you.
Oh, I'm-I'm kidding.
Wh-Whatever I can do.
Terrific.
Do you think you can
get to D.C. by 5:00?
What, like, tonight?
-(bell chimes)
-MONK: Tayatha om
bekandze bekandze maha
bekandze maha bekandze.
Radza samudgate soha.
Tayatha
om bekandze bekandze...
-(door opens)
-(typing)
(door closes)
How's Monk-chella?
See for yourself.
(chanting continuing faintly)
-TRISH: This is
a live image, right?
-KATHERINE: Mm-hmm.
So, cell growth has been
almost completely arrested.
And keep in mind,
this isn't just any cancer.
These cells
are poorly differentiated,
chemo-resistant,
highly aggressive.
And these guys
sung them right to sleep.
This is breakthrough stuff.
Harnessing the power
of focused thought beats
the hell out of chemo, right?
And we may only
be scratching the surface.
(phone vibrates)
Langdon, this is a surprise.
To what do I owe this pleasure?
Well, you can thank your dad.
Apparently the keynote speaker
for his gala got sick,
so he wants me to step in.
I don't know anything
about a gala.
The Smithsonian Gala
at the Capitol.
He didn't mention it?
He may have.
I've just been so buried.
But that's nice of you
to come in on such short notice.
You know I'd do anything
for Peter.
Yeah, and a captive audience.
-That's a slander.
-Come on.
Beguiling a room full
of wealthy, half-drunk patrons
with your historical expertise?
It's pretty much your dream.
That's nice.
Okay.
Uh, I thought maybe
we could have dinner tonight.
I can't.
-Hey, no. No worries.
-I'm right in the middle
of an experiment. We're seeing
some incredible phenomena.
Like moving dice with your mind?
You know, my dad
thought he could do that.
And there it is.
You know I think
you're brilliant.
It's just your field.
Noetic science.
You should remember those words.
One day,
-they're going
to rewrite physics.
-Ah.
-When do you get in?
-Oh, I didn't mention it?
I'm already here.
NUÑEZ:
Did y'all just meet here?
You picked up a date?
Here?
That-that...
He's smooth, man.
I like your style, man.
We're finding love over here.
-(beep)
-That's okay.
-Come on. Step over.
-I thought that might happen.
I'm wearing a ring under this.
My finger was too swollen
to get it off.
Oh, yeah? (chuckles)
Open up.
Thank you.
My girlfriend says, you know,
a man shouldn't wear jewelry,
-but I disagree.
-(wand beeps)
Must have hurt.
Yeah, you'd think
after 30 years,
I'd be able to walk
down an icy driveway
without falling on my ass.
-No, I-I meant the ink.
-Mm.
You know, I got a Little Mermaid
tattoo on my back,
and I almost cried
when they put it on.
-A Little Mermaid.
-Yeah.
Well, that must have
been some party.
Well, you know how it is.
Misspent youth.
Yeah, well, same here, I guess.
I'd like to, um, get a good look
inside before you close.
Yeah, sure.
Yeah, you're all good to go.
God bless you.
NUÑEZ:
Everything okay, sir?
Yeah.
Can't read my own writing.
-Hmm.
-Um...
Thank you. Thanks.
Statuary Hall?
-It's, uh, upstairs,
to the left.
-Thanks.
Excuse me. Hey.
Sorry. Um,
there's supposed to be
a Smithsonian event in there.
Nothing on the schedule.
Maybe it got moved
to another room.
I-I'm supposed to give a speech.
I doubt it.
But don't let that stop you.
I'm a real good listener.
-(phone vibrates)
-(chuckles)
Peter.
Nobody's here.
Did I get the time wrong?
MAN:
No. You followed
directions perfectly,
which bodes well.
But the hall's locked.
Th-There's no event.
I'm sorry, c-could you
just put Peter on?
(chuckles)
Peter is in the A'raf.
I'm sorry, what?
The borderland
between heaven and hell.
Yeah, thank you.
I know what the A'raf is.
And whether he returns
to your world
or moves on to the next
will depend on your actions.
There exists within the city
an ancient portal.
Now, I need you to find it.
And unlock it.
An ancient portal.
I know Peter likes to be
the center of attention, but...
this is objectively extreme.
Um, Peter, if you're listening,
honestly, consider medication.
For someone
with so much knowledge,
you know so little.
But that will change.
You will solve
the great mystery.
-It looks so real.
-MAN: And Peter
-will point the way.
-Well, where is he?
MAN:
As above,
so below.
-Hello?
-(woman screams)
* *
(indistinct chatter)
Hey, okay,
we're clearing this area.
-Phones away. Sir.
-OFFICER: Ma'am. Ma'am.
NUÑEZ:
Sir, please. Phones away.
Keep it moving.
Ma'am. Thank you.
Clearing this out.
Get these guys...
Get these guys away from here.
Please, keep moving.
Thank you.
We're closed up now.
Clearing this out.
Thank you.
Sir?
Sir.
LANGDON:
I know these symbols.
He's got Peter.
That's his ring.
NUÑEZ:
Stay right there.
* *
PETER: The shucking
of the oyster. We break in
at the hinge here.
Then we...
tear through
the adductor muscle.
Sure not to break the mantle.
Et voilà.
-(Isabel chuckles)
-Wow.
ISABEL: Don't worry.
He does this
-every year.
-The oysters or the TED Talk?
-(chuckles)
-PETER: One of the many lies
told to us at Thanksgiving
is that early American settlers
feasted
on turkey.
Now, duck, maybe. Swan, even.
But most certainly, bountifully,
-on oysters.
-My dad would rather us be
historically accurate
than happy.
PETER:
Robert appreciates history.
He may be
one of the sharpest students
I've ever known.
But I've told him
that raw intellect
can only get you so far.
KATHERINE:
Raw oysters,
on the other hand,
is a very different story.
PETER:
Indeed, it is.
-I lost track of time.
-Well, Descartes
will do that to you.
My daughter is doing a thesis
on Passions of the Soul.
ISABEL:
I originally thought
it was a romance novel,
but I was wrong.
It is not.
Well, it does
romanticize nonsense.
Have you ever read him?
I-I tried.
Genius mathematician.
He lost me
when he said the pineal gland
was the gateway
-to the soul.
-Can you disprove it?
Do I need to?
A-As far as I can tell,
he had a prehistoric
understanding of anatomy.
And yet he posited
psychophysiological laws
-that are still relevant today.
-Psychophysiological.
Oh, that's right.
Peter mentioned
you're into the pseudosciences.
-Did he?
-PETER: "A credible mind
drawn to incredible things"
-is the way I put it.
-Mm.
I suggest we change the subject.
Zachary, why don't you tell us
about your itinerary.
PETER:
Yes, my son is going
to the Middle East
to lay siege to the beaches
-of Aqaba.
-Just to get away
from here, really.
Really? Why?
Oh, I-I just mean, uh,
is it always like this?
Like, debating,
exchanging ideas,
even if they aren't...
credibly rational?
(chuckles):
What... I-I just mean, um...
You're all very lucky...
to have this.
You really hit the jackpot
with this one, Dad.
Each year,
Professor Solomon
takes in a stray
for Thanksgiving as some sort
of a charitable exercise,
but, really, he's just looking
for a new audience
to fawn over him.
What he doesn't realize is
you don't really care
any more than we do.
I care.
-(chuckles)
-I think he really does.
Can we keep him?
PETER:
I think
he's earned an open invitation.
(indistinct chatter)
All right, let me know
when you hear from the chief.
In the meantime,
we sweep the building
and keep it locked down.
-OFFICER: Roger that.
-Are you in charge here
-or what?
-Yeah. Um, for now.
For now? What does
that-what does that mean?
Just give me a sec, okay?
Ma'am, you can't be here.
-This is a crime scene.
-Maybe you shouldn't let
a bunch of tourists
tweet photos of it.
-Excuse me?
-Just a thought.
Oh, sorry.
(chuckles)
I should have this on.
Inoue Sato.
CIA? I-I thought the Bureau
handled kidnappings.
They do.
Sometimes. It depends.
I can't really
say anything else.
Those two are with me, by the
way. They'll need full access.
So, I understand this hand may
have belonged to Peter Solomon.
Yeah. You know him?
-Of him.
-Ah, well,
this is Robert Langdon.
He's a coworker
of Mr. Solomon's.
-The suspect called him. Twice.
-Yeah,
we-we're not coworkers.
I teach at Harvard.
Symbology.
Peter was my mentor.
This morning,
I got a call from his assistant.
Least, thought it was
his assistant.
He said that Peter
wanted me to come down,
speak at the Capitol
at this gala.
Peter's not known
for his consideration
of other people's time,
so it didn't seem
out of the ordinary to me
-to get on a plane...
-Robert. Take a breath.
(exhales)
Did this person
say what he wants?
Uh... it won't
make sense to you.
Tell me anyway.
He said he's looking
for an ancient portal
buried within the city.
He wants me to locate
-and unlock it.
-And that means something
to you?
It didn't until I saw that.
On the other three fingers,
I expect you'll find
more tattoos.
A sun, a lantern and a key.
* *
He's replicated
the Hand of the Mysteries.
It's an icon you see
throughout history.
The alchemists, the cabalists.
It's an invitation to seek
a body of ancient knowledge
beyond a mystical gateway.
-A portal.
-NUÑEZ: Yeah, the suspect
walked through security earlier
with his hand in a sling
like it was his.
And he was wearing makeup,
I think.
-Concealer.
-You got a good eye.
See if the sergeant
can pull some security stills
of the suspect.
The ring on Peter's hand--
33rd-degree Mason.
From what I remember,
that comes with some
ancient knowledge of its own.
Despite what some people think,
the Masons
are essentially a social club.
Still, it could explain
why he was targeted.
If this guy thought Peter knew
about the portal thing...
Then he would've been
sorely disappointed.
Peter knows that what this guy
is after doesn't exist.
He has a daughter, right? What's
your relationship with her?
-Uh, we're friends.
-We need to make sure
she's secure,
and we'll need a DNA reference
to confirm that's actually
her father's hand.
Uh, let me do it.
Let me-let me call her first.
(phone vibrates)
-Hey.
-LANGDON: Katherine.
Something's happened.
It's your dad. He...
He's been taken.
And, um, I don't know exactly
what's going on,
but we're gonna get him back.
* *
(phone vibrates)
Have they left the Rotunda?
OFFICER:
Hey!
Hey, you can't be in here, man.
Park's closed.
Sorry, I didn't realize.
Hey, Ma, I got to go.
Rich!
Those yours?
Uh, does it look
like I'd wear that?
RICH:
So that wasn't you
by the Capitol earlier?
Oh, yeah. They were vetting me
for the Supreme Court.
Yeah, very cute.
Let's see some ID.
Man, I don't...
I don't want any trouble.
RICH:
Just want to see some ID, sir.
Of course.
Yeah. Yeah.
-(grunting)
-OFFICER: Hey!
(choking)
(grunting)
No! Stop!
(screaming)
(whimpering)
No.
(panting)
(grunts)
Liberty. Freedom.
E pluribus unum.
13. 13. 13 states.
Local PD found Solomon's car
in a lot off of Canal Road.
No cameras. No witnesses.
No signs of struggle.
You know, it would
be helpful if I knew
what our actual interest
in this is.
I know.
Liberty. Freedom.
13 maidens.
SATO:
What's he doing?
No idea.
"Peter will point the way."
He said that on the call.
The fresco above us
is Brumidi's
Apotheosis of Washington.
From the Greek "apo," to become,
and "theos," God.
There, in the central panel,
George Washington is ascending
on a cloud above the mortals.
His moment of transformation.
I think this guy
is telling us what he wants.
Apotheosis.
To become a god.
And he thinks he can do that
by accessing
this ancient knowledge?
It was said to hold the keys
to unlocking abilities
that lay dormant
in the human mind.
I'm-I'm playing catch-up,
but th-the ransom
is superpowers?
Everything he's doing
is-is in accordance
with ancient protocols.
The Hand of the Mysteries.
It must be presented
in a sacred place.
-That's why he chose this room.
-SATO: Sacred?
They sell "We the People"
shot glasses in the gift shop.
It's symbolic.
This room was built
as a tribute
to the Temple of Vesta in Rome.
There's a purpose
to-to everything he's done.
And everything he's said.
What is it?
"As above, so below."
It's the last thing he said
before he hung up.
I wonder...
-Oh.
-Wait.
There it is.
Roman numerals?
No. As a subtractive notation,
it doesn't work.
-Uh, e-excuse me.
-It could be, uh, an Arabic...
-Not Arabic.
-No?
SATO:
It's a specialty of mine.
If I can just interject
for a quick second...
Well, it actually looks
like a runic variation.
Hey, smart people.
It's upside down.
So it's not 885.
It's S-B-B. Right?
We use that numbering system
here in the Capitol.
Subbasement.
Room 13.
Okay. Let's go.
* *
(drill whirring)
Come on.
(sighs)
Sorry, Dad.
(exhales)
-Aah!
-(Katherine grunts)
(grunting)
What are you doing
in my father's house?
(panting)
CIA?
Your turn.
Let me see some ID.
How's that?
I'm gonna need you to come
with me to the Capitol.
NUÑEZ:
No, Larry. Surprisingly,
the master key
doesn't say "master" on it.
No labels. Just numbers.
Find it.
Okay. Down we go.
(Langdon breathing shakily)
* *
(water dripping)
You good, man? Come on.
* *
We're below sea level, so it
can get pretty wet down here.
Probably why no one
ever comes down anymore.
SATO:
Didn't stop Peter Solomon.
They just told me
room 13 was designated
as his private space.
NUÑEZ:
Oh, this keyhole's
a bit funky.
None of these are gonna work.
(keys jangling)
(Nuñez grunting)
LANGDON:
Hang on.
This sconce.
Sprigs of acacia.
Masons consider it
a symbol of immortality.
* *
(lock clicks)
(door creaks)
SATO:
Do you have any idea
what Peter would have been doing
down here?
NUÑEZ:
What's that smell?
Sulfur.
SATO: Maybe you don't know Peter
as well as you thought.
These bones look human.
They are.
Uh-huh.
And this book, it's bound
in human flesh or what?
It's just a Bible.
This isn't
some sacrificial altar.
It's a Masonic Chamber
of Reflection.
-Hmm.
-Meant to be a place
to come and reflect
on one's own mortality.
-With some dude's femur?
-That any stranger
than chanting
before a four-armed elephant
or praying at the feet
of a man nailed to a cross?
-SATO: Something wrong?
-LANGDON: This symbol. The...
The Leviathan Cross.
It's incongruous.
It shouldn't be here.
What about this?
LANGDON:
"VITRIOL."
It's an acronym.
How's your Latin?
Not as good as my Arabic,
better than my German.
"Visita interiora terrae
rectificando invenies
occultum lapidem."
"Visit the interior
of the Earth,
and, purifying it,
you will find a dark stone."
Hidden stone, technically.
(faint creaking)
SATO:
Do you know what it means?
LANGDON:
It's a Masonic mantra.
"Purifying it,
you will find the hidden stone."
(chuckles softly)
(creaking)
Did you happen to put that key
back in the sconce?
You-you mean this?
No, no one told me
to put it back.
Maybe we should hurry.
Uh, in alchemy,
the first purification
is dissolution,
represented by the dissolving
of calcifications.
These letters
are calcifications.
It's salt.
(stone scrapes)
The wall.
LANGDON:
I know, it's remarkable.
No, the wall!
I-I think it's moving.
LANGDON:
These aren't just letters.
They're handles.
(rumbling)
-(grunts) Damn it,
I can't get it.
-Yeah, yeah, we're okay.
We're okay. Hurry, please.
Oh!
Oh, man.
That's not... That's not
gonna hold. We got to go.
Watch out. Watch out.
Hurry up. Come on!
What we waiting for?!
(Sato grunting)
LANGDON:
Whoa.
Whoa, whoa.
(Sato panting)
SATO:
Come on, let's go.
-NUÑEZ: Come on!
-(Sato grunts)
NUÑEZ:
Langdon!
SATO:
One step at a time. Come on!
NUÑEZ:
Are you kidding me right now?!
-Come on!
-SATO: You've got this. Come on!
-Let's go!
-NUÑEZ: Take a step.
Come on.
Just keep going forward.
Langdon! Langdon!
-SATO: Langdon, come on!
-NUÑEZ: Snap out of it!
-(breathing shakily)
-(water dripping)
SATO:
Come on!
(Langdon panting)
-(Nuñez panting)
-(Sato coughs)
* *
I used a common
Masonic decryption key,
and the, uh, resulting cleartext
is, to use a technical term,
gibberish.
Well,
maybe your decryption's off.
No.
I think it's a segmented cipher.
When the Greeks wanted to store
secret information,
they inscribed it on a tablet,
then shattered it into pieces,
storing each piece
in a separate location.
Only when the pieces
were gathered together
could the secret be understood.
Which would explain
why the top is missing.
The capstone
could complete the message.
In theory.
Why are you here?
You said before that, uh,
maybe I didn't know Peter
as well as I thought.
Was he working for the CIA?
No.
(phone vibrates)
LANGDON:
It's him.
Hang on.
-Go.
-Just like we talked about.
Hello?
MAN:
What have you found?
Um, I'll tell you,
but first, I-I want to know
that Peter's okay.
I want proof that he's alive.
Oh, he's alive.
But,
by any measure,
in great distress.
You expect me
to just accept that?
I expect you to focus
on what you can control,
which is whether
he lives or dies.
There's a small granite pyramid.
Contains a numerical grid.
But if this is your, uh, portal,
then I'm afraid
I got some bad news.
I'll be the judge of that.
Any deciphering of the grid
would require further context.
The capstone.
You didn't think
it was gonna be that easy,
did you?
We have more work to do, Robert.
Find it.
I-I-I wouldn't know
where to start.
Well, this is the journey.
And it's just begun.
Got the trace.
Three miles away.
-Let's go.
-We're on our way.
Not you.
I'm not gonna just sit here.
You're the only expert we have.
I need you safe and secure.
Sounds like a nice way of saying
I'm not allowed to leave.
-You're not.
-Hey. Hey. Hey!
* *
NUÑEZ:
Hey, man. They didn't have oat.
Soy okay?
(sighs)
Guess it'll have to be.
-Thanks.
-Yep.
Look...
I know you want to get out there
and help find your friend,
but I think
CIA lady's pretty capable.
I think there's something
she's not telling us.
(sighs)
It's a "need to know" world,
man.
(sighs)
I did two tours in the desert.
I'm still waiting
for someone to tell me why.
They like their secrets.
Yes, they do.
All this talk about a portal,
that's what Peter was to me.
A gateway.
To books. To-to art.
Myth.
You think you know everything,
then you meet someone
who actually does?
It's, uh, it's-it's humbling.
And it could be hard.
He'd push me to open my mind,
appreciate points of view
that I found...
...unsupportable.
PETER:
Good evening.
Oh, hey.
Sorry to interrupt, but, uh...
I'm sure we're all relieved
that I did.
(chuckles): Oh, no.
No, no, no, no. We were... We...
-Dad, what are you doing
in here by yourself?
-Okay.
-Working on the notes
for my lecture.
-You're hiding
from your guests.
Hiding from
your mother's guests.
Sorry to disturb you.
Uh, we should probably...
I'm happy you did,
'cause I actually wanted
to ask you about these notes,
and your thoughts always
change things for the better.
-Uh...
-(laughs) Okay, you know what?
I'm gonna get us a drink. Um...
Dad? Scotch?
I'm good, Katie.
Thank you.
I thank the gods
I had the good taste
to introduce you two.
Katherine would
probably call it fate.
Or the immutable reality
of the Akashic Field.
You don't believe
in that kind of thing, do you?
God, no.
But you do believe in Katherine?
The worst thing you can do
if you love someone
is to give them reason
to doubt themselves.
Our partners. Our family.
These are people we lean on
because these are
people we trust
and who trust in us
no matter what.
I guess I-I never had that.
You have it now.
Yeah, he never gave up on me.
(sighs)
I can't give up on him.
* *
(grunts)
SATO:
Solomon's phone.
-Goodness.
-SOJANI: Okay. So,
the statue's a symbol.
That's how
this guy works, right?
Like with the fresco
at the Capitol?
It's not about the statue.
It's about the inscription.
"Mundus vult decipi
ergo decipiatur."
"The world wants to be deceived,
so let it be deceived."
Deceived.
Well, that sounds like
we brought everyone
out here for nothing.
Almost everyone.
Get Simmons on the phone.
(phone vibrates)
-Yeah.
-(speaking indistinctly)
Oh, it's all quiet over here.
Yeah, we are secure.
Okay.
* *
(Nuñez breathing raggedly)
Whoa.
Why are you doing this?
Mal'akh needs you free of here
to find the portal.
Mal'akh.
JANITOR:
Take that and go.
He'll be in touch.
-He needs help.
-JANITOR: He'll need last rites
if you don't go.
* *
-Whoa, whoa, whoa!
-DISPATCHER: Officer down.
-Repeat, we have reports
of an officer down.
-OFFICER: Stop!
DISPATCHER:
Can we get EMS Code 3,
East Capitol and First.
-That's coming
from inside the Capitol.
-Stay here.
-What does this have to do
with my dad?
-Just stay here.
-Hey!
-ADAMU: CIA.
(indistinct chatter)
SOJANI:
Still no sign of Langdon.
But we've got everyone looking.
I want to show you something.
You asked about my interest
in this case.
Solomon's kid worked for us?
Briefly.
In Ankara.
Then he got locked up
for trafficking.
(shouts)
Three years ago,
there was a riot in the prison.
(breathing raggedly)
SATO:
Zachary Solomon
was beaten to death.
So, what's the connection?
That's what you're going
to Turkey to find out.
Langdon?
(indistinct announcement
over P.A.)
Langdon!
Kat.
What are you doing here?
Are you okay?
No, not really.
Where are you going?
What do...
Oh, my God.
Are you...
Is that blood?
It's not mine.
Tell me what's going on.
You're gonna have to trust me.
If I'm gonna help your dad,
I got-I got to go.
-Robert.
-The people who took him
want me to find something.
A... A-An artifact,
a piece of a very old puzzle.
-Then I'll help you.
-No.
They shot two people back there
so I could do this thing alone.
It's... It's not safe.
I got to go.
I have something.
-Katherine.
-Maybe it can help.
(sighs)
What is it?
I don't know,
but Dad said that its secrecy
was more valuable than his life.
He said that?
Those exact words?
Close enough.
He made me promise to destroy it
if anything
ever happened to him.
I'm coming with you.
What is it?
LANGDON:
A Leviathan Cross.
MAL'AKH:
There's been a shift.
A stirring in the atmosphere.
Can you feel it?
Your fate
is in Robert's hands now.
And the fate of mankind,
as well.
Now, hopefully,
he's not a disappointment.
Like your son.
Poor, disappointing Zachary.
You know nothing of my son.
I do, though.
I was there with him in the end.
I was the one who ended him.
* *
SATO:
Langdon, I'm giving you a chance
to come out on your own
or I'm sending someone else
in after you.
-(hangs up)
-Robert?
Well, you just hung up
on the CIA.
I've been friends with Peter
for 30 years.
He was the one who brought me
into the group.
The Leviathan Group
was formed based on
a belief that the ancient wisdom
unlocked hidden power.
And what would happen
if this power
fell into the wrong hands?
LANGDON:
And you think Peter
would die to keep
-that secret?
-Be careful.
We wouldn't be here
if had any other options.
You were right about Sato.
There's something she's hiding.
Do what you do best.
(grunting)
LANGDON:
Only way to get Peter back
is to find the capstone,
give Mal'akh what he wants.
Time is running out.
We have to finish this.
-Or my dad is dead.
-MAL'AKH: Death will be
a blessing for him.
* *
You're in my world now.