MAL'AKH:
Peter will point the way.
Previously on
"The Lost Symbol"...
He's got Peter.
CIA? I thought the Bureau
handled kidnappings.
SATO: So, this hand belonged
to Peter Solomon.
Peter was my mentor.
SOJANI:
Solomon's kid worked for us?
Briefly. Three years ago.
He was beaten to death.
In Ankara.
LANGDON: The capstone
could complete the message.
Mal'akh needs you
to find the portal.
We have more work to do, Robert.
Your fate
is in Robert's hands now.
If I'm gonna help your dad,
I got to go.
I'm coming with you.
(subway rattling)
(drumming)
(crowd chatter)
-What is that?
-Gilded edges,
Hebrew...
Probably a religious text.
(reading Hebrew)
-Ah, my Hebrew's a little rusty.
-Okay, I have an app.
Right. 'Cause you never Google.
-I didn't say anything.
-Yeah, I know your looks.
I work on the
Global Consciousness Project
with scientists from all over.
This has saved me
more than once.
First Kings, chapter three.
Old Testament.
Uh, the Judgement of Solomon.
Huh.
(phone buzzes)
Langdon...
LANGDON:
What? Who sent this?
"Pass the wayfarer.
Find the wolf."
What?
We should go.
-Katherine. Your phone.
-What? Oh.
Pass the wayfarer...
What are you doing?
Find the wolf.
There's a hatch here.
(drumming intensifies)
* *
(grunts)
BELLAMY:
There's a bolt to the left.
Slide it over.
-Warren?
-(bolt thuds)
It's good to see you,
Katherine.
Sorry it's under
these circumstances.
-Phones?
-We left them.
-Good.
-Does someone want to tell me
what's going on?
We can talk on the way.
* *
Where'd you lose him?
ADAMU: Tunnel, on the way
to the platform.
I don't know.
He was there, then he wasn't.
And Solomon's daughter
was with him.
Katherine?
We'll keep looking,
check the cameras,
comb the tracks.
-They've got to be close.
-Boss is here.
Keep me posted.
BLAKE: We're saying
disgruntled employee.
Workplace shooting.
-Apolitical.
-SATO: It's my fault.
I left him exposed.
You did your job.
What about the shooter?
The janitor is
Nicholas Bastin. 37.
Former Army medic.
Honorable discharge 2015.
No criminal record.
Politically ambivalent.
Six months ago,
he goes off the grid.
-And the other one?
-No hits. He's a ghost.
And in addition to leaving
a severed hand
at the Capitol, he left
two uniforms half-dead
in the park a mile away.
What if there's a connection?
To...?
Zachary Solomon died
in a prison riot in Turkey.
And whoever killed him...
left this.
Triskelion.
It's an important symbol
in Freemasonry.
Or maybe you're reading
too much into this.
You're making it personal.
Maybe.
And the artifact you found
in the Capitol basement?
The pyramid's gone.
With Langdon.
And with it, many secrets.
We've heard of this portal.
And we are interested in it
and any information
it might lead to.
But from where I'm sitting,
it looks like our best chance
to find it has flown the coop.
We need Langdon.
What about Peter Solomon?
We can walk and chew gum.
But I would manage
my expectations on that front.
MAL'AKH (recording):
Peter is in the Araf.
LANGDON:
I'm sorry, what?
MAL'AKH: The borderland
between Heaven and Hell.
LANGDON: Yeah, thank you.
I know what the Araf is.
MAL'AKH: And whether
he returns to your world
or moves on to the next
will depend on your actions.
He might already be dead.
That call was made
from Solomon's phone.
You were monitoring him?
We monitor a great many people.
Find Langdon.
BELLAMY:
I've been friends with Peter
for 30 years.
LANGDON:
Freemason friend?
"The Wayfarer."
A painting by Bosch known for
its Masonic references.
I'm sorry for all
the cryptic texts,
but I was afraid your messages
were being monitored.
LANGDON:
Right.
So we're just supposed
to follow you now?
-No questions.
-I trust him.
He was like an uncle
to me and Zach.
Which doesn't explain
how he knew where to find us.
I used to be with
the State Department.
Then I got a new job:
Architect of the Capitol.
Which puts me in charge
of every building
in the Capitol complex.
I know everything that goes on
in these buildings
and under them.
(door closes loudly)
We're under
the Library of Congress now--
the old circulation room.
LANGDON:
Huh.
-So that's the, uh...
-The old conveyor system.
It ran books
under the other two buildings.
Look, you'll be safe here.
Just lay low for a bit.
Lay low? How is that
going to help Dad?
BELLAMY:
Just until we figure out
our next steps.
May I see it?
LANGDON:
I used the Mason cipher
to translate it, but...
It requires the capstone
to be understood.
You know about the capstone.
Do you know
where we can find it?
No.
Long ago, the Master Masons,
they hid the pyramid
and the capstone
in two different locations.
No one person is allowed to know
the location of both pieces.
Dad kept this in his safe.
We think it might be a clue.
It's from First Kings.
The Judgment of Solomon.
KATHERINE:
It's just your typical,
moderately disturbing
Bible tale.
I don't know why
he'd keep it in a safe.
-Neither do I.
-LANGDON: There has to be
something about this
beyond the story we all know.
Well, if there is,
I don't know about it.
Rest.
I'll press my contacts
to find out
if there's more information
about your father.
Katherine...
I'm so sorry.
Extra phone?
It's not mine.
Back at the Capitol,
they had me in a room,
under guard.
A man came in
dressed like a janitor.
He shot the guards
and gave me this.
Mal'akh.
That's what he called him.
The person who took Peter.
How many people
are a part of this?
I don't know.
And the hand?
How do they know it was Dad's?
It was his ring.
Well, a ring can be switched.
The hand had been
severed... recently.
That still doesn't prove
it was his.
Y-You're right.
No, don't do that.
Don't humor me.
I'm not going to break.
I-I don't know
what I'm supposed to say.
That's not a surprise.
I'm sorry. I'm just trying
to process all of this.
I just need him to be okay.
Me, too.
(inhales sharply)
(exhales sharply)
(groans)
* *
(rattles softly)
(hinges creaking)
* *
ISABEL:
Trafficking?
What does that even mean?
Well, u-usually,
it refers to, uh,
illegal trading,
dealing narcotics...
In this case,
a staggering amount of heroin
found in Zachary's apartment.
The question is, what are
we going to do about it?
Um, Professor Sahin
wrote a study
on the Turkish justice system
for Human Rights Watch.
She might have a contact.
Maybe this is just
what he needs.
To rot in a decrepit,
Second World prison?
To not be rescued
from his own mistakes.
ISABEL:
He doesn't need
your lessons right now.
He needs your love.
I gave him my love.
He rejected it.
You wanted him to be
just like you.
To share in your obsession
with all of this... trivia.
That's what he rejected.
But it doesn't mean that you
get to stop being his father.
Excuse me.
(Langdon sighs)
You don't really think
we should leave him there.
Robert, am I being unfair here?
You-you don't have
to answer that.
I-I think you're just...
a father
in a difficult situation,
and I... I get that.
(door closes softly)
(quiet footsteps approaching)
Hey.
Hey. Hey.
KATHERINE:
Langdon, what are you doing?
Let go. He took the page.
I thought he was holding
something back before.
He knows why it's important.
Is that true?
I took an oath to protect it.
Protect what?
The ancient wisdom.
BELLAMY:
Look, I understand
-your skepticism...
-Do you? How generous.
But there are other things
at play here.
I know these stories.
And that is all that they are.
Take the myth of
the Masonic pyramid,
built so high God could
reach out and touch it.
And you're telling me that's
what they're talking about?
Well, perhaps those stories
were deliberately exaggerated.
-To what end?
-So that academics
like you would
continue to believe
they're a myth.
So no one would search for them.
It's a piece of rock.
It's a map.
(clicking nearby)
KATHERINE:
What was that?
Maybe we should continue
this discussion upstairs.
There's a sect
within the Masons.
Very small and very secret.
The Leviathan Group.
Our purpose is to make sure
that the ancient wisdom
stays hidden,
until such time
as the world is ready.
This is what Peter wants.
So h-he also took your oath.
You said the pyramid was a map.
What does that mean?
It is said that,
when brought together,
the pyramid and the capstone
will reveal the location
of the portal.
And you think Peter would die
to keep this secret?
You're entitled to your beliefs,
as unhinged as they are,
but this is his life.
What is it, anyway,
this secret wisdom?
Is it an... an equation?
An invocation?
BELLAMY:
No one knows.
No one living, at least.
Well, this is all
very on-brand for Dad.
He'd always say
that modern physics
was only starting to comprehend
what the ancients knew
to be true.
He's why I do what I do.
He's very proud of your work.
The genetics of psychic ability,
collective consciousness...
A lot of people
think it's crazy.
But for all my certainty that
I'm right and they're wrong,
there is always a subtle voice
in my head,
this doubt:
What if it's not real?
Don't you want to know
if it's real?
I'm not sure I'm meant to know.
KATHERINE:
I saw the way you looked
at that pyramid.
I know that look.
You may never get
this chance again.
Help us find it.
The Hebrew...
It's code.
If that's true,
then there has to be a way
to decipher it.
A key.
BELLAMY:
Yes.
And Peter's the only one
that has it.
That's how it goes.
One veil is lifted
only to reveal another.
He'd have it close.
Somewhere he can keep
an eye on it.
Maybe even on him.
Override key
for the safe in my lab.
I keep it on me at all times.
-Does Peter even wear jewelry?
-Just one piece.
His ring.
You don't wear yours.
Only for functions.
-A lot of Masons do that.
-Not my dad.
He always wears his.
Always.
It's small. It doesn't mean
it's not concealing information.
Problem is:
it's in the possession
of the Capitol Police.
I don't suppose
these tunnels could sneak us
into their evidence room.
I can't help you with that.
I might know someone who can.
NUÑEZ:
You know they make it
out of pig bones, right?
Gelatin.
You a vegan?
Hell no. I eat animals.
The meat parts,
not the... other parts.
I could, uh...
get you some applesauce.
Why all the baby food?
Doctor said the bullet
didn't hit anything important.
Still, you're technically
recovering from surgery.
Okay, I'll take the applesauce.
(clears throat)
(Nuñez exhales)
(footsteps approaching)
That was quick.
No, wait!
NURSE (distorted):
You awake, awake?
(normal voice):
You awake?
I think so.
You have a visitor.
Hey.
How you feeling?
Pretty good, you know?
Doc says I could be out
in a day or two.
How's your agent?
Oat Milk.
He didn't make it.
Damn. Sorry.
Can you tell me what he said?
The shooter. To Langdon.
I don't know.
It's all just...
It's okay. Don't force it.
Who is he? The janitor.
I mean, there's got to be...
video, facial recognition,
fingerprints...
You get an ID yet?
Can't say.
Hey, it's me, remember?
The guy who stopped
the giant wall
from turning us all into panini?
(chuckles softly)
Dude came into my building.
That building.
You know what I'm saying?
Give me a name.
Right.
It's a need-to-know world.
(Adamu clears throat)
Get some rest.
(indistinct chatter)
Someone's helping them.
And I still don't know
how they got out of there.
We swept the station
in every direction.
-What about down?
-The tunnels?
There's no public access.
This isn't a public person.
Think they might've
dropped this.
When you found Katherine
in her father's house,
did you search her?
Mm-mm.
It's okay.
The Capitol Power Plant on 25th
should be able to tell us
who has access to the tunnels.
I'll head over now.
Where you gonna be?
Peter Solomon's.
(bell tolling in distance)
* *
Well done.
We'll be needing more sedative.
I'll go see my contact
at the hospital.
Unless you need me
looking after Solomon?
No, it's fine.
He isn't going anywhere.
* *
(clank, whirring)
(whirring stops)
ZOE:
I don't understand.
Was it political?
Was he some kind of
insurrectionist, or what?
I don't know.
They're trying to figure it out.
Look, for four years
I went to sleep
afraid that you were gonna
be blown up by an IED
or get your head chopped off.
We're supposed to be safe here.
Hey, hey. It's okay.
I'm safe now.
KATHERINE:
Sorry to interrupt.
-I need to borrow him
for a CAT scan.
-For what?
I don't need any more
gamma rays warping my DNA.
I'm not trying to be
Spider-Man over here.
KATHERINE:
The Hulk.
Gamma rays created the Hulk.
Okay.
I will see you later.
Go.
Where's Angela?
The usual nurse.
KATHERINE:
Oh. Went home sick.
Sorry, sir, this patient's
extremely contagious.
Say what now?
I got shot.
I'm not infectious.
Maybe you got the wrong patient.
We need your help.
Oh, hell no.
(engine starts)
Just gonna take a quick look.
CIA. Busy day for you guys.
Your friend just left.
* *
(phone buzzing)
I think I know where
Katherine got that envelope.
-Is it important?
-No idea.
Do you know
if Blake sent anyone else
-over to Solomon's house today?
-Not that I know of.
You think he's got
someone shadowing you?
Wouldn't put it past him.
What'd you find at the plant?
So it services the Capitol
and 22 other buildings.
There's five miles
of tunnel down there.
And...
do we know who has access?
Engineers, service techs,
and three or four
federal agents.
Is the Architect of the Capitol
one of them?
His name's Warren Bellamy.
Yeah.
How'd you know that?
Get me his phone.
Get me everything.
(phone clicks off)
* *
NUÑEZ (whispering):
Are you crazy?
They're looking for you, man.
We wouldn't be here
if we had any other options.
Who's "we," anyway?
I'm Katherine Solomon.
LANGDON:
Peter's daughter.
Nice to meet you.
And-and I-I'm sorry.
-Thanks.
-We don't have a lot of time.
-What do you need from me?
-We need the ring.
From his hand.
The ring. That's evidence.
It's in a locker downtown.
Could you call someone?
Ask to get it released?
Sure, yeah, like takeout.
Maybe get some egg rolls.
You'd have to have someone
go in and sign it out.
We'll have to make do
without it.
Well, we don't have
any other options.
What do you need it for, anyway?
There's this page
from the Old Testament,
the story of Solomon.
We think it's encoded
and that the ring could contain
some type of decryption key...
Yeah, okay, that's fine.
He goes on, doesn't he?
Look.
Sato came to see me earlier.
And you were right,
there's something
she's hiding from us.
I can deal with secrets
to a point,
but I passed that point
when that guy started shooting.
Okay.
We'll need
to head by the cleaners.
I got another uniform there.
Nice ride.
LANGDON:
It belongs to a friend.
NUÑEZ:
Yeah? What's he do?
LANGDON:
Architect.
(Nuñez grunts)
(engine starts)
* *
(distant siren wailing)
(indistinct radio transmission)
NUÑEZ:
Hey.
Here goes nothing.
If I'm not out in 20 minutes,
call the cops.
(door opens)
(Nuñez groans)
(exhales sharply)
(Katherine exhales)
(sighs)
What are you going
to tell your mom?
KATHERINE:
Nothing.
She's finally in
a relatively stable place,
so I, um...
I can't tell her about this.
Not yet.
I should check in at the lab.
And my phone is in a tip jar.
Just pretend it's the '70s.
-Pre-cellular.
-Can it be the '80s?
The '80s...
Yeah. Great music.
By every cultural measure,
the '70s was the better decade.
The films alone...
What?
The '80s had amazing movies.
"E.T.," "Back to the Future,"
-"Willow"...
-Yeah.
I'm talking about
grown-up films.
"Godfather," "Network,"
"Chinatown"...
"Raiders."
"Raiders." "Raiders," okay.
(chuckles softly)
We had a few good months, right?
Before my family exploded
and we got caught
in the blast radius?
Ten and a half.
You had a lot going on.
(Langdon sighs)
Does Dad ever talk
to you about it?
About Zach?
No. You?
No.
I feel like he thinks
I blame him for what happened.
You know, it's hard.
Uh... I didn't know
that was going on.
I'm sorry.
I just want to see him
so I can tell him
it wasn't his fault.
The thought that
I might not get the chance
to tell him that is...
Katherine.
You're gonna get the chance.
I promise.
I just need him to know
that I love him.
It can't end with him
the way it did with Zach.
(distant clamoring)
* *
-(distant thudding)
-(gasps)
(buzzer sounds, lock clanks)
(panting)
(men speaking foreign language,
laughing)
(door clangs shut)
(exhales)
Boo.
Hi.
ZACH:
Special K.
Looking very civilized.
I'm surprised
they even let you in.
KATHERINE:
Robert knew someone
who, uh, helped me
pull some strings.
You're still with that twat?
What happened to your feet?
(soft chuckle)
Well, I was having
some interpersonal issues
in here,
and there was a rumor
I might try to escape.
So the guards made sure
I couldn't.
They can't do this to you.
Why?
Human rights?
You're in the wrong
part of town, K.
We have to get you out of here.
-We?
-Yes.
-(slam hand on table)
-You had your chance!
Dad could have gotten me out
with one phone call.
Instead, I got a letter.
"I won't allow you
to play victim
to circumstances
you alone created."
(laughs bitterly)
Did you hear about that?
(snorts) What am I saying?
You probably helped write it.
No. I didn't agree with him.
Oh, you disagreed.
How bold.
Really stood your ground, I bet.
I'm glad you came.
You can give him
a message for me.
(exhales)
(Zach grunts)
I'm not his son anymore.
(panting)
(tapping on window)
(inhales)
This the one?
Yeah.
Great. I'm-a go lie down now.
(car door opens)
(car door closes)
(panting)
* *
(urn thuds)
(lock clicks)
(electrical buzzing)
* *
What's this?
Hebrew Bible.
Published 1814.
It's in three parts.
The first part is the Torah.
300,000 letters
unchanged in over 2,000 years.
The Jewish tradition
of preserving text
is uncompromising.
If a scribe is found
to have added, subtracted
or altered a letter,
the whole manuscript
is invalidated and buried.
Hmm? Look.
Here.
This entire section--
the Hebrew has been changed.
So, what, the page is fake?
No, doctored.
To hide a message.
Look at it closely.
Can you see anything
unusual about it?
Well, looks normal enough.
All the requisite markings
are here:
the double-headed eagle,
triangle, the...
Oh, wait a minute.
This is supposed to be a yod,
but it's a he.
What?
Yeah, this mark on it.
A jeweler's mistake?
What does that look like to you?
Pi.
That is not a mistake,
it's a cipher.
Pi.
3.1415926...
You memorized pi?
Part of it.
Did a competition
in college once.
Got to the 417th character.
Only 417?
I got hungry.
Okay. So,
starting from there,
first number's three.
Circle the third character.
-Then one, circle the fourth.
-Okay.
Four, circle the eighth.
And so on.
Okay, so we have
14 letters that spell...
BELLAMY:
Let see.
Nothing. It's a jumble.
There must be another step.
One veil lifts
to reveal another.
(phone buzzes)
(phone buzzing)
Do you recognize the number?
No.
H-Hello?
Oh, good, my text worked.
I always send unknown calls
to voice mail, so...
Who is this?
Inoue Sato,
with Central Intelligence.
I'm a friend.
I was hoping to talk to Robert.
Uh, Robert...?
SATO:
We don't have time, Mr. Bellamy.
Peter's in trouble.
I don't want anyone else
getting hurt.
-Hello?
-Langdon.
What do you think you're doing?
I'm trying to help Peter.
You're going
to get yourself hurt.
Or Katherine.
I'm giving you a chance
to come out on your own, or...
Robert?
(sighs)
Let's go.
You just hung up on the CIA.
They're, uh, outside.
Let's go.
(indistinct chatter nearby)
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
(sighs) Damn. Somebody's coming
through the tunnels.
Is there any other way out?
KATHERINE:
What about this?
BELLAMY:
That's the old conveyor system.
I know. You said it goes
to the other buildings, right?
The system hasn't been
in use for years.
-But does it still work?
-It's worth a shot.
(clanking, whirring)
You want us to go in there?
Robert, it'll be okay.
I'll go first.
* *
In case of emergency.
(sighs)
I'm sorry,
but the library's closed.
SATO:
Where are they?
(clattering)
KATHERINE:
You doing okay back there?
How much further?
It's not far.
I can see the light.
I can't see anything,
my eyes are closed.
Just try to relax
and enjoy the ride.
(clattering stops)
Oh, no.
KATHERINE:
It's okay.
Oh, no.
KATHERINE (distantly):
It's okay.
You'll be okay.
BOY (shouting):
Help me! I'm stuck!
KATHERINE (echoing):
Robert?
BOY:
Help!
KATHERINE:
Robert.
BOY:
Help!
(normal voice):
Robert.
You're okay.
We're gonna crawl.
It's not that far.
-You can do this.
-(shudders)
Okay?
* *
(grunts)
PETER:
Hey, hey! Hey!
Hey! Hey, hey, hey!
Hey, hey, hey!
Stop, hey!
Hey!
Stop.
(distantly):
Hey.
(echoes):
Hey!
(exhales)
(sighs)
(groans)
Oh.
Oh, my God.
-Are you hurt?
-No. I'm fine.
I'm good. I'm good.
Okay, um...
I'm gonna go check up ahead,
make sure it's clear.
Yeah.
(breathing deeply)
(phone buzzing)
Hello?
MAL'AKH:
I understand you've picked up
a fellow traveler.
I am doing what you wanted.
You were told to do it alone.
No, I can't have you
distracted by emotions.
Cut her loose.
Or I'll have someone
do it for you.
(monitor beeping rhythmically)
(fly buzzing)
PETER:
Oh, thank God.
Hello?
Can I use your phone, please?
MAN:
I'm afraid not.
There's more to be done.
LANGDON (distorted):
Where is he?
(monitor beeping rhythmically)
MAL'AKH:
Peter is in the Araf.
The borderland between
Heaven and Hell.
Whether he returns to your world
or moves on to the next
will depends on your actions.