-Is everything okay?
-The less you know, the better.
Previously on
"The Lost Symbol..."
(coughing)
* *
SATO:
Three years ago, Zachary Solomon
-was beaten to death.
-So, what's the connection?
That's what you're going
to Turkey to find out.
I was there with him in the end.
Mal'akh made it very clear
that he wants me
doing this on my own.
-To the mind-body connection.
-Cheers.
* *
(horns honking)
(indistinct chatter)
* *
(clears throat)
(camera clicks)
(helicopter blades whirring)
(phone ringing)
Sojani, how's Turkey?
Great coffee.
And, I'm gonna be sending you
something shortly.
It's about the guy
that killed Zachary Solomon.
* *
(coffee pouring)
(cup clinking)
She was just here.
She came here to help me,
and the last thing
-I ever did was lie to her.
-No.
-I should have listened to you.
-Kat...
Why couldn't I just
listen to...?
We couldn't have known
he'd do something like this.
We did know! He warned us.
God, what was I thinking?
You were thinking
about your father.
KATHERINE:
My father.
We don't even know
if he's still alive.
He's alive.
I want to believe that, I do.
But... but if he's not,
then Trish died for nothing,
and all we're doing is
putting more people in danger.
I have to know if he's alive.
The only way to know for sure,
is for us to find the capstone
and give Mal'akh what he wants.
Not us.
You.
-I'm not leaving you.
-You have to do this alone,
you have to do what he wants.
Find the clues,
and hope that in the end,
you're right, and this ancient
wisdom is just some myth.
-Of course it is.
-You saw what was on that film.
I don't know what I saw.
A natural phenomenon,
a trick of editing...
Dad would always cite
these historical anomalies:
how did the ancient Egyptians
move hundred-ton stones
and build pyramids?
How did the pre-Columbian tribes
cut solid granite
with more precision
than a modern laser?
He thought that it could be
explained by some kind of power
that we've forgotten.
What if he was right?
What if that power reemerged in
the hands of someone truly evil?
I'm not going to be there
to remind you,
but if your mind isn't open,
you are limiting
what you can perceive,
and understand.
Like, answers from the universe?
We need all the help we can get.
Kat.
You can't go back to the house.
Sato probably has people
watching it.
I'm counting on it.
NUÑEZ:
So, this dude made them
kill themselves.
-A whole flock of birds?
-No, that would be impossible.
So, what then? Mass suicide?
I mean, can birds even do that?
It's got to be some kind of
trick photography.
If I can just find the edits...
Does this mean anything to you?
LANGDON:
Looks like a Triskelion.
Why?
Where he left Trish,
he drew that.
It represents different things
to different cultures.
Celtics, pagans, Freemasons.
Most often it represents
a-a cycle:
birth, death, rebirth.
Uh-oh.
You got that look.
Film companies use
shape sequences as edge code
to indicate different things
like date or production number.
Squares, triangles,
X's, crosses, but they didn't
start using three-shape
sequences until the '80s.
This circle shouldn't be here.
Um...
-(snaps fingers)
-That a scanner?
NUÑEZ:
Okay, here we are.
Boom, got that...
LANGDON:
Microdots were used
as early as World War I
in tiny notes
sent by carrier pigeon.
They could hide information
in something
as small as a punctuation mark.
Huh.
-There it is.
-What the...?
LANGDON:
"An architect with 46,
builds a bridge
of weightless bricks."
It's a riddle.
That's incredible.
Sojani found a former guard
from Ag Gecidi prison,
now runs a coffee shop
in Istanbul.
-He gave her this.
-What am I looking at?
SATO: Zachary Solomon,
three years ago at the prison.
And this is one
of the only known photos
of a prisoner who
went by the name of Samyaza.
Look familiar?
Intel points to him
as Zachary's likely killer.
Which means, he left this...
which should look familiar.
And when you consider that,
this guy?
Starts to look a lot like...
-...this guy.
-No way.
You think he came 5,000 miles
to finish off the family?
Never underestimate
a man with a God complex.
Hey, coast is clear out front.
-You got it?
-I think so.
"An architect with 46,
"builds a bridge
of weightless bricks.
"In Etam waits a stone
once hewn,
"returned at last
to mother's womb.
"Lastly,
heed the Starling's call,
for all who seek
must also fall."
Yeah, I'm more of a sudoku guy.
I'm not sure if I know
what it means either.
-The word "stone"
is pretty clear.
-Right.
Wh-Where's Etam?
It's interesting--
in the 9th century BC,
it was a city located
in the Kingdom of Judah.
In present day, I'd put it
somewhere south of Bethlehem?
See, I was thinking
I'd come with you
on this capstone mission,
but Israel might
be a little far for me.
Yeah, I appreciate the offer,
but I think it's best
if I go it alone.
Hold up.
You might need protection.
And who's going to protect you?
And your wife?
Zoe went to stay
at her cousin's, so...
Oh.
Um, I think I got to do this
on my own.
Okay. All right,
hold on, hold on.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Any sign of trouble,
make sure you get to a phone
and you call me.
-Thank you.
-Yeah?
-Yeah.
-All right.
Oh...
Oh, all right.
-Yeah.
-Come on. I'll let you
out the back.
(clock ticking)
* *
YOUNG KATHERINE:
What do you mean
you don't know what it is?
You know everything.
Well, that's the problem
when knowledge gets lost
to history.
But people have theories
about henges, okay?
Some people think that a henge
was an ancient burial site.
Other people say
that ancient astronomers
would use a henge as a sundial--
you know sundials?
And they'd use it to worship
a solar deity, a sun god.
I don't get why Zach and Mommy
didn't want to see this.
Well, sweetie, not everyone's
as curious as you are.
Always keep that.
You make me curious;
you're my own little sundial.
(sniffles)
(exhales shakily)
Where are you, Dad?
-(ticking)
-(heart beating)
(creaking)
Hi, Katherine.
I'm Inoue Sato.
(letter opener drops)
Can I have a few moments alone
in my father's house?
Do you think
that's such a good idea,
considering everything
that's happened?
You and Robert
have been through a lot.
I can't imagine what a shock
this has all been.
Your father,
now your research assistant.
-If there's anything I can do...
-I just want my dad back.
-Me, too.
-Really?
Because, as far as I can tell,
you've been spending
all your time chasing us.
I'm trying to protect you.
(indistinct chatter)
Roosevelt was once shot
in the chest
right before giving a speech.
Didn't faze him, though.
And he went on to give
an iconic performance.
They should have
tried poisonous gas.
Something happen?
Son, I've been locked up
in a CIA bed-and-breakfast
for the last 48 hours.
Seems they're after
the portal as well.
Look, you called me here. Why?
I decoded the Hebrew
from the Bible page.
It led us to
Oaken Hill Cemetery.
Guy showed up, tried to gas us;
I thought it might be one of
your Leviathan friends.
Well, there are members
within the group that, uh,
will go to extremes
to protect the secret.
How's Katherine?
Is she all right?
Not really.
A woman she works with
was killed last night,
body was left
at the Adams Memorial
as a warning to us.
I heard about that.
I had no idea
there was a connection.
A psychopath
is killing people to ensure
that I keep going,
and your Leviathan friends
are showing up in gas masks
trying to get me to stop.
But I can't stop,
not if I want to get Peter back.
How can I help?
We found a film.
There was a riddle hidden
in the edge code, a clue:
"An architect with 46."
The "S" of the six
written as a dollar sign.
Forty-six...
-That mean something to you?
-Well, if I were to guess,
I'd say that was in reference
to the architect
who designed the plans
for Washington, D.C.
Pierre Charles L'Enfant.
Who was a Mason,
so that part fits,
but, uh, why "46"?
And-and, what does that
have to do with the capstone?
Well, that's something
I can't tell you.
Because you're afraid
of who might find out?
Because it would be
better to show you.
KATHERINE:
Figured you'd come here.
I was banking on it, actually.
Okay.
I need something
only the CIA can provide.
Are you familiar
with psychometry?
Sometimes people can sense
things off of personal objects,
feel things about the people
the objects belong to.
Kind of a psychic surveillance.
But some people
don't need objects.
The CIA refers to them
as "remote viewers."
Not exactly my department.
But you know
about Project Stargate.
I know it was terminated
in 1995.
"Officially defunded"
was the technical designation.
A side program still exists.
If the remote viewing program
were still active,
hypothetically,
what's your interest?
I want to talk
to the head viewer.
I need him to find my father.
I'll see what I can do.
In the meantime, I received
some information today
that you might be interested in.
About my dad?
About the man who
might have taken him.
* *
His real name is a mystery. Most
of the personnel records were
burned up in the riot,
but at the prison,
he was called Samyaza.
-What kind of a name is that?
-Biblical. A fallen angel.
By all accounts,
this guy embraced the role.
Ran an extremely violent
drug gang at the prison,
inspired slavish devotion.
And those who wouldn't devote,
he'd break.
I think Zachary
was one of those people.
That makes sense.
My brother was pretty
antiestablishment,
so he wasn't about
to join some cult.
Whatever his issues, I think,
in his own way, Zachary was
trying to do the right thing.
What does this have to do
with my dad?
I think it might
be the same guy.
-What?
-First your brother,
then your father.
You could be next.
-This is crazy.
-Did Zach ever
mention anyone like this
at the prison?
I just don't-- I don't know,
not that I can remember. He...
He wrote me some letters.
There might be something
in them.
I haven't looked at them
in years.
I'd like to take a look,
if that's okay.
(phone vibrates)
My contact at Project Stargate
came through.
He found the man you asked for.
What now?
Bring him to my lab.
Then you can have the letters.
(breathing deeply)
(Bastin clears throat)
It's urgent.
Blood pressure's plunging,
respiration is weak.
-I can stabilize him.
-No need.
We'll continue as is.
-He could die.
-He must
go all the way
through the process
if he's to serve
his ultimate purpose.
BELLAMY: L'Enfant was on top
of the world; then, overnight:
persona non grata.
Some say he tried to
learn too much.
(trills, beeps)
All he left behind
were three watches,
three compasses,
two books and a map.
The last of
his earthly possessions.
Value at the time: $46.
Huh.
Take the books.
LANGDON:
3:40,
2:30,
5:45.
Why did the riddle lead to this?
Weird.
The 38 latitude marker
is in blue ink,
which would have been
extremely expensive
in the early 19th century.
Thirty-eight.
Look at that first watch:
three and eight.
This isn't right.
If this watch had stopped
at 3:40,
then the hour hand would be
two-thirds of the way
between three and four,
but both hands point precisely
at numbers-- same for these two.
Three and eight: 38.
Huh.
Degrees. Minutes. Seconds.
-These watches are coordinates.
-Coordinates for the capstone.
-Could be.
-Wouldn't you need longitude?
Yes.
Okay, where are you?
What does that look like to you?
It's a Masonic square.
The square represents morality.
And the compass:
boundaries.
Which gives us
a very familiar symbol.
BELLAMY:
"Ye who are engaged
in the pursuit of wisdom
must also make use of
the square and compass."
And the other.
So...
if 38 degrees,
26 minutes and 59 seconds
gives us our latitude line,
then the compasses
point to our longitude.
"X" marks the spot.
-Aquia.
-It's a town in Stafford County.
Wigginton, that's a quarry
in Aquia
that L'Enfant purchased.
-A quarry.
-In fact, half the buildings
are made with sandstone
from that quarry.
The Capitol Building,
the White House,
the Washington Monument...
"In Etam waits
a stone once hewn,
returned at last
to mother's womb."
The capstone is returned
to the quarry it came from.
SATO:
Katherine Solomon,
meet Ario Fazeli.
Thank you so much for coming.
Ario started at the Agency
in Tehran,
helping to remotely
track victims
during the hostage crisis.
-Now, he assists at...
-Fort Meade. I know who you are,
Mr. Fazeli. It's a pleasure.
Did you know he located
the "Titanic"
on the ocean floor?
They couldn't put it
in the movie, of course.
National security or whatever.
Well, I'm just very glad
you're here.
Shall we get started?
(birds chirping)
* *
(exhales)
"An architect with 46,
builds a bridge
of weightless bricks."
"In Etam waits
a stone once hewn,
"returned at last to mother's...
...womb."
(phone vibrating)
Yeah, hello?
Lace, Lace, I'm here.
You got something?
On the Janitor, right?
Nicholas Bastin.
You got an address?
Perry Street.
Yeah, up by LeDroit Park?
Uh-huh.
* *
(knocking)
Hello, ma'am,
my name is Alfonso Nuñez.
Are you with the CIA?
'Cause I already talked to them.
Never thought I'd hear those
words come out of my mouth.
I'm not with them.
I'm looking for Nicholas Bastin.
So are they.
They wouldn't tell me
what they wanted with him,
though.
Will you?
(sighs)
What is it?
What happened?
Your husband shot me,
and I'd like to ask him why.
But since I can't,
I'm here talking to you.
He's not my husband anymore.
Thank you.
When's, um,
last time you saw him?
I don't know,
six or seven months?
If you don't mind me asking,
how long were you together?
Six years,
before he got deployed.
He was a medic.
Wanted to come back
and become a surgeon,
but when he got back,
things were different.
I was there, too, uh...
It's tough on a marriage.
We tried to start a family.
But it wasn't meant to be.
Then he went back to
the Middle East to travel,
to get away.
Said he felt drawn to
that part of the world.
And he met someone, some guru.
Said he saved his life.
Did this guru have a name?
Nick never said it.
Like it was sacred or something.
You've seen him since--
did he seem "saved"?
-Um, I-I've got to go.
-(phone chimes)
I have work.
Yeah, I got to go, too.
I was, uh,
treated at Faiths United.
-You a nurse or...
-Pharmacist.
And I really got to go.
Thanks again for your time.
-(sighs)
-(door closes)
A fundamental belief
of noetic science is that
all information is connected
beyond space and time: hunches,
intuition,
even knowing when someone
is about to call
right before they do.
I'm a scientist,
so I'm the first to admit
that there is a wide margin
of error here.
But I need to try.
From what I know about
remote viewing,
it's location-directed.
He doesn't need coordinates?
That's the traditional model.
In this model,
Peter himself is the location,
and Ario is trying to see him,
or see what he sees.
It could come in flashes
of color,
smells, tastes, visual images
so fleeting, a less-trained mind
might miss them.
I have pickleball at 6:00.
Of course.
Whenever you're ready.
(wind whistling)
(panting softly)
(quietly):
So stupid.
(grunting)
(exhaling sharply)
Oh...
(breathing heavily)
(groans)
* *
(wind gusting)
"Lastly,
heed the Starling's call,
for all who seek
must also fall."
Again, the name of the target
is Peter Solomon.
Born in 1963,
alumnus of Harvard,
secretary of the Smithsonian.
My father.
There's... a degree
of intensity.
-Something biological.
-Human or animal?
There's an upright point.
A triangle, a rectangle.
A... a metallic taste,
something permanent.
Ah, something very white,
or that reflects light.
Some element containing water.
Cold, cold.
I-It's cold.
(gasping)
T-Tension.
There's slowing, it's...
darkening.
-(gasps)
-(monitor beeping rapidly)
(beeping slows)
(monitor flatlines)
I'm sorry, it's gone.
What happened?
What did you see?
Well...
It's all here.
It's just that I, um...
I sensed him, and then...
I don't think
he's with us anymore.
I'm so sorry.
SATO:
There's a wide margin
of error, you said that.
This doesn't mean anything.
I'm sorry, I need some air.
Did you really see him?
I sensed him.
(paper rustles)
(wind whistling)
(groans, inhales sharply)
-(panting)
-(bird cawing)
I got offered
a fellowship at Oxford.
Well, congratulations,
that's great.
Thank you.
I don't know what to do.
It'd take me away from Katherine
at the worst possible time,
as well as you, too.
(sighs) I've analyzed it
from every angle,
all the variables,
possible outcomes...
Yeah. Yeah, well,
you can't solve this
like one of your puzzles,
Robert.
This is different, this is life.
How do I decide then?
Use your intuition.
"To one of faith,
no explanation is needed.
To one of no faith,
no explanation is possible."
Thomas Aquinas.
You know I don't believe
in a higher power.
I mean,
have you never experienced
something you couldn't explain?
Have you never considered,
even for a moment,
there might be something
larger at work?
Uh, when I was eight years old,
I ran away from home.
I just remember
wanting to get away, hide.
And there was this, uh,
old well in the woods.
I lowered myself
about halfway down,
-and I lost my grip and fell.
-(echoes): Help!
So what happened?
I tried to get back up;
the walls were too wet.
I was stuck, treading water.
I yelled for help,
but no one came.
(echoing):
Help! Someone!
It seemed like hours.
I was going to give up,
let myself drown.
(gasping)
And then I...
I heard this voice,
like it was right there with me.
-It told me to keep going.
-VOICE (whispers): Keep going.
It said that they'd find me.
And they found you.
What did you think it was?
Oh...
I was exhausted, delirious.
It was my mind playing tricks.
Well, maybe it's time to
stop insisting that
that voice wasn't real,
and try listening for it again.
* *
(yells)
Whoa! Whoa!
(laughs, pants)
Oh...
And then it had to be a cave.
All right.
(bird caws)
* *
(gasps softly)
(clinks)
(low rumbling)
(scraping)
* *
"The secret hides
within The Order."
(wind whistling)
* *
Oh!
(grunts) Oh!
-* *
-(gasping)
NUÑEZ:
Take my hand!
-Gotcha.
-(grunting)
Come on.
(both panting)
Guess going solo
didn't exactly pan out.
-How did you...?
-Put a tracker in your coat.
Signal went dead
a little while ago.
Had this feeling something bad
might've happened,
so I followed it
and it led me here.
-You put a tracker on me?
-Yeah.
It was the hug, wasn't it?
It was the hug.
* *
Project Stargate?
I hear you pulled
some guy named Ario Fazeli
out of the sub-program.
Your job is
to find Robert Langdon,
not hold a séance with his
girlfriend; so what's going on?
I'm getting close to Katherine,
so that when Langdon surfaces,
I'm right there waiting.
Just like you want to be when
he finds your portal, right?
You chose me because I always
get it done, so let me do it.
Keep me apprised.
(exhales)
(crickets chirping)
I don't know about this, man.
She said she doesn't
want to see you.
-She's afraid.
-Yeah, she should be.
There she is.
I just think she'd
really want to see this.
NUÑEZ:
Yeah, I bet Mal'akh would, too.
Look, all I'm saying is,
is after everything I done
been through to save your ass,
I'm not gonna have you
get carved up 'cause you can't
keep your puzzle in your pants.
I'm just saying.
When I was out there today,
it was almost like,
for a moment, I don't know,
Peter was right there with me.
NUÑEZ:
That's why you want to see her.
Tell her you believe
in stuff now.
Maybe I just want her to know.
(sighs)
Drive.
-Yup.
-(engine starts)
* *
(exhales)
(sniffles)
I won't give up, Dad.
* *
(beeping)
(shuddering, groaning)
(panting)
Katie...
Shh.
Save your strength.
You're going to need it.