Previously on
"The Lost Symbol"...
This is breakthrough stuff.
And we may only be
scratching the surface.
BLAKE: Zachary Solomon died
in a prison riot in Turkey.
-We need Langdon.
-What about Peter Solomon?
MAL'AKH (recording):
Peter is in the borderland
-between Heaven and Hell.
-He might already be dead.
-LANGDON: It's a piece of rock.
-It's a map!
The pyramid and the capstone
will reveal the location
of the portal.
The Hebrew... it's code.
LANGDON (voice-over):
The ring could contain
some kind of decryption.
I am doing what you wanted.
MAL'AKH:
You were told to do it alone.
Cut her loose.
MAN:
Hey!
Hey, you can't be in here, man.
Park's closed.
Let's see some ID.
-Hey!
-(grunting)
-(gunshot)
-(yells)
(monitor beeping steadily)
The doctors say his partner
should make a full recovery.
What about him?
SATO:
Too early to say.
NUÑEZ:
I got sent 7,000 miles away
to fight extremists.
This isn't your fight.
I got a hole in my side
that says otherwise.
Some evidence went missing
yesterday.
Peter Solomon's ring.
You happen to know anything
about that?
What are you saying?
I'm saying if--
hypothetically--
you were aiding
Langdon and Katherine,
you'd only be putting them
in more danger.
You can't protect them
from the guy who did this.
You don't have to worry
about me.
I'm done playing the hero.
Made my wife a promise.
Make sure you keep it.
-Home sweet home.
-Hmm.
Oh, you make tostones, babe?
ZOE:
I wouldn't get my hopes up.
What?
KATHERINE:
Welcome home.
-Hey.
-How you feeling?
Hungry.
I said you guys
could set up here,
-to crack your Bible code,
not eat all my food.
-Oh.
I'll leave you
to your new friends.
-Maybe we should go.
-No. She's fine.
She's just worried about me.
Besides, I wouldn't go anywhere
right now.
We got a lurker.
Three houses down, north side.
-He's found us.
-No, it's Sato's people.
She came to the hospital
looking for you two.
And if you're wrong
and it's Mal'akh
or someone he sent, what then?
Why would he do that?
He needs you.
What's going on with you?
Nothing. Nothing, I'm fine.
Don't bullshit me, Robert.
There's something
I haven't told you.
He called when we were
at the library.
Who?
Mal'akh.
And he made it very clear
that he wants me doing this
on my own.
Without you.
-And you didn't tell me this
before?
-I didn't want to scare you.
Right.
Or maybe you agree with him.
Maybe you think you'd be
better off doing this alone.
-It's not about agreeing
with him.
-He has my father.
-It's about acknowledging the
very real danger he presents.
-I'm not going anywhere.
He has a literal assassin...
And that's what it's going
to take to get me to stop.
* *
Mr. Bellamy, Ellison Blake,
Central Intelligence.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Oh, I doubt that.
Looks like you put
your time here to good use.
Caught up on a little reading.
Uh, I miss books.
Sci-fi-- that was my first love.
I know it's not high art,
but the stakes--
I mean, how can you beat a story
about the end of the world?
I don't get much time
to read anymore.
Not fiction.
But that's okay,
because I've come to realize
that the most
interesting stories...
...are true.
I don't know what that is.
I do.
That's the sign
for the Leviathan Group.
It's a secret sect
within the Freemasons,
to which you belong.
I also know that their purpose
is to protect
some very old,
very valuable information.
So my question for you is:
where is it?
This portal
that I've heard about.
I don't know
what you're talking about.
But I do know
that you can't keep me here.
No.
Not here.
Any word on Langdon?
Not yet. Got people looking.
-What about him?
-Mm, he's the quiet type.
I think he could use
a change of scenery.
Have him moved over
to Southwoods.
LANGDON (quietly):
All right, where are we?
Okay, it's an equation.
Maybe an equation.
Maybe a...
Or coordinates?
Maybe coordinates.
No.
So what else?
(sighs) Ciphers...
A Hill cipher.
Maybe a Hill cipher.
It's right here.
(pencil tip snaps)
Damn it.
(Langdon sighs)
-Back to anagrams?
-Back to nowhere.
Clearly, a cipher was used
to alter the Hebrew,
likely one with...
Masonic characteristics
or themes.
I-I j... I just cannot
figure out what it is.
Well, maybe it's related
to the Solomon story.
When Dad talked
about the Masons,
he always said it was
a beautiful system of morality
-veiled in allegory.
-Veiled in allegory, yes.
It's in there,
hiding in plain sight.
-(pouring tea)
-I should be able to see it,
but I... can't think.
I'm blocked.
(sets teakettle down)
(takes deep breath)
Please reconsider.
-No.
-My-my brain, it...
it can't work if I'm
constantly worried about you.
Well, that's very sweet,
but I'm not gonna let this guy
tell me that I can't participate
in saving my own dad's life.
But... we're not gonna save him
if I can't work this out.
-We are going to work this out,
Langdon.
-Katherine...
At some point,
you are going to realize
-that you actually need me,
you know that?
-You have vast knowledge
in-in many topics.
Codebreaking isn't one of them.
It's not my knowledge
that's important, it's yours.
The key to decoding this
is buried in your mind...
and I know how to dig it out.
Uh...
(water burbling)
He's getting weaker.
But we can't rush the process.
You know that better
than anyone.
This things belonged to his boy.
They will find him in the Araf.
Then he will see himself
for who he truly is.
(echoing whisper):
What is the predominant wish
of your heart?
Has his daughter surfaced?
No. She's still off the grid,
as far as I can tell.
If they've ignored my warning...
...then they must be made
to understand.
(dog barking in distance)
(quietly):
Okay.
Trish.
Aw, that's so sweet.
You got me cannolis?
That's my jam.
Oh. Okay.
(chuckles)
We're hugging.
Come on inside.
Did you get a new EV?
-Yeah.
-That looks great.
How many miles are you getting?
-What?
-Yeah.
Hang tight.
(quietly):
Okay.
Thank you so much for coming.
Yeah.
So, who was that?
And why am I sneaking you
lab equipment
-disguised as baked goods?
-I'll explain later.
You're kidding, right?
Listen, I know
how this is gonna sound,
but the less you know
the better.
Is everything okay?
Everything's fine. I promise.
Um, I'm just really pressed
for time,
but I can't thank you enough
for coming
-all the way out here.
-Mm.
And I'll call you tomorrow.
(sighs)
It's your name on the door.
Hey, do me a favor?
Say goodbye to the complete
stranger that just hugged me?
(mouths)
That's tight.
So what's this thing do, anyway?
It lets Katherine reprogram the
parts in me she doesn't like.
Oh, no, that requires
much more equipment.
With all the cryptographic data
you've absorbed over your life,
it's not a question
of having the answer.
We know it's in there.
There's just
too much other noise.
With auditory stimuli that
can boost neurological activity,
we can elicit your
frequency following response,
drown out that noise
and find it.
Ah.
It would be best
if we had a closed environment.
Ah, yeah.
Sure, I'll leave y'all to it.
(sighs)
Lie back. Relax.
Interconnecting our energies
will help you relax.
Listen to the beats,
to the sound of my voice.
Inhale slowly.
Good. And exhale.
Concentrate on your feet.
They're warm...
heavy.
Let that warmth flow up
through your body.
And as it does...
feel your body growing heavy
as well.
And as you feel your body
become heavier
and warmer,
feel yourself sinking
into the floor...
...being enveloped
by the warmth beneath...
...being delivered
to a new place...
where all of your knowledge
and experience reside.
(inhales)
(exhales)
(sighs)
(groans softly)
* *
(three echoing knocks)
MAN (echoing):
Who asks for admission here?
MAN 2:
A poor candidate
in a state of darkness.
What is the predominant wish
of your heart?
To see the light.
Zachary?
ZACH:
I solemnly promise
and swear that I will
never reveal the secret arts
and hidden mysteries belonging
to Free and Accepted Masons.
Should I knowingly violate
this oath,
I expect no less penalty than
to have my throat cut across,
my tongue torn out by its roots
-No.
-and my body buried
in the rough...
-No!
-(blood spatters)
(faint gasping)
Dad...
(exhales)
* *
MAL'AKH (voice-over):
The secret is how to die.
KATHERINE:
Tell me the words
as they come to you.
Solomon.
Amulet.
Ring.
Kings.
Wise.
Heart.
Hey.
How do you feel?
Fine.
You didn't make me do
anything embarrassing, like...
bark like a dog or...
rap?
Close.
"Lo, I have given thee
a wise and understanding heart."
I-I need to see a Bible.
(gasps) Careful.
(indistinct chatter)
(sighs)
MAN:
Oh, excuse me.
-Hmm?
-Would you mind watching
my stuff for a moment?
-I have to...
-Oh, yeah, no problem.
-Unless you're about to leave.
-No, it's fine.
Um, I'm gonna be here
for a while.
I was hoping you'd say that.
-Thank you.
-Sure.
Whoever altered the Bible text
replaced some of the words.
In First Kings, God gave Solomon
a wise and understanding heart,
making him
the legendary ruler of myth.
But here
that script was changed.
It no longer reads
"wise and understanding heart."
It just reads "wisdom."
So that's supposed to help you
unscramble the letters?
It's what's known
as a keyword cipher.
It works like this. Here.
You pull the letters of "wisdom"
out of the alphabet
and place them at the beginning.
The Hebrew transliteration
goes here,
and then you translate.
"I" becomes "B."
"T" becomes "U."
"P" is "R."
(mumbling)
"D."
KATHERINE:
"Buried... Ezra...
Dove."
Does that mean anything to you?
-No.
-Sounds like a '90s grunge band.
I know I haven't always been
the most supportive
of you and your work,
but this was good.
-It was...
-Science.
I mean, like you said,
I had the...
words all along...
Quit while you're ahead.
NUÑEZ:
So, big surprise,
not a grunge band.
Ezra Dove's a Freemason.
LANGDON:
Ezra Dove.
Died 1848.
Buried at Oaken Hill...
Cemetery.
So maybe the capstone's buried
with him?
(dogs barking in distance)
(sighs)
What's up, man? How you doing?
You having fun?
I'm sorry, what?
Maybe instead of...
hanging outside my house,
you should be out trying to find
the guy who shot up the Capitol?
Killed one of your guys, man.
Instead,
you're out here harassing me.
-I'm not harassing you.
-Yes, you are.
You're spying on me and my wife,
and I'm making you
uncomfortable.
I'm a cop, too. Yeah,
I fought for this country.
I'm a victim here. Look at me.
Check this out. Let me show you
something right here.
It came through here
and here, okay?
Now what that's called
is a through and through,
and I got cream from the doctor.
I can't get back there
sometimes. It's difficult.
Maybe you could help me
rub it on.
Maybe you
should go back inside, sir.
Let me ask you a question.
How do you go to the bathroom
in here, you know?
Um, CIA give you
a special bottle or something?
* *
BLAKE:
He's keeping his vow of silence.
TRISH:
He's Peter's good friend.
If he knew where to find him,
don't you think he'd tell us?
BLAKE:
No.
I think that his group has
different priorities.
You mean the Masons.
A group within the Masons.
Leviathan.
Self-appointed guardians
of the wisdom.
That is everything
that we know about them.
I saw this symbol
in the Capitol basement.
In the room Peter Solomon had
down there.
This is why you had
his phone tapped.
How long have you been looking
for this portal thing, exactly?
Not long enough, apparently.
Otherwise I'd have
more information than that.
That's why
you're gonna go in there
and you're gonna get more.
With your keen eye
for pressure points
and your mutual connections
to the Solomon offspring,
I suspect that you're gonna
crack him without much trouble.
So put aside regrets...
and do what you do best.
(loud, indistinct chatter)
-(horn honks)
-I can't believe this.
It's bullshit.
I don't understand
what you want from me.
I was here the entire time.
I didn't even know Ahmad
had left.
(laughs):
None of this is my fault.
From where I stand, I'm afraid
that's not entirely true.
When you go on a three-day
bender with a Saudi prince
and he drives his Ferrari
into a telephone pole,
high on coke you provided,
it doesn't really matter
where you were.
Certainly not to his family.
Where are you from?
The embassy?
I have an office there.
-I'm here to help, Zach.
-Good.
Then you can help me
get in touch with my dad.
He has a lawyer
who can fix this.
If he doesn't kill me first.
What if there was a way
for you to take care of this
without your father?
You know...
...help yourself.
How?
You made connections
that could be useful to us.
Just means going
where I tell you for a bit
and keeping a clean nose.
Do that,
and no one...
including your father, needs
to know anything about this.
It's kind of gotten to the point
where I-I can't work
anywhere else.
I guess I'm a bit superstitious.
So, you're a writer?
Guilty, yeah.
Would I know
anything you've written?
Well, if I told you my pen name,
you know, possibly.
But I barely know you, so...
I believe in superstition, too.
Oh, you believe in superstition?
Seriously,
there is a whole section
-in my dissertation
dedicated to...
-Dissertation?
-Oh, my God.
-In what field?
Um, it's called noetic science.
-Mm-hmm.
-I'm a research assistant,
and we are looking for proof
of parapsychological phenomena.
So that's
the mind-body connection,
the whole spiritual healing
gamut.
-Yeah.
-Are you serious?
The book I'm writing
is all about parapsychology.
-What?
-I swear to God.
You-you wouldn't happen
to know Katharine Solomon
by any chance, would you?
Um...
yes, actually-- she's my boss.
-She's your boss?
-Yep.
-Get out of town.
-(laughs)
I saw her earlier today,
in fact.
-You saw her today?
-(laughs): Yeah.
Where?
Oh, no, I... you know, I've just
read a lot of her work,
-doing research
for my latest book.
-Right.
She did this study
on indigo children.
It was really fascinating.
I assisted that study.
-No way.
-Mm-hmm.
Could I buy you
another cup of coffee?
-I mean, if you have time,
of course.
-Sure.
Uh...
how about a glass of wine
instead?
-I'd love that. Yeah, sure.
-Okay.
-MAL'AKH: Oh, my...
-Oh!
I cannot believe
I just did that.
I'm... I am so sorry.
Oh, it's nothing. I'll just...
I'm gonna go clean up quick.
-I'll be right back.
-Needless to say,
-the wine's on me.
-Okay. Deal.
KATHERINE:
We're gonna need to find a map.
This place is huge.
He could be buried anywhere.
MAN:
Excuse me.
Can I help you?
Yes. We're looking
for someone.
Someone... dead.
Obviously.
KATHERINE:
Our grandfather.
We drove all the way
from Marblehead to see him.
Right, Sean?
Yes. I, Sean,
and, uh, my wonderful...
Sister.
...sister and I
w-would love to pay our respects
to, um, Grandpa.
It's still hard for him
to talk about it.
Pain never leaves a person.
It's why we build monuments
to it.
If we didn't, you'd
be standing on a golf course.
(chuckles):
Right.
You'll find the directory
to the grounds
off the path to the left.
-Thank you. Thanks, Father.
-KATHERINE: Thanks.
There he is. But hold on.
-What?
-Uh, the code said "buried."
This says he's in section Y09,
which is the columbarium.
So he's not buried at all?
No.
* *
(footsteps continue)
What are you gonna do with that?
I'm gonna push that button.
Then you're gonna tell me
what I want to know.
Your boss doesn't like getting
his hands dirty?
So he leaves that to you?
Essentially, yeah.
But he and I don't always see
eye to eye.
(low, rapid beeping)
(beeping stops)
(clicking)
This is an A80
short-range EMP generator.
I just shorted out the cameras.
Pretty soon
they'll bring new ones,
but whatever happens before then
is completely between us.
Look, I don't care
about finding some portal.
I just want to find
your friend Peter Solomon.
CIA doesn't generally involve
itself in missing persons.
I have a personal interest.
His son Zachary was
one of our assets.
I know because I recruited him.
It was the first time I'd worked
with someone so young.
And lost.
I thought he could handle it.
When he was thrown into prison
for trafficking,
I was ordered to disavow
any knowledge of him.
To burn him.
So that's what I did.
So what?
You think finding Peter
will make everything all right?
No.
But it'd be a start.
We're running out of time.
Look, I don't know anything
about the man who took him.
You know what he's after.
If I understand that,
I can understand him,
and that might be the difference
between Peter living and dying.
Section Y.
LANGDON:
There he is.
-Make sure no one comes in.
-Whoa, whoa,
-what are you doing?
-(chuckles): Don't worry,
I got it.
Tight spaces are one thing;
heights I can handle.
KATHERINE:
Why would somebody hide
a capstone in an urn anyway?
Many cultures have superstitions
about desecrating human remains.
I don't believe in of them, of
course. But a strong deter...
(both gasp)
Nice catch.
Saved us.
And you want me to believe
you're not superstitious?
I was worried about the noise.
Well...
prove it.
We got a problem.
There's nothing in here but ash.
-(vehicle approaching)
-What?
That's not our only problem.
Someone knows we're here.
-Who?
-Doesn't matter. We have to go.
If someone's trying to stop us,
that means
we're on the right track.
The capstone
must be here somewhere.
-What are you doing?
-Buying time.
-(key clatters)
-Oh, my God.
-Apologies again. I'm...
-Oh, my God. It's all good.
-Thank you for the wine.
-Of course.
To the mind-body connection.
-Cheers.
(laughs softly)
Well, I have
a confession to make.
Hmm?
I knew exactly who you were
when I sat down.
(laughs):
I don't understand.
Your finger...
You should probably go now.
(distorted, echoing exhale)
(distorted, echoing voices)
(distorted jingling of keys)
(distorted, echoing breaths)
(echoing):
Easy.
* *
(panting)
There's got to be
something we're not seeing.
Okay, um, buried, not buried.
14 letters.
Wisdom. Kings. Heart.
He's almost here,
and you locked us in!
Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah.
Jonah.
Langdon.
Buried Dove.
(door rattling)
Langdon.
In Hebrew, Jonah means "dove."
Langdon!
Come on!
These reliefs tell the story
of Jonah and the Whale.
-Get down!
-And what's another word
for "whale"?
Leviathan.
-(Langdon coughing)
-Look.
(coughing):
There's something in here.
-Oh. Oh, my God.
-(Katherine strains)
Wait. Wait.
(Katherine gasps, coughs)
It's here.
-It's not the capstone.
-Just take it and keep going.
(both coughing)
(gasping breaths)
(coughing)
(panting):
Here.
No!
(thuds, creaks)
(Katherine strains,
coughs loudly)
How did Jonah get out again?
(panting):
God commanded it.
Well, now would be a good time.
(grunts loudly)
* *
(engine starts)
(tires squeal)
(insects trilling)
(dialing)
-(line ringing)
-(sighs)
Hey, hey, Lace.
What's up, man?
Yeah, I know.
I'm sorry. It's late.
Yeah, yeah, no, all good.
Yeah, I got out today.
So, listen, um...
you, uh,
you got anything on the shooter?
Yeah, yeah, I know, the CIA got
some "eyes only" bullshit,
but... we got him on camera,
right?
So run him through Clearview,
get me a name.
Yeah, tomorrow works fine.
Thanks, man. I owe you one.
(chuckles)
All right, man,
go back to watching bowling
or whatever.
(car engine starts)
All right.
(radio static)
WOMAN (over scanner):
...all units in vicinity,
Code 1, Adams Memorial.
Nonresponsive female,
yet to be identified.
Black and red SUV
found at scene.
-Huh.
-Maryland license
plate number...
(clicks off scanner)
Peter...
brought me
into the Leviathan Group.
He was the one who revealed
its purpose.
All Masons tell stories
about deeply held secrets.
Most of them are tall tales
to intrigue new members.
But this was different.
(voice-over):
I saw in these men
a belief...
in something beyond possibility.
A belief
that the ancient wisdom
was not only real,
but that it could
unlock consciousness,
allowing man to access
hidden reservoirs of power.
The group was formed
based on two questions:
Could humanity handle
such an evolution?
And what might happen
if this power fell
into the wrong hands?
(voice-over):
We made a pact
to safeguard the clues.
But the lure of the myth
was strong.
* *
There's a story
of a member of the group
from the beginning
of the last century
for whom the lure was too great.
He abandoned his oath.
He sought the wisdom
for himself.
And he found it.
It is said that he learned
to control things,
that he could bend
matter to his will.
* *
(gasps) Oh, God.
(turns off projector)
(takes deep breath)
I did an EMP gambit
in Frankfurt in '09.
I didn't have one of these.
I'd use a garage door opener.
(soft chuckle)
SATO:
What do you want to do with him?
BLAKE:
Cut him loose.
Now that you've bonded,
you can use him as needed.
(Langdon sighs)
(phone buzzes)
(sighs)
Is it him?
It's a quote from the Apocrypha.
Fourth Book of the Maccabees.
(voice-over):
"For if you dispose me to anger
"by your disobedience...
"you will compel me,
with dreadful punishments...
"...to destroy
every one of you."
* *