[ominous music]
BASED ON THE KINGDOM OF THE GODS
BY YLAB
[ominous music rises]
[ominous music continues]
[snarls]
THE JAPANESE INVASION LEFT
THE SOUTHERN LANDS OF JOSEON IN RUINS.
AND NOW ANOTHER STORM WAS LOOMING
IN THE NORTHERN LANDS OF JOSEON.
THE JURCHENS ACROSS THE MANCHURIAN
PLAIN NORTH OF THE AMNOK RIVER
STARTED GATHERING AT THE BASIN
OF THE PAJEO RIVER
UNDER THE FLAG
OF THE VICIOUS, POWERFUL PAJEOWI.
WHEN 10,000 JURCHENS GATHER,
NO ARMY IN THE WORLD CAN DEFEAT THEM.
FEELING THREATENED
BY THE PAJEOWI'S SUSPICIOUS MOVE,
WARRIORS OF JOSEON SCOUTED
ANOTHER GROUP OF THE JURCHENS
IN ORDER TO KEEP THEM IN CHECK.
THEY WERE JURCHENS LIVING IN JOSEON
CALLED "SEONGJEOYAIN".
SINCE THEY HAD LIVED IN JOSEON
FOR OVER A CENTURY,
THEY WERE NEITHER CONSIDERED
JURCHENS
NOR ACCEPTED BY THE PEOPLE OF JOSEON
AS THEIR OWN
AND WERE SHUNNED BY ALL.
[foreboding music]
[footsteps]
[foreboding music continues]
[man chanting]
[chanting continues]
[distant animals screeching]
[ominous music]
[deer grunts]
[deer grumbles]
[footsteps]
[ominous music continues]
[rustling]
[eerie music]
[deer grunts]
[deer squeaks]
[leaves rustle]
-[thuds]
-[deer grunting]
[deer groaning]
[eerie music continues]
[deer snorts]
[serene music]
-[creature snarls]
-[deer squeaks]
[creature snarls]
-[rustling]
-[creature growls]
[deer snorts]
[creature snarls]
[deer shrieks]
[tiger snarls, growls]
-[tiger growling]
-[deer yells]
[deer yelping]
[tiger snarls, munching]
[eerie music]
THIS PLANT BRINGS THE DEAD BACK
TO LIFE… BUT YOU MUST PAY THE PRICE
[suspenseful music]
JURCHEN
JOSEON, HANYANG
PAJEOWI, BOUNDARY VILLAGE, PYESA-GUN
[clanking]
[clanking continues]
PYESA-GUN
[scout 1] What's that?
[both panting]
[ominous music]
-[men grunt]
-[horse neighs]
CITADEL OF MANPO
[men grunting]
Isn't he the deputy commander
of the Chupajin troops?
Please don't tell me
there's going to be another raid.
[male vendor 1] I suppose
the rumors you heard are true.
What rumors?
Well…
[sighs]
I heard the Jurchen people went
to Pyesa-gun to get wild ginseng
were all killed.
-What?
-[sniffs]
According to the army,
it's against the law to enter Pyesa-gun.
I cannot believe
such a horrible thing happened there.
I heard that
something scary lives in the woods.
I heard none of those wild ginseng hunters
came back out alive.
No one has been allowed to enter
for the past 100 years.
[male vendor 1] Who knows
if some vicious monster lives there?
[ominous music]
[man chanting]
[suspenseful music]
[soldier] They're all from the same clan.
They're Pajeowi Jurchens.
The word has already spread.
It's only a matter of time
before the Pajeowi find out.
What do we do?
Let's go to the boundary village.
-[thuds]
-[Tahab grunts]
[Tahab sighs, grumbles]
-[Tahab exhales]
-[scraping]
[background chatter]
[grunts]
[knife scraping continues]
Don't look at that.
Animal bloods and innards are
for the lowborn.
[Tahab grunts]
[kids cheering]
[Tahab] There it is. All set.
-[grunts]
-[spits]
Remove your filthy hands.
[kids laughing]
[woman grunts]
[kids chattering]
[woman] Let's go.
[kids yelling]
[dramatic music]
[Tahab grunts]
[kids chattering]
Hey!
Let's eat some meat!
[kids cheer]
BOUNDARY VILLAGE
A VILLAGE
WHERE THE JURCHENS IN JOSEON LIVE
[all laughing]
[all chattering and chuckling]
It's Ashin! Ashin!
[woman 1] Ashin, come join us.
-[woman 2] Do you want some more?
-[Tahab] Come on, Ashin.
[background chatter]
[thuds]
[sucks teeth]
Hey! How dare you? Give it.
Give it back to me.
-Hey!
-Oh, I'm sorry.
[sighs]
How many times have I told you
not to go to Pyesa-gun?
You told me that
it was actually dangerous.
You told me yourself that
people spread the rumors
so they could take all the wild ginseng
for themselves.
That's why I told you not to go.
What's more dangerous than a monster?
Are soldiers.
Then what do we do?
Are we just gonna let Mom die?
Just like that?
[dramatic music]
[breathing shakily]
They say the wild ginseng there,
it can even bring back the dead.
-Why not Mom?
-You are not a ginseng hunter.
How will you find the wild ginseng
in that huge mountain?
I'm not sure if it was wild ginseng,
but I saw a strange plant.
It was drawn on a mural that said
that it can bring back the dead.
That's just nonsense.
In those parts, there are no shrines left.
-But I saw it, it was right--
-Stop talking nonsense.
Listen to me and do not go there.
Anybody who sneaked in there
and got caught,
they were punished,
had their tongues cut out.
I can never let that happen to you.
Do you understand?
[distant horse neigh]
[horses whinny]
[horses neigh]
[horse snorts]
I had planned to travel to Chupajin
to offer these gifts to you, my lord.
Fifteen Pajeowi Jurchens
who went into Pyesa-gun
crossing the river to hunt wild ginseng
were all found dead.
They are the Pajeowi Jurchens?
Are you sure, my lord?
But who… who would do something like that?
It was a tiger.
[suspenseful music]
[Chi-rok]
You will have to cross the river.
Go spread the word that
all the Pajeowi Jurchens…
were killed by a tiger.
[suspenseful music continues]
Understood, my lord.
[Tahab] When will my village
receive a government position?
An official one?
We are very aware of your loyalty.
Don't rush.
You must be patient and wait for it.
Good news will come soon.
[door opens]
[Chi-rok] Hurry up. Get ready.
[sighs deeply]
[door closes]
JOSEON MILITARY CAMP, CHUPAJIN
[soldier] Our boys are here.
[horse snorts, neighs]
Sir, we have brought all the corpses
found in Pyesa-gun
as you commanded us.
[horse whinnies]
[foreboding music]
[soldier] We've verified that
the limbs were torn by wild animals,
but it happened after they died.
It wasn't the tiger.
They were killed by humans.
I am aware of it.
If 10,000 Jurchens come together…
a great danger will befall us.
[Jurchens grunting]
[Jurchen 1] Hyah!
-[horses neigh]
-[all clamoring]
[grunts]
[Jurchen 2] Hold out a hand
and you shall receive help.
Pull out the knife and you shall be slain.
[grunts]
[Jurchens grumbling]
[eagle calling]
[Chi-rok] While Joseon was floundering
in chaos during the Japanese invasion,
Aidagan, the head of the Pajeowi,
has gathered the Jurchens under his wing.
The Japanese in the south are
preparing to attack.
If the Pajeowi in the north uses this
as an excuse to invade us as well,
what will happen to this country?
We can never let them know
those men were killed by our own people.
They weren't attacked by people.
They were attacked by a tiger.
[gayageum music playing]
[guard] The deputy commander
from Chupajin is here.
[Beom-il] Let him in.
[gayageum music continues playing]
[dancer chuckles]
Here you are, sir.
-[door closes]
-[gayageum music stops]
[Beom-il sighs]
[Beom-il gulping, exhales]
So what brings you here at this hour?
[door closes]
The bodies of 15 dead Pajeowi Jurchens
were found in the pit.
Are you certain there were 15 of them?
Why?
Are you saying that
I got the number wrong?
[Chi-rok] I heard you went hunting
in the Birch Pass two days ago.
[Beom-il scoffs]
So tell me…
since when do I need your permission
to go hunting?
Every single Pajeowi Jurchen receives
martial arts training from an early age.
With that straight in training,
it would be nearly impossible
to take down 15 of them at once.
Unless it was you
and your elite guards who did it.
[dramatic music]
[dramatic music rises]
You'd better discipline your men
before someone else finds out.
[bangs on table]
Those Jurchen rats…
they dared to steal
the Haewon Cho Clan's wild ginseng.
They all deserved to die.
You should have captured them
and punished them according to the law.
That wild ginseng, does not belong
to the Haewon Cho Clan.
It belongs to His Majesty,
the King of this country.
-[sword clinks]
-[rattling]
Do you think you can insult me
and my family like this
just because I'm stuck…
here in the boondocks?
You abandoned your people
and fled during the war.
That is why you're here.
If you commit a crime
and endanger this country once again,
you won't be able to avoid
the consequences.
Even if you are from the Haewon Cho Clan.
The people are growing anxious,
so I will begin a tiger hunt
to calm their anxiety.
You would do well to stay where you are
and keep out of trouble.
[scoffs]
I'm telling you, this is a warning.
[exhales]
[soldiers grunting]
-[grunting continues]
-[flame crackles]
[soldiers panting]
[ominous music]
[ominous music continues]
AMNOK RIVER, BORDER AREA
BOUNDARY VILLAGE
[Ashin] Are you sure it was a tiger?
The Pajeowi learned martial arts
as soon as they can walk.
They all got killed by one tiger?
[grunts, inhales]
-[soft sigh]
-[sighs sharply]
-[knife whooshes]
-[sighs]
If it turns out to be a lie,
no one will like it
when they find out the truth.
It might put you in danger, Father.
Being undercover…
is always going to be dangerous.
[inhales]
While I'm gone,
it's your job to look after the family.
[Tahab] All right, then.
[panting]
Father, let's go back to our clan
and cross the river.
You let them take all your pelts
and risk your life
to go undercover for them.
Are you gonna let them walk
all over you forever?
Pyesa-gun is where
our ancestors used to lived.
[inhales]
The King of Joseon bestowed the land
upon our clan,
we were battling hunger and thieves
on the barren fields
on the other side of the river.
The King offered us a public office
and exempted us from paying taxes.
Joseon…
he was very gracious to us.
Hence, I cannot betray Joseon.
Do you understand?
They may have been gracious
to our ancestors,
but they've taken back everything
they gave us.
Hang in there just a little longer.
Soon, I will officially be appointed,
and we will live a good life.
[dramatic music]
-[sloshing]
-[Tahab grunts]
[grunting continues]
[water sloshes]
[indistinct chatter]
[pants]
[background chatter]
Good.
[woman sighs]
[exhales deeply]
I think it's time we call for a doctor.
No doctor would come here.
There's no point.
[woman] Then what do we do?
Stay with Mom until I come back.
[boy] Ashin! Please hurry!
JURCHEN VILLAGE, NORTH OF AMNOK RIVER
[Tahab] Far past the Amnok River
is Mount Baekdu,
Joseon's highest mountain.
It's so huge that you'll find
all kinds of trees and animals.
The most famous beast
among the animals is…
-the tiger.
-[crowd] Ooh…
[all laugh]
They say that
this tiger is 1,000 years old.
Sometimes,
it even transforms into a human like us.
[crowd derides]
No, for real!
Thousands of men have gone
into the mountains
and met their death
trying to catch the tiger.
-[indistinct chatter]
-[mocking laughter]
Look, haven't you heard
of the Pajeowi Jurchens
who climbed the Birch Pass recently?
They all got eaten by that tiger.
[crowd derides]
-[Jurchen 1] Is that true?
-[Jurchen 2] No way.
It is.
I saw it with my own eyes.
[sheepish laugh]
Really?
[cackles]
If you're lying to us…
you will die.
[sneers]
[cackles]
[panting]
PYESA-GUN
[ominous music]
[Ashin breathing heavily]
[ominous music continues]
[rustles]
[suspenseful music]
[suspenseful music continues]
THIS PLANT BRINGS THE DEAD
BACK TO LIFE…
BUT YOU MUST PAY THE PRICE
-[clanking]
-[all clamoring]
[Chi-rok] Our hunt will take place
in the Birch Pass.
We will begin in these two areas.
The Chupajin soldiers will spread out,
guard the trails and go after them.
We'll lure them out…
to here.
[soldier] You want to lure them out
to Pyesa-gun.
Do not forget.
We will only pretend to hunt them.
[all clamoring]
[leader] Quiet now!
All right, when hunting a tiger,
you shouldn't go too slow or too fast.
If we are too fast,
we might get attack by the tiger.
-All right. Let's go!
-[hunters] Let's go!
[leader] Let's go! Come on.
-[indistinct chatter]
-[leader] Come on!
-[indistinct shouting]
-[gongs clanging]
[soldier 1] That's a tiger's paw print
right there.
This is very odd.
Tigers hate the sound of gongs,
so it should be avoiding it,
but it's not running away.
What do you mean by that?
[soldier 1] That it's coming toward us.
-[eerie music]
-[distant tiger growls]
[growling continues]
-[indistinct shouting]
-[gongs clanging]
-[growls]
-[all fall silent]
[all breathing heavily]
-[rustles]
-[all gasp]
-[tiger roars]
-[all exclaim]
[all clamoring]
-[tiger snarls]
-[hunter screams]
[clamoring continues]
-[hunter 3] Shit.
-[tiger growls]
[tense music]
-[hunters panting]
-[tiger snarls]
[shrieks]
[yelling]
[screaming]
[yelps]
[intense music]
[suspenseful music]
It's a tiger.
[leader 1] No, it's not a tiger.
It's a monster.
[grunts]
Tell the hunters to fall back.
We will take it from here.
[blares]
[leader 2] Retreat!
Retreat! Go!
-[all clamoring]
-[leader 2] Come on!
[tense music]
[all panting]
[heaving]
[tense music continues]
[breathing heavily]
[ominous music]
[rustling]
[all heaving]
[rustles]
It's the Pajeowi. Stop them!
[tense music]
[tiger growls]
[tiger snarls]
[grunts]
-[soldier 1 screams, groans]
-[tiger roars]
-[soldier 2 shrieks]
-[tiger snarls]
-[tiger growls]
-[grunting]
[soldier 2 grumbling]
[tiger snarls]
-[soldier 2 groans]
-[tiger growls]
[tiger snorts]
[tiger roars]
[soldier 3 yelps]
[both grunt]
[both grumble]
[soldier 1] Sir! What's that?
[tiger growls]
[tiger snorts]
[tiger grunts]
[tiger hisses]
[tiger roars]
[soldier 4 screams]
-[grunting]
-[tiger snarls]
[soldier 4 yelps]
[soldier 4 screams]
[soldier 4 grunts]
[soldier 4 breathing heavily]
[soldier 4 panting]
[exhales]
[soldier 4 grunts]
[soldier] How bizarre.
How is that possible?
It was already dead.
[man panting]
[soldier 4] Here's what's really bizarre.
We were told that
our brothers were killed by a tiger.
Then where are their flesh and bones?
They are the one who crossed the borders
and entered Pyesa-gun,
which is against the law.
There is no reason for us
to be held responsible for their deaths.
Our brothers died on Joseon soil.
Prepare yourselves for a bloody revenge.
[ominous music]
-[rustling]
-[distant crow squawking]
[panting]
[ominous music continues]
[heavy breathing]
[suspenseful music]
[wind howling]
[boy] Ashin?
[creaks]
[foreboding music]
[fire whooshes]
[Ashin panting]
[all] Fire! Fire!
[all clamoring]
[all grunting]
[tense music]
[whooshes]
[clamoring continues]
[sighs]
[tense music continues]
[panting]
[suspenseful music]
[Ashin breathing heavily]
[panting]
[sobbing]
[crying]
[crying continues]
[somber music]
[somber music continues]
[footsteps]
JOSEON MILITARY CAMP, CHUPAJIN
[Chi-rok] I heard about
the tragic massacre at your village.
Are you the only one who survived?
What happened to your father, Tahab?
I've heard that…
[breathing shakily]
the Pajeowi have executed a spy
from Joseon.
Did you cross the river
and go all the way there?
I don't understand what happened.
[shaky breath]
Why would the Pajeowi do this to us?
I have been racking my brain
but I don't get it.
Have you come to see me
to find out why it happened?
No, sir.
[sobbing]
That doesn't matter to me at all.
I beg you. Avenge my father.
A lowborn weakling like me cannot do it.
But Joseon can.
You have the power to punish them.
I'm sorry for your loss,
but this is not a matter for Joseon
to intervene in.
My father…
was loyal to Joseon all his life.
Although you never did the right thing
and gave him an official post…
you could at least do this for him now.
[Ashin] It, it doesn't have to be
right away.
Next year or the following year…
or even a decade from now.
Please make them all shed tears of blood.
Then I will make peace with it.
I will do anything.
I will be your loyal spy if you want,
or even work as a butcher
if you tell me to.
Even if it's something nastier,
I will gladly do anything.
[shaky breath]
Please avenge… the death of my father.
Let's take care of this child.
[indistinct chatter]
[man] Is she here?
[background chatter]
This is where you will stay.
[pigs snorting]
-[snorting continues]
-[door closes]
[somber music]
[pig snorts]
[wind gusts]
[bangs]
[pig shrieks]
[Ashin pants]
[breathes heavily]
[dramatic music]
[Ashin sighs]
[Ashin groans]
[exhales]
[dramatic music continues]
[pigs snorting]
[rustling]
[indistinct chatter]
-[wind gusting]
-[sloshing]
[pants]
[mellow music]
[Ashin sighs]
[exhales]
[soldier sighs]
She's a survivor
from the boundary village.
That tenacious little wench.
I heard that
she buried all the bodies herself.
[soldier groans]
[mellow music continues]
[grunts, pants]
[background chatter]
PAJEOWI MILITARY CAMP
[dramatic music]
[leaves rustle]
[Ashin panting]
[tense music]
-[deer yelps]
-[rustles]
[boar squeals]
-[gasps]
-[boar wails]
-[panting]
-[boar snorts]
[Ashin panting]
[boar squeals]
[suspenseful music]
Hey. I know, right?
[both chuckle]
[pig snorts]
[whispers]
Ashin.
[sighs]
-[knife clinks]
-[gasps]
[shaky breath]
[whispers]
Now get out.
[breathing shakily]
Do you think…
[sighs]
you can survive in this camp…
[breathes heavily]
after killing a Joseon soldier?
[soldier gasps]
[soldier sighs]
You've gotten too big to fit in here.
[soldier scoffs]
[soldier pants]
-[dramatic music]
-[pig snorts]
[dramatic music continues]
[dramatic music rises]
[soldier] Good job.
[door closes]
MESSENGER
[messenger] I come with news!
The peace conference with the Japanese
was called off?
Yes.
His Majesty has ordered every troop
to assemble in the southern region
except those in Uiju and Kanggye.
We will leave a few soldiers behind
and prepare for battle.
Yes, sir.
And keep a close watch
on the Pajeowi's every move.
[soldier] Yes, sir.
[pig snorts]
[soldier gasps]
Sir.
What atrocity is this?
Please forgive me.
If something like this
were to happen again,
I will not let it go unpunished.
Yes. Yes, sir.
[soldier pants]
I need you to cross the river again.
You need to find out in detail
what the Pajeowi are up to.
[foreboding music]
-[horses neigh]
-[soldiers grunt]
PAJEOWI MAIN MILITARY BASE
[grunting continues]
[suspenseful music]
[pants]
[eerie music]
-[metal clanks]
-[man grunts]
-[clanking]
-[both groan]
-[soldier] Open your mouth.
-[man chokes]
Open!
[man gags]
[soldier] Take it, traitor.
[man pants]
-[metal clinks]
-[thuds]
[man groans]
[door opens]
[door closes]
[metal clanks]
[man grunts]
[ominous music]
[shaky breath]
[Ashin sobs]
[sudden music sting]
[breathing shakily]
SPY WHO BETRAYED HIS OWN TRIBE
Dad…
[Ashin sobs]
[cries]
[quavers]
Dad, it's me.
Dad…
[sobs]
It's me, Dad…
[Tahab sighs]
-[Ashin sobs]
-[clanking]
[crying, grunting]
[whimpers]
[sobs]
Dad, let's…
let's go home, come on.
It's okay.
Everything will be okay, so let's go home.
Let's go back together, Dad.
[Tahab] Kill me.
No more…
[crying]
Just kill me.
[whimpers]
[crying]
[Ashin sniffles, sobs]
[quavers]
Let's go back.
[somber music]
[Tahab] Please…
kill me now.
Ashin.
-[stabbing]
-[Tahab grunts]
[eerie music]
[eerie music continues]
[men distant yell]
[yelling continues]
[background chatter]
[ominous music]
[horses neigh]
[horses whinny]
[ominous music continues]
[horses neigh]
COMMANDER'S OFFICE, CHUPAJIN
[door slides open]
[door slides close]
What are you…
[soldier grunts]
[thuds]
[knife clinks]
[man] Some Pajeowi Jurchens sneaked
into Pyesa-gun to steal ginseng.
All of them were ambushed and killed.
A war with Pajeowi Jurchens
seemed imminent due to growing tensions,
but we wiped out a Seongjeoyain village
and managed to prevent such a disaster.
[soldier 4] Our brothers died
on Joseon soil.
Prepare yourselves for a bloody revenge.
[Chi-rok] Stop where you are.
If you silenced us by killing us,
our brothers will come after you.
And then you'll have a bigger price
to pay.
You are right about that.
Your brothers were not killed by a tiger.
They were attacked by someone.
In the place where
we found the bodies of your brothers…
-we found this.
-[rustles]
[eerie music]
[eerie music intensifies]
[thuds]
[Chi-rok] Have you come to see me
to find out why?
I beg you… avenge my father.
[tense music]
It is your job to look after the family.
[Ashin crying]
[tense music intensifies]
[pig snorts]
[soldier sighs]
[soldier whispers]
Ashin.
What is this flower?
-[gasps]
-[knife clinks]
[soldier grunts]
[body thuds]
[ominous music]
[suspenseful music]
[man pants]
[foreboding music]
[man snarls, groans]
[soldier 1] What is that?
[soldier 2] No idea.
[tense music]
[snarls]
[growls]
[soldier 1 grunts]
[soldier 1 yelps]
[man snarls]
-[growls]
-[soldier 2 whimpers]
[soldier 2 screams]
[shrieks]
[man snarls]
[soldier 2] Go away! Get off of me!
Go away!
[soldier 2 grunts]
[soldier 2 screams]
-[soldier 2] Help! Help me!
-What's happening? Quick, help him!
-[soldier 2 grunts]
-[man snarls]
[soldier 2 shrieks]
[soldiers grunt]
[soldier 2 yelps]
[soldier 3 grumbles]
[snarls]
[soldiers scream]
-[soldiers shout]
-[thuds]
[all grunting]
[soldier 2 panting]
[man snarls]
[tense music]
[soldier 2 screams]
[grunts]
[soldier 2 shrieks]
Gosh, it's so cold.
[sighs]
[exhales]
[shivers]
It's so cold.
[taps on floor]
[chilling music]
[gasps, screams]
Is he dead? Oh.
[soldier gasps]
[snarls]
-[nervous gasp]
-[man snarls]
[growls]
[soldier screams]
[shouts]
[man snarls]
[soldier indistinct]
[soldier shrieks]
[foreboding music]
[man snarls]
[growls]
[yells]
[grunts]
[man snarls]
[flame crackling]
[panting]
-[gasps]
-[man snarls]
[distant yelling]
[soldier grumbles]
-[whimpers]
-[snarling]
[screaming]
[tense music]
-[all clamoring]
-[pigs snorting]
-[monsters snarling]
-[soldier] Run faster!
-[soldiers groaning]
-[monster growling]
[screaming]
-[shrieks]
-[thuds]
[grunts]
[grumbles]
[monster snarling]
[tense music]
-[arrow whooshes]
-[soldier yelps]
[suspenseful music]
-[twang]
-[thuds]
[suspenseful music continues]
[soldiers clamoring]
[fire explodes]
[monsters snarl]
[soldier gasps]
[soldier yelps]
-[soldiers grunting]
-[monsters snarling]
[screams]
[soldiers grumble]
[all grunt]
-[thuds]
-[pants]
[soldier 1] Is he dead?
-[arrow whooshes]
-[soldier 2 grunts]
What?
-[arrow whooshes]
-[body thuds]
[yelps]
-[soldiers scream]
-[monsters snarl]
[soldier 2 whimpers]
[grumbles]
-[monster snarls]
-[soldier 2 screams]
[grunts]
[arrow whooshes]
-[monster snarls]
-[soldier 2 screams]
-[arrow whooshes]
-[yelps]
-No!
-[monsters snarl]
[arrow whooshes]
-[soldier screams]
-[monster snarls]
[monsters growling]
[soldliers clamoring]
[grunts]
-[monster snarls]
-[shrieks]
[tense music]
[foreboding music]
[monsters snarling]
[soldier grunts]
Ashin. Ashin.
[groans, panting]
Hey, Ashin. Help me out, please.
[groans]
[pants]
[grunts]
[soldier] No. Oh, no, Ashin. No, no, no.
Ashin! What are you doing?
-No, no, please! Don't, don't kill me!
-[arrow whooshes]
[shrieks]
-[shrieking continues]
-[monsters snarl]
[soldier shouts]
[monsters snarl]
[soldier grunting]
[screams]
[epic music]
[monster snarls]
[fire crackling]
[soldier shrieks]
-[arrow whooshes]
-[fire explodes]
[soldier screaming]
[epic music continues]
[crow caws]
[light music]
[man grunts]
[grunting continues]
[groaning, sighs]
[panting]
Ashin.
Don't kill me.
[heaving]
I'm sorry for everything.
Please spare me, huh?
[sighs]
[coughing]
[grunts]
[breathing heavily]
[dramatic music]
[dramatic music rises]
[girl] Ashin, you're back!
Yes.
I've come back home.
[dramatic music continues]
[inaudible]
[sighs]
[somber music]
[children chuckle]
[all laughing]
You didn't eat anything again.
I told you that you have to eat.
[monsters snarl]
[chain clanking]
[snarling continues]
I don't think I've taken
proper care of you all this time.
Pheasants, deer, rabbits…
that's not what you wanted, after all.
[monsters snarl]
From this moment on…
I'll provide you
with only delicious meals.
[soldier in muffled voice]
Ashin!
Ashin! Ashin!
[whimpers]
-[monsters snarl]
-[soldier yelps]
Ashin!
[screams]
[shrieks]
[soldier yelps]
[epic music]
[screaming]
[background chatter]
-[man 1] Nice.
-[man 2 laughs]
[woman] There you go.
[somber music]
[thrilling music]
[Ashin] I am not lonely.
We are together, so I am not lonely.
When my job here is done,
after I kill every living thing
on Joseon and Jurchen soil,
I will join you.
[foreboding music]
JOSEON BORDER, UIJU
[man 1] I heard
the Japanese hit the south again.
What if they come all the way up here?
I heard the envoys left to request help
from the Great Empire.
[man 2 grunts]
If they help us,
we won't be overrun like last time.
-[man 1] Mm.
-[man 2 grunts]
[man 3] The envoys are here!
The envoys are here!
[drum banging]
[eerie music]
Can this plant…
PHYSICIAN LEE SEUNG-HUI
…really bring back the dead?
Yes, that's correct.
[Ashin] Before the nervous system rots,
mash the plant and put it
on an acupuncture needle…
then pierce the needle
deep into the forehead.
And the corpse will come back to life
in two hours.
[snarls]
[suspenseful music]
-[distant men grunting]
-[horse whinning]
[horses neigh]
[grandiose music]
[tense music]
[arrow whooshes]
[ominous music]