OLIVER:
When I direct a new show,
the hardest part is getting
the actors to trust each other.
I'm doing a podcast.
A true crime podcast about a murder
in our own building.
‐ Are you associated with the deceased?
‐ You're probably just starting
your investigation,
looking into all the forensic‐‐
‐ Goddammit.
If I meet one more true crime nut...
‐ I am onto something great here.
‐ What was it? 32K?
‐ Now, it's 35.
‐ I tend to make packs wherever I go.
When I was a kid,
I had my Hardy Boys pack.
‐ Mabel is a sweet young woman who
promised not to keep secrets from us.
‐ Oh my God! There she is!
[gasps]
‐ It's Tie‐Dye Guy!
‐ I didn't murder Tim Kono.
‐ Tim was murdered?
Damn, he was right.
‐ Tim thought he was gonna get murdered?
‐ He'd been trying to take down this black
market jewelry dealer named Angel.
‐ Tim Kono was a loner
who worked in a bank.
Taking down a black market jewelry dealer
seems a little off‐brand, don't you think?
‐ Maybe... Then again,
I found all these in his apartment.
♪
DETECTIVE WILLIAMS:
We're all born alone.
Unless you're a twin or something,
but twins creep me the fuck out.
And don't even get me started on triplets
or quadrupla‐‐
Whatever the fuck they're called.
I don't know 'cause that's
not my point. My point is
we're born alone,
spend most of our time alone,
then we all go out alone.
When I was a kid,
there was this show on TV‐‐
Herman's Head.
You remember this shit?
Herman was this dude who had
these imaginary people
in his head, advising him.
‐ There's no such thing
as love at first sight!
WILLIAMS: One was the nervous one,
one was the romantic one...
I‐I can't remember all the details,
but I remember the fuck outta that show.
And I liked it 'cause
old Herman wasn't alone.
You know what I mean?
He had these people in his head.
[sitcom laughter]
♪
For a long time, I played it like Herman.
Just me and the people
advising me in my head.
And then I went and fucked
that up by listening
to that romantic fucker
in my head a little too much.
CHARLES [on podcast]:
Hey, podcast listeners.
Here at Only Murders in the Building,
when we get hungry...
[door opens]
WILLIAMS: Hey.
What you doing? We said
we're doing the nursery together.
‐ I waited. As long as I could.
CHARLES: Perhaps Evelyn the cat's
paw prints meant nothing.
But perhaps they were key to the entire...
‐ Do not subject our unborn child
to this true crime bullshit, please!
‐ This one is cute.
‐ Mm...
‐ I don't get a kiss hello?
‐ Oh, my bad. My bad. I got you.
CHARLES:
...can't actually see the color red...
‐ You think I won't smell
that cigarette on you?
‐ Don't start.
I had a dead kid today.
CHARLES:
I'm coming to you live from...
‐ A little girl.
Stepfather.
Abuse. All of that.
‐ Alright.
[podcast CONTINUES]
But this shit stops when Kareem comes.
‐ Who the fuck is Kareem?
Not my son.
‐ Kareem Abdul‐Jabbar?
‐ So?
‐ Is an athlete, a scholar,
an activist?
‐ And Kareem Hardison is Dwayne Wayne
on A Different World. I don't care.
‐ Kadeem.
‐ What?
‐ Kadeem Hardison.
‐ That's what I said. It's the same shit.
What are you talking about?
[Kiara laughs]
‐ You know, I was hoping you'd be
home in time to help me with this.
‐ Did you not just hear me
tell you about my day today?
[podcast continues]
‐ Just...
don't end up like Jerguson, Dee. Okay?
That's not who I married.
‐ Alright. Okay.
CHARLES: Howard Morris lives
at the Arconia in apartment 3D,
a place pungent with cat dander.
‐ The Arconia?
CHARLES:
But even stronger than the odor
was Howard's rage toward Tim Kono.
‐ What the fuck?
No, I‐I closed that case.
‐ Oh shit, that's you
they're talking about?
‐ What? W‐what the fuck are they saying?
‐ You know what?
Let's just turn it off.
‐ No, that was a suicide,
open and shut.
[podcast stops]
‐ Okay, but, um, sorry...
What about the paw prints?
[exaggerated gasp]
Because the cat
that came in after, and th‐they found it.
‐ You fuckin' for real?
So, what?
The cat did it?
[laughs]
No, for real. Let‐let's just‐‐
So, the cat did it?
Why are you listening to this shit?
‐ My Yard Dog Homies were
boosting it on Twitter.
I mean, these guys, they're...
they're dopey, but they
tell the story really well.
‐ Yeah, I don't... I don't tell stories.
And I don't make mistakes on my cases.
‐ Wait, where are you going?
‐ Where do you think?
‐ Dee, come on.
‐ You know...
you didn't have to hit me
with the work shit. Not today.
[door shuts]
♪
‐ We continued staring at the jewels
for what felt like a beat too long.
‐ I found them in Tim's apartment.
I went back alone after we left.
‐ You went back without us?
‐ Charles I get, but without me?
‐ I found him this one.
And this one.
These are all from Angel.
‐ Who is Angel?
‐ That's the only name I got.
Kono was obsessed with
buying pieces from Angel.
Sucks Tim died before he
got the one he really wanted.
‐ And which one was that?
‐ Uh, I got a pic somewhere.
He'd been trying to track it
down for years. I can dig it up.
‐ Yes, please,
and text it to me as soon as you find it.
‐ Me, too.
‐ Me, three!
‐ Just me.
‐ You know, I hooked Tim up
with my jewelry connection,
Cutter, to talk about
that piece he wanted.
‐ Oh my God!
The twists and turns of this
are just unbelievable.
It's like a‐a rainbow crafted
by a drunken leprechaun.
I can say that 'cause
I'm three‐quarters Irish,
and I have a teeny bit
of a drinking problem.
‐ Wait. Tim was supposed
to meet Cutter here today.
[door opens, bell rings]
‐ I'm gonna guess you're not Cutter.
‐ You come to Bayport,
I have to hear it from
Miss Skullcap over here?
You don't call me?
‐ Hey, Mom.
♪ lively theme song playing ♪
♪ vocalizing ♪
♪
‐ And that sad and lonely boy
raised by a psychologically abusive
mother was none other...
than Stephen Joshua Sondheim.
[Charles sighs]
And let me tell you something about Steve.
[Charles groans]
When he is on his game, it's a blessing.
And when's he's not, I'm patient.
‐ Mm.
[text chimes]
‐ Hey.
Tavo texted me that photo from Tim.
SILVIA:
Tim?
From the Arconia, Tim?
Why are you still in contact with
that boy after what he did to Oscar?
‐ I'm not, Mommy. He died.
‐ He was murdered.
‐ Murdered?
‐ In the building.
‐ Catchy, right?
‐ Ay, dios mio.
That place is no good for you.
I knew I shouldn't have
let you go back there.
‐ Let me? I'm grown, Mommy.
‐ We're investigating, and your daughter
has been a big help in this.
‐ What do you mean investigating?
CHARLES: I mean, we,
and your daughter, are producing a podcast
about Tim Kono's murder.
‐ I only let you go back there
because you promised me
you were focusing on your design career.
‐ Stop saying that you let me.
And a podcast is nothing.
‐ Well, tell that to our 17 subscribers.
‐ Wow. Seventeen, is that good?
‐ No.
‐ My daughter can't help herself.
She's trapped in the past.
But, you...
How old are you two? 80?
‐ I'll have you know that I am in
my very early mid‐60s.
‐ Dragging my little girl back into
the worst thing that ever happened to her?
‐ Look, I'm not a little girl!
My friend, our friend, Zoe died
at a New Year's Eve party
on the roof of the Arconia.
And we think Tim saw what really happened.
‐ But he never told anybody.
‐ Oscar got blamed and went away,
but he's out now, and I'm fine.
‐ Is fine not being able
to finish anything or focus
because your mind is trapped in the past?
‐ Please stop!
‐ Temores nocturnos fine?
[chair scrapes]
‐ Ahem.
♪
[shuffling papers]
‐ Wait, what? "Not submitted"?
Oh, I thought I sent you to IT.
[lighter clicks]
[clicks]
‐ How they hangin', Williams?
‐ Lower by the day, Jerguson.
‐ That's my guy. [soft laugh]
[puts down cup]
[sighs]
SILVIA: It's my fault.
I was always working.
So, when my rich sister
offered to take Mabel
for the school breaks, I thought...
qué maravilloso.
She'd go to the city,
see museums and plays...
be inspired to dream big.
[sighs] You try watching your only child,
so smart, so sure of herself...
turn into a ghost from grief.
Then see if you want to
make a podcast about it.
‐ We didn't know about that.
We didn't know about a lot... it seems.
But, your daughter is extraordinary.
[laughs]
She's funny,
intuitive...
‐ Weird.
[laughs]
But, in‐in‐in the best ways.
The way all your favorite
people are weird.
‐ Have you ever felt like
there was something you screwed up
so bad,
you'll never forgive yourself?
♪
‐ Well...
‐ For me,
it was letting her spend time
at that damn apartment.
Please leave her be.
Let her move forward, not back.
‐ Mommy.
‐ Thank you for dinner.
‐ Yeah, th‐thank you.
MABEL:
You know, she's probably right.
This whole thing was stupid anyways.
‐ It was many things,
but I'm not sure it was stupid.
‐ Why?
I'm a stranger that lied to you a bunch,
and you're two randos that
dragged me into a podcast.
‐ "Rando" is a slang for
a person of no significance.
‐ I used context clues, but thank you.
‐ You're welcome.
‐ You could still do the podcast though.
Can learn how to use Twitter.
It's not that hard.
Don't do TikTok.
‐ Mabel, it's been, uh...
it's been the most alive
I've felt in a decade.
‐ Me, too.
♪
[insects chirping]
‐ So, uh...
Goodbye.
[locks door]
[traffic noise]
‐ We got yelled at.
By a mom.
‐ I know.
I'm shook.
Mabel taught me that word.
‐ Mm.
Same.
‐ You know, it's a law of nature.
Nothing good ever happens on Long Island.
[Oliver sniffs]
Gut Milk is really good.
‐ Right?! I think it's giving me abs.
‐ 13% alcohol.
‐ Mm.
Cheers.
‐ Hey.
We had a good run,
but we can't possibly go on.
‐ Fully agree.
And why is that exactly?
‐ This is Mabel's life.
We can't exploit her pain,
playing detective.
Every true crime story
is actually true for someone.
‐ And this is just occurring to you?
‐ I guess it feels personal now.
‐ It already felt personal
to me 'cause of Winnie.
‐ Who's Winnie?
‐ Who‐‐ Are you kidding me?!
My dog! Winnie! Who's recovering
from being poisoned‐‐ The fact that
you forgot about her completely
is deeply concerning to me.
‐ Why? We barely know each other.
Mabel was right. We're all randos.
‐ Of course we know each other!
‐ Are my parents dead or alive?
‐ Dead.
‐ Lucky guess.
[text chimes]
Is that Mabel?
‐ No, it's Teddy. Our sponsor.
"Come to me.
We need to speak."
[sighs]
‐ All caps. Ominous.
‐ No, that's just the way he types.
But it still seems bad.
♪
Would you mind coming with me?
Or am I too rando?
[insects chirping]
[drops keys]
♪ soft music, indistinct singing ♪
‐ You know I barely dated my entire 20s?
Did you know that?
I was alone.
Then,
on a random Tuesday night,
I pull over this woman
who I caught texting while driving.
And then this broad had the audacity
to lie to my face
and say that she wasn't texting.
‐ I wasn't lying!
‐ You still lying to me in my face!
[both laugh]
But, I knew...
then...
I wasn't gonna be alone anymore.
And now, we got this kid coming‐‐
‐ Kareem.
‐ No. Over my dead body.
We're not doing it.
[laughs]
I just need to know that
I'm gonna be good at this.
‐ You will be.
‐ No, you don't know that.
‐ I do!
Just like I knew those podcast guys
were onto something.
You missed something, didn't you?
‐ The tox reports...
they weren't submitted.
And the victim's phone...
never made it to IT.
‐ Oh my God, yes!
So now, you swoop in there
and reopen the case
like a goddamn hero boss,
and just‐‐
‐ Baby, no.
When they don't submit something,
that means they want all hands off,
and I can't get up to sergeant by opening
a case that I already closed.
No. That's not how it works.
That's what we're not gonna do.
But what we will do...
is that we gonna go in here
and work on this nursery
for my man Keith.
‐ Keith?
‐ Oh yes. You know,
it's not quite... Kareem.
‐ Yeah, it's not‐‐
‐ But it's also not lame as fuck.
‐ I could dig it.
‐ Okay.
‐ Keith...
‐ Thank you.
[insects chirping outside]
[sighs]
[door shuts]
‐ Wow, I think I would've remembered this.
‐ Yeah. Well, during my depressing years,
my mom told me to read
about the Tree of Life.
Instead, I just made one.
‐ It's amazing.
Could never forget the SVU poster.
Weird‐ass crush you had on Stabler.
‐ The hottest criminal mind ever
is right here.
‐ Oh.
‐ And he kept it pretty tight.
I know it's nothing compared to
what you went through, but...
I had it pretty hard after
everything happened.
‐ Yeah.
Seems like we all did.
What's this? Huh?
‐ Oh. No, no.
‐ Mabel Sixth Grade?
‐ So embarrassing.
‐ Yes, please. Hold on.
‐ No! Don't want you to see it!
‐ Have a seat! Come on!
‐ I don't wanna look at‐‐
‐ We'll look at it together. Here.
[Mabel scoffs]
[Oscar laughs]
Whoa! Who is this cute little boy? Huh?
MABEL: Um, I was adorable.
I don't know what you're...
‐ What did you do to Silvia
for her to give you a bowl cut?
‐ And now, you've lost the right
to look at these. So, good job.
[Oscar sigh]
[turning pages]
[crinkling]
[sighs] Damn.
MABEL:
Holy shit.
Tavo's text.
♪
OSCAR:
What the hell?
‐ Why was Tim after the ring
that Zoe had on
the night she died?
‐ No.
She didn't have it on.
Not when she died.
[low sirens]
[quiet crowd chatter]
You don't forget the image of your
girlfriend's body on the ground.
‐ But it's right here.
So, does this mean
she lost the ring before she went over?
‐ Yo, can we stop now?
‐ Are you okay?
‐ Can we please spend, like,
two minutes talking about not death?
All I wanted to do today
was just... be with you.
I've thought about this moment a lot.
I've thought about you a lot.
‐ Me, too.
I think...
I've kind of been waiting for you.
Uh, sorry.
I‐I don't mean waiting for you
like I was waiting...
waiting for you.
I didn't save myself for‐‐
‐ No, no, yeah, yeah. Yeah. For sure.
‐ I did other things. I...
I worked. I went to parties.
I got bangs that were awful,
and I had to hide for a month.
‐ No, I‐I bet you looked hot.
‐ You'd lose that bet.
‐ Well, let's see for myself.
Were they like the lower‐‐
‐ Little longer and then
they did, like, a curl...
‐ Oh God. You're right.
[Mabel laughs]
‐ They're‐‐ It's horrible.
I can't unsee that.
♪
‐ Do‐do you ever feel like you've been
too inspirational, Cinda? You know,
like everyone has a podcast now.
‐ It has gotten a little out there.
Like, I guess the actor who played Brazzos
has his own podcast now?
JIMMY FALLON: What?
Wait, Charles, uh...
Haden Church?
No, I'm mixing him up.
CINDA CANNING:
Uh... He's Brazzos, and he's
investigating a real murder, uh,
in his Upper West Side building
with a theater director
and one of their granddaughters.
FALLON: Wow.
‐ And their prime suspect is Sting.
[audience laughter]
‐ No!
No!
CINDA: Yes! The title of their podcast
is Dimas Chicken Wraps Presents...
Colon. Only Murders In The Building.
[Fallon, audience laughing]
[banging table]
[Cinda laughing]
‐ Well, I do‐‐ I do love
a Dimas Chicken Wrap.
‐ Love 'em! Everybody loves
FALLON: My goodness.
[shuts off TV]
[Teddy sighs]
[puts down glass]
OLIVER: Teddy...
‐ Do you understand...
how huge Fallon is in Greece?
Do you know what
my cousins back on Nisyros
are gonna do when they see this?
They're gonna shit themselves, Ollie!
They're gonna squat right down
in their goat fields
and shit themselves in envy!
[laughs]
‐ Ha. That's... Wow.
‐ Yeah, that's... quite an image.
‐ You did it! You fucking homered!
Two episodes of your "podcast,"
and my name is in Fallon's mouth! Wow!
You've got more coming, right?
Please tell me
you've got more coming soon!
OLIVER: Of course.
Yes. Yes, of course.
‐ Actually, we've had a setback‐‐
‐ With lots of juicy twists and turns
and room for at least
four Dimas spots in every hour?
‐ At least. Sure.
‐ Oh...
I gotta tell you,
I feel like a proud papa.
My boys.
[sighs] Now...
I'm writing you a check...
and it's gonna be large.
But, I don't want a fight.
50,000 for the next three episodes.
CHARLES: Oh...
We can't accept that, Teddy.
‐ Don't say that.
‐ Oh please, don't say that.
‐ Well, uh, we lost one of our partners,
and it wouldn't be right.
‐ Come here. Come here, right now.
You see that?
That coin is my entire family legacy.
You know of the Greek
and Armenian Holocaust?
♪ somber music playing ♪
My grandmother.
My yiayia Evangelia
was a young woman when the Turks
started slaughtering all the Greeks,
forcing them to flee their home.
They didn't have banks back then,
so women would wear necklaces
with their family's life savings
in gold coins around their necks.
Desperate to flee,
my yiayia made a trade
with a Turkish soldier.
Her necklace for a spot on a boat
to take her to America.
The soldier let her keep two coins.
One to invest in a new future,
and one for luck.
Yiayia...
held tight to those coins...
through a sea
made red with blood
and the chopped‐off limbs
of her whole family.
Till she finally made it to Ellis Island.
♪
Still clutching those two coins.
She used one
to start a small sandwich shop,
and the other she held onto...
and passed it on to my father,
so he'd never forget the sacrifices
made to carry on
our proud Dimas name.
‐ And your father passed it to you.
‐ We, uh, didn't see eye‐to‐eye.
In fact, he vowed he'd take
the coin to his grave
rather than give it to me.
‐ Well, obviously he changed his mind.
‐ Or I dug the fucker up and ripped
it out of his cold dead hands.
[laughs]
[continues laughing]
‐ Oh... Oh...
[Oliver laughing nervously]
Oh, y‐‐ Oh...
‐ What... the fuck?
‐ Th‐that's so good.
Tha‐‐ You fooled me.
‐ My yiayia Evangelia taught me
to make investments in the people
who've been loyal to you,
even when there's risk.
I have a whole separate business
in her name where I do this work.
♪
So, please...
do me this honor.
[insects chirping]
SILVIA: So, is Oscar a good kisser?
‐ Mommy!
[Sylvia laughs]
‐ I saw the way he was looking at you.
The same way he looked at you
when you were teenagers.
I wish I could go back
in time to those days.
‐ And do what?
‐ I don't know.
Keep you there until...
‐ Till...
‐ Until I'm dead.
Then, you can go do whatever you wanted.
The old men are sad characters.
‐ I guess. Sort of.
‐ Mm.
‐ They're also the first friends
I've had in a really long time.
‐ But seriously, how old are they? Yeah.
‐ They're, like, really old.
I have to see this through.
I have to figure this out.
‐ I could never read you stories
when you were little.
I tried, but...
you always wanted
to skip right to the end.
[soft laugh]
You always needed to know what happened.
♪
[sighs]
[kiss] Baby...
CHARLES [on podcast]: If only we
had a window into Tim Kono's mind.
Some way to know more of
what he was doing in the days
leading up to his death. A laptop,
a calendar, any piece of physical
evidence that would bring us closer
to the truth.
♪
WILLIAMS:
I don't remember how Herman's Head ended,
but I suspect it ended with
him finally finding the girl.
Or the guy.
I could never tell with Herman.
And not needing those advisors
in his head anymore.
That's how I would've done it.
Herman doesn't need them
'cause he's not alone anymore.
But even if you're not alone,
it doesn't mean you don't
need help sometimes.
‐ We have 1,265 downlo‐‐
1,267!
Why do we have to get popular now?
‐ Apparently, people still watch live TV.
Where was this audience when
I directed Godspell Live on NBC?
‐ That was you?
‐ No, but it should've been.
See, I‐I'm not getting them.
I'm hitting refresh,
and nothing is working.
‐ You're in airplane mode. Again.
[click, beeping]
What?
‐ You knew my phone settings.
I'm not a rando.
‐ Alright, we need to deal with this mess.
Your dip man gave us $50,000.
‐ Right, and‐and...
we can't accept it because...
we agreed not to profit off
our young friend's tragedy.
‐ That's right, so we have
to take that check,
and we have to rip it up.
[growls]
[whimpers]
Now?
‐ Yes.
I think we have to rip it up, uh, now.
Wait, wait, wait!
‐ Wha‐‐ Thank God. What?
‐ What's this account?
It's not in Teddy's name.
‐ Well, he said he had
a separate business account for‐‐
‐ Look at the name.
‐ "Angel, Inc."
Oh no, no, no. Teddy is not the Angel
that Tim Kono was trying to bring down.
‐ I was wondering
when he said his yiayia's name.
Evangelia.
Angel.
[doors open, bang]
You don't knock?
‐ Hey.
‐ Women who knock rarely make history.
A peace offering. Silvia's tamales,
and I picked up some hummus.
‐ This hummus expired yesterday.
‐ But we both know you're gonna eat it.
‐ I know. It's true.
‐ Look...
I'm really sorry about lying to you guys.
‐ On multiple fronts. For weeks.
‐ An inordinate amount of lying.
It was borderline sociopathic.
‐ It's just...
very hard for me to trust people.
Honestly, it's pretty hard
for me to even like people.
But you guys...
Are you really gonna make me say it?
‐ I'd kinda like to hear the words, yes.
‐ Also rank us. I'm dying to
know who your favorite is.
‐ I want to do this podcast.
I have to finish this with you guys.
‐ That...
is so rando.
is not the right gesture.
‐ Give me those tamales.
‐ Wait.
My final peace offering.
Someone left this for
me at the front desk.
It's Tim Kono's phone.
CHARLES: What?
OLIVER: Whoa!
‐ But we need to find the password.
‐ Oy...
‐ Oh...
‐ Well, we got one for you.
♪
Here.
Say hello...
to Angel.
‐ Teddy Dimas?
Wait, so you're saying‐‐
‐ That's right. Our prime sponsor
is now our prime suspect.
‐ Ooh, that's good.
That'll make a great
last line for an episode.
♪
[fanfare]