Transcript by sub.Trader & Clarity
1991 DA NANG, VIETNAM
Hello, did you do all of this?
Beretta 93
Usually dependable.
We should be good to go now.
Come on.
Don't be afraid.
THIRTY YEARS LATER
BUCHAREST, ROMANIA
What the fuck? Are you having a party?
Where is Anton?
Why didn't he answer the phone?
Vali!
Your father is looking for you.
Get up!
Get up, Vali!
Come on, girls, come on. Go home.
Away, away!
Come on, get out of here.
Come on Vali, let's go.
Anton?
Where the fuck is Vali?
You had to look over him,
where the fuck is Vali?
Yes?
Who's talking?
It's me, Vali.
Vali?
Explain to me where did you go?
Why don't you--
Some assholes kidnapped me
outside the hotel.
What? Who?
Who kidnapped you?
How they fuck would I know?
They want three million euros now.
Vali, tell them how I am.
They don't fucking care
who you are, just pay!
They want three million euros
in two hours.
Or they'll cut my throat like a pig.
How dare you take my boy?
There it is. You wanna count it?
Do you know who I am?
Don Preda.
Butcher of Bucharest, Killer of Men.
Tell your boss it's done.
Exactly, who are you people?
We're just--
We just find people
who can't be found.
The money.
You gonna have it maybe for an hour.
Then we come take it back, cut you both
into pieces and feed you to my pigs.
That doesn't worry you?
No.
Why?
I didn't come here for money.
I came here for you.
Stop the girl. She killed
Don Preda. Kill her.
Why are you fighting so hard, huh?
You're going home, motherfucker.
Fuck off!
I'm good.
You fucking pieces of shit.
You can't leave me here!
Fuck you, you bastards!
Did you take any, huh?
Take what?
Money.
It was all there, right?
We were paid to eliminate
the target. We did that.
Yeah, you know, three mil…
dirty money… nobody's looking for…
Just saying.
Oh, I'm sorry,
I didn't know you're hurting.
Please.
This is R & D Plumbing.
Your leak has been fixed.
Please remit the balance
of your payment for the withd--
€7,000,000. Transfer complete.
Done.
You need to see a doctor about that cough.
Traditional or a witch?
You? Definitely a witch.
Ah, I know just the voodoo queen to call.
LONDON
Chelmsford was a bloody war zone.
Every train was 30 minutes late
and jam-packed as always.
Welcome back.
Thank you for taking care of her,
you know you're the only one
she'll tolerate, right?
She gets really mean when you're away.
Spent most of the time
hanging out with Proust.
Is that true?
Three weeks, and this
is all you come back with?
Ah, you know sellers,
they know you've come all that way,
and they play hard to get.
Didn't you wanna
just kill people like that?
What do you think you're doing, huh?
So, the other day, he says to me
"70 is the new 30."
Well, that's just something old guys say.
How is he doing with his protocol?
Is he following the doctor's orders?
More like, following his own orders.
Happy birth--
No more fucking birthdays.
Take birthdays and shove them up your ass.
Bastard.
What a wonderful toy!
You skimped on the candles I see.
Seventy would have been a fire hazard.
Could you make us some tea please?
Sure.
All right, make your wish.
Happy birthday.
Yeah.
To thank you.
A 1958 Gibson Flying V.
This was in production just two years.
There is only 90 in the whole world.
I know.
That sound…
It's the wood.
African limba.
Nothing else sounds like it.
I was just about giving up hope
on finding one.
How in the world did you…
You.
You taught me how to find things
that didn't wanna be found.
Albert King played one.
Albert King played that one.
No!
You're gonna cry now, aren't you?
Only because I can't play it the way
it needs to be played.
Thank you.
One of the twins called me
last night, said she was pregnant.
Daisy in Dover?
No, Daisy in Manchester.
Daisy in Dover is a dyke.
It is a rare gift to have a friend
who trusts you enough
not to try and help until you ask.
If you fell in the pond
with those you'd drown.
Well, if I fell in a pond without them
I would probably float away.
-Hi, honey.
-Mind your fingers.
That hefa bites.
She's a baby and doesn't know any better.
There.
You have your own secret hideout.
Why am I not surprised?
I bought the building.
-What?
-The bookstore.
It's yours. Free and clear.
You didn't have to do that.
I know, but it's your passion.
And, it makes me feel good to know
you'll have something
to work on while I'm gone.
What is that?
Those are the souls
waiting for me on the other side.
I'm sure they have a reception planned.
Ah… sent away so many prematurely.
Either by my hand or through you.
We never sent anyone away
who didn't have it coming.
Maybe.
But… I'm sure there are
quite a few spirits up there
waiting for me with a bone to pick.
You really believe you're going up?
Don't you?
Lucas Hayes.
I need our friend to find him for me.
I have him up till 1998, Paris,
after that nothing.
-Just find?
-Just find.
Discreetly, and with the quickness.
Okay.
I may have to go back to Vietnam.
It'd be nice if you went with me.
I'm never going back there.
Our past is never
where we left it, little chameleon.
We all have scars.
You stare at them long enough
you remember how you got them.
-Hi.
-Morning.
The blue dress has a small tear in it,
I was hoping to talk to Benny about it.
What do you think?
Of what?
My, mustache.
Oh, you know, I don't have
my contacts in, sorry.
Funny.
You wait till this grows in
women like you are gonna be so…
No, it's okay. I'll help you out.
I need you to find this guy.
What? No satellite shots of a
mafia compound outside Bucharest?
No, but that was
some of your better work.
Moody wants this guy, Lucas Hayes,
last seen in Paris in '98 and then nothing.
Yeah.
I'll be with you in a second.
Can I help you?
Yeah, I'm looking for a book,
an old book. Like, rare.
-"Like rare"?
-Yeah.
Either they are or they aren't.
Books aren't like stake,
you can't get them like medium rare.
-It's funny.
-Sarcastic.
Yes, but funny.
Listen, my boss' wife is having a party
and she collects books, first editions.
Any particular subject?
Birds. It's Audobon's…
"Birds of America"?
Yeah, that's it.
He said she's looking for a copy.
-A first edition?
-Yeah.
-Sorry.
-You don't have it?
No one does,
only one first editions exists,
it was sold to a private buyer
in 1991 for a 9.6 million dollars.
Wow, okay.
Well, looks like I'm out of luck.
All right. What do you think?
Maybe poetry?
Hang on…
It'll be the hit of the party.
TAMERLANE AND OTHER POEMS
I don't-- I don't know this one.
It's Edgar Allan Poe actually.
His first collection of poems
published anonymously.
You think she might have it?
Doubtful. Only 50 copies were printed.
Only 12 are known to exist.
How much?
I can give it to you for $265,000.
Perhaps a bracelet instead?
She does have exquisite wrists, good idea.
Is there something else?
I find you interesting.
-You mean--
-You're interesting.
Beautiful, sure, not in that
ornamental kind of way.
It's the interesting part
that got me wondering,
Wondering what?
How long after I give you
my number will it take you
to decide that I'm just
as interesting and give me a call?
Twenty seven minutes.
That long?
First I have to pretend to cancel my date
and then I have to feed my cat.
That's six.
The rest is me playing hard to get.
Cute.
How many of these are you
carrying around, Mr…
Rembrandt. Michael Rembrandt.
Actually, I haven't had an occasion
to use one until just now.
So…
Interesting.
"There rose a fountain once, and there
full many a fair flower raised its head."
That was from the book, wasn't it.
"But she who rear'd them was long dead,
And in such follies had no part."
You almost got me on this one.
You didn't say I'd be tracking
an eight year old.
Lucas Hayes did arrive in Paris in '98,
but returned to Da Nang, March '99.
Everything else I have is on there.
B. B. KING
LIVE AT THE VILLAGE GATE
READY TO GO
Benny?
You'll stay up
until I get there, 45 minutes.
Lucas Hayes, born April 5, 1990.
Father: Edward Hayes.
Mother: Mary Christian.
St. Quiteria Hospital
Lucas Hayes, admitted
to St Quiteria Hospital on June 2nd, 1999.
Father: Edward Hayes, assassinated
at Christmas Day, 1991. No other records.
Edward Arthur Hayes
Businessman indicted for war crimes
dies in car bomb attack.
Edward Hayes… was killed
in a car explosion in Da Nang yesterday.
Moody.
"Company will continue," vows CEO
"Edward Hayes
was my partner for 25 years.
I will continue to steer our company
as he would have wanted me to."
Jossino Vohl
DA NANG, VIETNAM
Shit! What the fuck is that?
Fuck.
Honey! Come on.
Never thought I'd see you here again.
Well, maybe you're not seeing me now.
Who's the bitch?
Billy Boy…
I know you run with all kinds
but now you're running with stupid?
Fuck you!
Hey! Go get a drink, sugar,
and give the adults some privacy, huh?
Beers!
Is that your ride outside?
Yours now.
It ain't my birthday.
Jossino Vohl.
How's Moody?
He's dead.
For Moody.
Vohl involved?
I don't know. But he knows who is.
-He's gonna be hard to kill.
-I just wanna talk to him.
Steverino!
Yeah, Boss?
You work security at the State Tower.
My friend there needs
a few minutes with Vohl.
Alone.
Yeah, that's not gonna happen.
He goes nowhere without private security.
The guy's never alone.
What is happening?
This is how easy it is
for me to get to you, Mr. Vohl.
Do you understand?
You were friends and business
partners with Edward Hayes,
so you would know most
about his short but interesting life.
Good, cause I have questions.
You give me answers:
if I'm satisfied you'll never see me again,
if I'm not, I'll be
the last thing you'll ever see.
I look forward to hearing from you.
Good evening, Miss.
It's been a long time since such
a beautiful young woman gave me her number.
You know who I am.
Jossino Vohl, born in April, 1945.
French national,
residing full time in Vietnam.
Was in business with Edward Hayes
until his untimely death.
Now you're a top political power broker
with some interesting side hobbies.
I see you're familiar with my resume.
I am not interested
in your business activities, Mr. Vohl.
I want to talk
about your friend's son, Lucas.
My office, one hour.
We'll be alone?
My lawyer will be present.
That would be the man
standing behind you pouring a scotch?
Delighted, Miss.
Exactly on time.
Please.
Monsieur Duquet,
my personal attorney.
-Would you like some champagne?
-Edward Arthur Hayes.
Eddie and I were involved
in a bauxite mining project together
until his accident.
It wasn't an accident,
it was an assassination.
We were useful.
The country was malleable,
ripe for certain business practices.
Eddie was juggling
a lot of delicate plates.
What's your interest in a man
who's been dead almost thirty years?
I'm interested in his son.
Lucas Hayes.
I'm sorry?
Three people are dead
because they inquired about him.
He had them killed
and I'm going to find him.
Should I be talking to him?
I have no connection with Lucas Hayes.
And what does any of this
got to do with me?
I was wondering the same thing.
Mr. Vohl's past relationships
are no one's concern.
And certainly none of yours.
Oh, I've made them my concern.
Too bad.
I need to know everything.
Who are you?
Who hired you?
Why the interest in Lucas Hayes?
We can do this another way if you'd like.
Fucking let me go!
Get up there.
Hand me a gun.
SPRINKLER VALVE
Where the fuck do you think you're going?
Say it.
Fuck you!
Say it!
She's down there!
Let's start with your name.
Why was Moody looking
for Edward Hayes' son?
Who else out there
should we know about?
Fuck!
Anyone ever last this long.
It's out of our hands now, anyway.
Him?
That was a long 27 minutes.
I'm still waiting for your call.
It's all right.
I don't take these things personally.
Bone broth.
Helps with inflammation and bruising.
Here.
Careful. It's hot. Watch it.
There you go.
I like this myself.
Here you go, small sips.
Good?
Not gonna lie to you,
there's not much of a chance
this ends well for you.
That guy out there.
We work for the same individual.
Boss has a problem.
He calls him, he takes care of it.
Little heavy handed for my taste
but that's not my call.
I'm sorry about your friend, Moody.
I had no part in that.
Or the fire fight at the bookstore.
I'm an after-the-facts guy.
I come in to make sure
there's no loose ends.
I look for things that might
seem benign, but aren't.
Like a bookstore run by an assassin,
boy, I never saw that one coming.
I misread you completely.
I can help you out of here.
Okay?
But you have to help me.
I'm your last line of defense.
End of the road, no more lifelines.
You understand?
All right.
You forgot to blanch the bones.
Your soup.
You have to blanch the bones
before you roast them.
Locks the minerals in,
it's better for healing.
You got anything out of her?
Yes and no.
What the fuck
is that supposed to mean?
Means I'll be back in the morning
to follow up with her.
-I don't need you here, Rembrandt.
-Well…
the man who signs the checks
thought differently.
-Oh, yeah?
-Yeah.
And why is that?
Oh, I don't know.
Maybe it's because you killed Vohl
without asking his permission.
Vohl knew everything,
he was a direct connection.
Would've folded like a tent.
You… yes, kill me, you're all the same:
shoot first and ask questions later.
And hold off on those
enhanced interrogation techniques.
I want her clear-headed in the morning.
He'll break her tomorrow.
Maybe he broke her already.
The old man is desperate
to know what she knows.
I wonder how it'd feel if his boy wonder
ends up killing her before he finds out.
I'm guessing he'll look
for a new boy wonder.
Just when we were getting
to know each other.
I've got teams at the airport,
shipyard and train station.
She's not gonna run, she's gonna lick
her wounds. Then she's coming after you.
Good.
Really?
Cause right now it's 4:0. She's wining.
Where do you buy your suits?
Cause I've got a cousin as big and tall
and he's a hard time.
Nobody's home.
Well, I can get you to the border.
London may not be safe
for you right now.
This is Vietnam, Anna,
you know what's it like here.
You owe it to Moody to stay alive.
I know what I owe him.
Go.
The fuck you think
I gave you the money fo--
End of the line, kid.
Get in!
Watch out!
Moody was beautiful,
in his way.
He was kind.
And not through effort,
it was just a part of who he was.
He didn't save my life,
he gave me a life.
He knew who I was, what I've become.
And he protected me.
Hayes has been dead for thirty years,
Vohl was gone longer.
You've got some very bad people
looking for you.
Lucas Hayes killed Moody,
he knows I'm looking for him.
His last known location
is St. Quiteria Hospital.
Nobody is as deaf as those
who don't wanna listen.
Hello, Ms. Nguyen.
It's been some time since we've had
a visit from the Ministry of Health.
And to request records
from that far back…
Yes, I know.
We're hoping to find something
in there that will help us
rule out environmental factors,
cause we are in the midst of a study.
Thank you.
Lucas Hayes, well before my time here.
2 5 8 5 0 2 4 5 8 6.
Copy, I'll get Doc on it.
Okay.
Doc came through, pulled his records.
And?
Sit down: Lucas Hayes was admitted
to St. Quiteria on 2nd June, 1999,
and according to his records never left.
I apologize, seems the boy was
re-admitted under the name Christian.
Christian, right,
his mother's maiden name.
He was already here when I arrived,
been a patient
for more than twenty years.
He doesn't like to be touched.
He can't speak. Also deaf and blind.
And how long has he been like this?
He was diagnosed when he was six,
I believe, it regressed rapidly.
It's a miracle he's lived as long.
And who pays for his care?
We have a generous endowment.
Everyone here is treated for free.
Wow! Four men dead, nothing on camera.
Place looks like an abattoir.
Was it the food?
You know, it was bad manners.
Yeah, well, that's no way to treat a lady.
I'm no lady.
Not that I was a gentleman myself.
I wouldn't sell yourself short.
Coming from you, that's a compliment.
I'm in the middle of something--
Hey, how were good sisters
of the St. Quiteria?
Good enough to let me know
I've been looking for the wrong person.
Good gals out there.
St. Quiteria, do you know who she was?
Fifteen years old, she led a guerrilla war
against the Roman legions.
Bad ass.
They chopped off her head
and fed the rest to the dogs.
Again, bad manners.
Hey, you up for a dinner? I could answer
some questions and save you some time.
What do say if we say La Cinq?
Tomorrow night, eight o'clock.
I mean you can say it.
But I won't be there.
I'll give you the time and place.
You're intrigued by her.
Curious.
Need I worry?
The gala list, sir,
200 guests, all vetted.
The joys of a room full of
the wealthy and the privileged
donating large sums for a noble cause.
Never gets old.
Good.
Why did you do this?
It's what people in my position
are supposed to do, Michael.
Give to the less fortunate.
I asked if I should be worried.
About the woman.
Nope. Not yet.
Please wrap up
this unpleasantness by Sunday.
I don't wanna be embarrassed
before the celebration.
Wow.
Thank you, Ben.
They know me here.
Cheers.
Someone killed a friend of mine
because of a contract
he completed years ago.
And anyone I ask about it ends up dead.
Why is that?
I don't know, but some people
might take it as a sign.
Why don't you just consider it
a mystery best left unsolved?
But I like mysteries.
When I started this I was curios.
And then I went from curious to concerned.
And now?
I'm testy.
An trust me, you don't wanna
know me when I'm testy.
HK 9mm.
Very good.
Not from where I'm sitting.
Who's paying for the orphan kid?
I'd like to talk to whoever that is.
That'd be unwise.
Unwise is killing a man
who was a second father to me.
We are way past unwise.
This is a really bad place for a hit.
High-end restaurant, the security
at every exit, not to mention the cameras.
You know what, you already knew that.
Oh, I'm not here to kill you…
Yet. Just to get answers.
You always ask like this?
Yeah, I like to have peoples' attention
when I talk, you know?
Well…
you certainly have the attention
of the boys down there.
Look, you're gonna have to put
at least three in me to be sure.
Four.
Fine. That leaves you with five.
In case there's trouble
You think that's enough
to get you out of here?
Four quick shots and then the slow walk
to the exit amongst the chaos. Yeah.
Something unexpected could happen.
You know, it usually does.
SIG 226, it's got that great kick.
Yeah.
How about that.
Our first awkward silence.
You know what, I didn't get your name.
Anna.
Pleasure.
We'll see.
What do you say we forget these tricks.
Let's just go for a nice hotel.
You point a gun at my pussy
and then you ask me to bed?
I like your style.
Said the woman with hollow-points
pointed at my balls.
Well, let's hope this doesn't get messy,
These are my favorite shoes.
Manolo's, classic four inch pumps.
A man who knows Poe and footwear.
Let me put this to you delicately,
you keep this up, you're gonna die.
Vietnam has always been a place of death.
Only lucky ones make it out alive.
I was lucky once.
You don't get lucky twice.
I'm going to find out
who killed my friend.
And when you do?
I'm going to end their life,
and anyone standing in my way.
Thank you for a lovely evening.
Hey, I know it sounds crazy,
but I'd really like to see you again
under, you know, different circumstances.
This was personal time.
So these are the best circumstances
you'll ever see me in.
Speak.
Call me when it's done.
I thought you're off
chasing corrupt accountants.
I found a hotel room with all
of her shit, including her passport.
Name's Nadia Zhukova.
An Asian Russian.
Boy.
You don't really see that ever.
Good work, you must be exhausted, huh?
Looks like I'm a day late.
And a dollar short.
Didn't take much I'm afraid.
He sang like a bird, didn't he?
All of the things I know now.
I know who your boss is,
the man who sanctioned Moody's killing.
He's a big fish.
More fun when you hook him.
Well, then I guess…
I guess we'll be seeing
each other real soon then.
Sooner than you think.
Hey, what happened to your hand?
Make up your mind:
kill me or fuck me?
It's so weird that we're
in this guy's bed while he's…
up there.
You know, hanging.
No.
Would be a waste of a nice bed.
Okay.
How long have you been doing this?
Not, you know, this, but…
Long enough not to miss.
You got lucky.
Nah.
You don't want me dead.
Yet.
Why haven't you killed me?
Could you?
I could put two in the back of your head
and go make a sandwich.
Well.
You always said
this wasn't gonna work out.
No.
It's been my experience, it never does.
At least not for the other guy.
Have a way around that?
You are holding all the cards.
I'm watching a woman
who walk over a shark tank
on a tight rope in high winds.
You're not gonna make it, Anna.
He's a bad man.
Who's done very bad things.
So, you just gonna lay there?
Good to see you, kid.
Get in. Get out.
You know you only get lucky once.
Yeah. Someone else just told me that.
Okay.
God!
-Just a little glue. Just a little glue.
-What's wrong with you!
It's okay, grit your teeth.
Oh, God.
You know, I still feel
really bad about Claudia.
She couldn't cook worth a shit,
but she didn't deserve to die like that.
Here we go.
Okay.
Okay, okay. We're done here.
Did you really think
they can kill me that easily?
Before I blew the rest of it off he didn't
have much of a face to begin with.
And I left just enough of me
for the authorities to think it was me.
I'm sorry you had
to be the one who found him.
You could always think
on your feet anyway.
Not so much tonight.
That's what friends are for, right?
Oh, good. We're friends again.
You got laid, didn't you?
Depending more and more on this shit
to take the edge off.
So, what's the plan?
Four hundred acres, to get there
you'd have to hike through 12 miles
of rat-infested jungle.
That leaves the river,
cameras, sonar, patrol boats.
Still a pessimistic little shit,
aren't you?
And you're still a cockroach
you can't kill.
I mean it in a good way.
They know you're coming.
What is this?
It's a panic room,
in this case it's a panic bunker.
If he gets in there, you're done.
All the guests arrive by boat,
they'll be screened
a moment they disembark.
Perimeter locked down and site secured.
And I've added an additional team
of 16 out of Israel just for the night.
Seems like you got everything covered.
Michael.
Thoughts?
Venice.
It's really nice this time of year.
You should go. Now.
These guys have no idea
who they're dealing with.
Copy that.
You look a little tense.
I've protected everyone
from crowned princes to cartel kingpins.
Nothing's gonna happen tonight
especially when we know what she looks like.
Boy…
I really hope you got paid upfront.
Sir.
Anything?
Nothing so far. Sectors one,
two and three are clear.
I'm waiting on the reports
from sector four.
Thank you.
It is with great pleasure that I welcome
you all here on this very expensive evening.
It warms my crusty heart to look across
the room and see so many familiar faces,
dear friends, and close
business associates.
As well as quite a few unfamiliar faces
that with luck will not remain so for long.
Perhaps I may even have spotted
a few former foes of mine.
I want especially to thank you for coming,
and for seeing the error of your ways.
Over these considerable years
I've learnt to my great satisfaction
there is no better way to cleanse the soul
than to do good,
to perform selfless deeds.
and acts of kindness,
to sacrifice for others,
and most importantly to give generously.
It is due to your generous spirit
that we've been able to enrich and enhance
the lives of so many infants,
children, young men and women
in desperate need of care
to a degree that would have been impossible
to achieve without every one of you.
Ladies and gentlemen, thank you for
the privilege of being your host tonight.
And for allowing me to slide my hands
into your pockets and purses,
but for a worthy a cause.
The sisters of St. Quiteria
do outstanding work… So…
…Give with your heart.
You look really good for a man
who's been dead thirty years, Mr. Hayes.
How'd you get in here?
Technology.
It just gonna fuck us all one day.
Who are you?
I'm the big bad wolf that comes to get you
when someone on this Earth
decides your time is up.
Moody.
Resurrection is a bitch, ain't it?
You've come to finish the job,
haven't you?
Well, you did hire me
all those years ago to kill you, right?
Who was really in that car?
Does it matter? Disposable asset.
No one of any consequence.
You see, that's the kind of shit
I expect someone like you to say.
"No one of any consequence."
"Someone like me"?
Man, I can't be all morally right.
I kill people for a living,
bad people, mind you, but still.
I never pretend to be anything else.
You, you're front and center
of a dozen high-profile charitable causes.
The world sees you as clean
as first fucking snow.
But your hands are covered in shit.
Blood, everything from from sarin gas
to human trafficking.
So you know why
I had to arrange my demise.
I had a son,
unexpected in many ways.
But what I couldn't fathom
was the depths of love
I had for this child,
this imperfect, wonderful, vulnerable boy.
If I were dead, Lucas would be free
from any threats or harm.
Bullshit.
You may love your son, Mr. Hayes,
but that was your chance to disappear.
You're very astute.
No one looks for a dead man.
I was able to continue behind the shroud
of respectability that allowed me to--
To become a bigger monster.
The irony of all of this, Mr. Hayes,
is that I was just trying
to make amends to your son
for taking his father away from him.
You brought all of this on yourself.
Anna.
You don't look so good.
I don't know.
Nothing an Apple Martini
and a liter of AB positive won't fix, huh?
Hey, what do you think
the chances are of me getting either?
Faint.
Something funny?
I find it amusing you think
you're better than me.
Not better.
Different.
You see, most people are good, Mr. Hayes.
Then occasionally they do something
they know is bad.
Some people are bad, and they struggle
every day to keep it under control.
Others… corrupt to the core and just
don't give a damn, that would be me.
But evil…
Evil is a completely different
creature, Mr. Hayes.
Evil believes bad is okay,
its actions are justified.
Violence divorced from conscience,
no matter what toll it takes
or who it takes it upon.
And there, my friend,
is where we part ways.
I'm just a bad man
who's looking to pay for his sins.
I see.
So you are here to clear
your conscience first then?
You'll never get out of here alive.
I never intended to.
One more thing.
You could have killed the old man.
Why didn't you?
That wasn't the plan.
ANNA: IT'S BEEN A BLAST.
LOCATION
Leave me alone!
No! No!
No! Mom!
Mom!
What took you?
Just out for a bite.
You just gonna stand there?
For now.
It doesn't have to be this way, Anna.
Not anymore.
We all have to pay
for our sins eventually.
Doesn't have to be today.
I'm tired.
I want peace.
And I can't have it
while you're out there.
What if I told you you could?
Yeah?
Two in the back of the head,
and then go have a sandwich.
You can't buy back your past, Anna,
can't change where you came from,
but you can change where you're going.
Where would that be?
Transcript by sub.Trader & Clarity