[Script Info]
; Script generated by Aegisub 3.2.2
; http://www.aegisub.org/
Synch Point: 0
ScriptType: v4.00+
PlayResX: 0
PlayResY: 0
WrapStyle: 0
Timer: 100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正黑体_GBK,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H32000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,1,2,5,5,2,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:03:42.68,0:03:59.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(2900,0)\c&H3CC43C&\an8\bord1\fs18\b1}洛基\N第一季 第三集
Dialogue: 0,0:00:05.47,0:00:07.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(740,310)\bord1\fs18\b1\pos(190.2,132)}前情提要
Dialogue: 0,0:07:41.52,0:07:48.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(1810,0)\bord1\fs18\b1\pos(191.1,129.6)}拉曼蒂斯1号
Dialogue: 0,0:00:02.63,0:00:05.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是宇宙里最强大的力量吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Is this the greatest power in the universe?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:07.32,0:00:10.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一名在逃时间异体一直在杀害我们的时间卫队\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}A fugitive Variant's been killing our Minutemen.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.16,0:00:14.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管这个时间异体是谁\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Whoever this Variant is,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:14.75,0:00:16.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们一直没能找到他\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}we haven't been able to find him.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:16.77,0:00:18.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,时间变异管理局\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The Time Variance Authority
Dialogue: 0,0:00:18.42,0:00:20.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和阿斯加德的神们都一样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and the gods of Asgard, one and the same.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:20.82,0:00:22.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因权力而迷醉  对真相视而不见\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Drunk with power, blinded to the truth.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:22.85,0:00:25.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,时间守护者在密切关注此案的方方面面\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The Time-Keepers are monitoring every aspect of this case.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.84,0:00:28.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他躲在了天启里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}He's hiding in apocalypses.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:29.33,0:00:32.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你就是时管局叫来追捕我的笨蛋\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You're the fool the TVA brought in to hunt me down.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:32.53,0:00:34.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你  是我吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Me, I presume.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:34.32,0:00:36.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要推翻时间守护者\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm going to overthrow the Time-Keepers.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:36.25,0:00:39.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没兴趣统治时间变异管理局\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm not interested in ruling the Time Variance Authority.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:40.91,0:00:42.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我泄密了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I gave it away.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:42.25,0:00:43.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,时间守护者  他们的所在\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The Time-Keepers, where they are.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.82,0:00:45.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想要什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What do you want?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.51,0:00:53.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  等等  洛基\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No! No! Loki, wait!
Dialogue: 0,0:00:53.40,0:00:55.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等  洛基  等一下\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Wait! Loki, wait!
Dialogue: 0,0:00:56.31,0:00:58.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  等等  洛基\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No! Wait, Loki!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:38.77,0:01:42.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们可以试试土豆皮或水牛指\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We could do potato skins or buffalo fingers...
Dialogue: 0,0:01:42.41,0:01:44.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们也可以去别处吃\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Or we could eat somewhere else.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:44.08,0:01:45.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你为什么讨厌这里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Why do you hate this place?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:45.51,0:01:47.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不讨厌它  我恐惧它\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I don't hate it, I fear it.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:47.25,0:01:48.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道卫生部\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Do you know how many times
Dialogue: 0,0:01:48.32,0:01:50.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,关过这里几次吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}the health department has closed this place down?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:51.05,0:01:52.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,酒水似乎还行\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Well, the drinks seem fine.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.36,0:01:58.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Oh, God!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:59.10,0:02:00.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大脑冻住了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Ah, brain freeze!
Dialogue: 0,0:02:00.28,0:02:02.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道大脑冻住是什么意思吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You know what brain freeze is, don't you?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:02.25,0:02:03.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又来了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Here we go.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:03.27,0:02:05.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是当你啜饮了很冷的东西\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's when you sip something so cold...
Dialogue: 0,0:02:05.58,0:02:08.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大脑冻住跟冷有关  懂了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Brain freeze associated with coldness... Got it.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:08.16,0:02:09.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等  我说真的呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Wait, I'm being serious.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:09.03,0:02:11.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,寒冷穿透你的上颚\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}So, it permeates the roof of your mouth
Dialogue: 0,0:02:11.91,0:02:14.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,冻住了你大脑里的突触\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and it freezes the synapses in your brain.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:14.31,0:02:18.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把你的记忆真正的冻结住了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}So, your memories are literally frozen in place.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:19.01,0:02:21.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-才不是呢  -就是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- That is absolutely not true. - It is!
Dialogue: 0,0:02:21.68,0:02:23.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好啊  试试吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Okay. Try it.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:23.17,0:02:25.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管你在想什么  都会冻结住\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Whatever you're thinking about will get frozen in place.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:25.35,0:02:26.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我来问你个问题\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm gonna ask you a question,
Dialogue: 0,0:02:26.61,0:02:28.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的突触解冻前\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and you won't be able to answer
Dialogue: 0,0:02:28.07,0:02:30.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你会无法回答我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}until the synapses have melted.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:30.39,0:02:32.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接受挑战\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Challenge accepted.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:36.05,0:02:37.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好  问吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Okay, ask.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:37.65,0:02:40.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有多少人在守卫时间守护者\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}How many people are guarding the Time-Keepers?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:41.52,0:02:42.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm sorry, what?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:51.13,0:02:53.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们做好闺蜜多久了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}How long have we been best friends?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:54.00,0:02:54.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太久了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Too long.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:54.72,0:02:57.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说真的  你知道你什么都可以跟我说吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Seriously, you know you can tell me anything, right?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:57.04,0:02:58.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Of course.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:58.15,0:02:58.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你怎么不肯告诉我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Why won't you tell me
Dialogue: 0,0:02:58.97,0:03:01.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有多少人守卫时间守护者\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}how many people are guarding the Time-Keepers?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:01.34,0:03:02.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Oh, well, there's...
Dialogue: 0,0:03:07.22,0:03:08.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这地方  我...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}This place, I...
Dialogue: 0,0:03:09.26,0:03:11.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我记得  我认得这里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I remember, I know this place.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:15.44,0:03:16.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我不认得你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}But I don't know you.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:16.65,0:03:19.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事  你只是累了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's okay. You're just tired.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:22.05,0:03:25.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  我可能只是累了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yeah. I'm probably just tired.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:27.93,0:03:30.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,电梯在哪\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}How do I find the elevators?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:30.78,0:03:32.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是金色的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}They're gold.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:03.42,0:04:05.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全体时间卫队前往军械库\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}All Minutemen to armory.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:05.54,0:04:07.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,保护时间线\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Protect the timeline.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:10.06,0:04:12.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全体时间卫队前往军械库\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}All Minutemen to armory.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:12.17,0:04:14.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,保护时间线\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Protect the timeline.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:17.85,0:04:18.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道  长官\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I don't know, sir.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:52.83,0:04:55.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全体时间卫队前往军械库\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}All Minutemen to armory.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.08,0:04:56.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,保护时间线\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Protect the timeline.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:25.31,0:05:26.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,站住\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Stop!
Dialogue: 0,0:05:43.76,0:05:44.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,问几个问题\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}A few questions.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:44.86,0:05:47.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你真没别的更好的事可做吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Have you really got nothing else better to do?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:47.19,0:05:48.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无礼\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Rude.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:50.29,0:05:51.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你确定你是个洛基吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Are you sure you're a Loki?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:51.94,0:05:54.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你挡我路了  -你是我的路\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- You're in my way. - You are my way.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:58.07,0:06:00.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们或许可以合作\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I thought perhaps we could work together.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:06.42,0:06:09.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但看来你缺乏远见\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}But now I see you lack vision.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:11.61,0:06:13.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要么自愿跟我来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}So, either you'll come willingly...
Dialogue: 0,0:06:16.25,0:06:17.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要么不愿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Or you won't.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:17.21,0:06:19.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管怎样  你都是我见到时间守护者的办法\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Either way, that's how I get to meet the Time-Keepers.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:19.17,0:06:20.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老天啊  闭嘴吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Oh, God. Shut up!
Dialogue: 0,0:06:26.66,0:06:28.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再靠近  我就杀了他\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Come any closer and I'll kill him.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:28.71,0:06:29.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,动手吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Go for it.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:45.27,0:06:46.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放开我的腿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Get off my leg!
Dialogue: 0,0:06:52.05,0:06:54.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再见  时间异体\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Goodbye, Variant.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:54.87,0:06:56.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你没电了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You're outta juice.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:58.75,0:06:59.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好用了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's not working.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:09.40,0:07:10.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Right...
Dialogue: 0,0:07:10.20,0:07:13.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还给我吧  你都不会充电\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Give It to me. You don't know how to recharge it.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:13.27,0:07:15.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我当然会  你不是唯一懂技术的洛基\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Of course I do. You're not the only tech savvy Loki.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:15.76,0:07:17.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,永远别那么喊我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Don't ever call me that.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:18.05,0:07:20.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-懂技术  -不  洛基\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Tech savvy? - No, a Loki.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:22.93,0:07:24.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来你就是个魔术师咯\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You're just fully a magician then?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:24.39,0:07:28.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好啊  下个魔术  我把你变没\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Fine. For my next trick, I'll make you disappear.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:33.38,0:07:35.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-那是你的能力吗  -你把我们传到哪了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Is that one of your powers? - Where did you send us?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:02.02,0:08:04.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你个白痴  这里是拉曼蒂斯1号\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You idiot! This is Lamentis 1.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:04.22,0:08:05.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道那意味着什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I don't know what that means!
Dialogue: 0,0:08:06.87,0:08:10.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这颗卫星马上要被那颗行星撞击并摧毁\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The moon that planet is about to crash into and destroy.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:10.94,0:08:13.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,时空器上存储的所有天启\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Of all of the apocalypses saved on that TemPad,
Dialogue: 0,0:08:13.15,0:08:14.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个是最糟的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}this is the worst!
Dialogue: 0,0:08:14.14,0:08:15.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里无人生还\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No one makes it off here!
Dialogue: 0,0:08:15.85,0:08:16.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小心\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Watch out!
Dialogue: 0,0:08:18.26,0:08:19.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉  女士\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm sorry, madam.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:19.30,0:08:21.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我又没时间浏览小册子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Didn't have time to scan the brochure.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:22.68,0:08:24.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对了  我以为你希望我死呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}By the way, I thought you wanted me dead.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:24.49,0:08:26.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道你把时空器藏在哪了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I don't know where you hid that TemPad,
Dialogue: 0,0:08:26.16,0:08:26.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但如果你炸了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}but if you blow up,
Dialogue: 0,0:08:26.87,0:08:29.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,它就炸了  那我也得炸\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}it blows up, and then I end up blown up.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:29.55,0:08:30.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}There!
Dialogue: 0,0:08:30.74,0:08:32.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我们是一队了吗  -才不是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- So we're a team now? - Oh, God, no!
Dialogue: 0,0:08:34.93,0:08:35.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,趴下\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Get down!
Dialogue: 0,0:08:37.00,0:08:38.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我才不需要你帮忙\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Didn't need your help!
Dialogue: 0,0:08:38.40,0:08:39.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好奇怪\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You're so weird!
Dialogue: 0,0:09:20.72,0:09:21.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在干什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What are you doing?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:22.42,0:09:23.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在干什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What are you doing?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:24.38,0:09:25.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是想对我用魅术吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You trying to enchant me?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:27.86,0:09:28.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不会成功的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It won't work.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:29.80,0:09:31.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么  因为你是魔法师吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Why? Because you're a magician?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:31.46,0:09:34.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-不  因为我的头脑太强大  -好啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- No, because my mind is too strong. - Fine!
Dialogue: 0,0:09:36.95,0:09:39.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听着  我们真要在这里开战吗  再来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Look. Are we really about to do this here? Again?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:39.91,0:09:41.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你说怎么办\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What do you propose instead?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:41.22,0:09:42.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道  休战吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I don't know. A truce?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:43.95,0:09:46.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听着  我们如果不能打开时空器\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Listen, neither of us is getting off this rock
Dialogue: 0,0:09:46.31,0:09:48.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就都别想离开这星球\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}if we can't turn that TemPad on.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:48.07,0:09:49.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你藏在哪了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Where do you have it hidden?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:49.35,0:09:51.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-在我心里  -那我就把它挖出来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- In my heart. - Well, then, I'll cut it out.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:51.65,0:09:54.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好啊  真好笑  有趣\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Nice. Very droll. Lovely.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:54.52,0:09:57.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  时空器是在我身上\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Okay, yes, I do have the TemPad,
Dialogue: 0,0:09:57.58,0:09:58.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但如果你无时无刻\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}but I'm not gonna get very far
Dialogue: 0,0:09:58.77,0:10:00.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不想着杀我  我也走不了多远\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}if you keep trying to kill me every 30 seconds.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:00.05,0:10:00.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你满嘴谎言\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You're full of it
Dialogue: 0,0:10:00.90,0:10:02.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为你需要我才能给它充电\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}because you need me to get that thing recharged.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:02.91,0:10:05.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以你刚刚才会在外面救我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}That's the only reason you saved me out there.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:07.38,0:10:08.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或许吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Maybe.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:08.10,0:10:10.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  是  还有那个原因\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yeah. I mean, sure. That too.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:11.30,0:10:12.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们也可以在这个废弃矿井里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Or we could slaughter each other here
Dialogue: 0,0:10:12.85,0:10:14.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,互相残杀\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}in this abandoned mining shack.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:14.49,0:10:16.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-怎么样  -我觉得挺好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- What do you say? - Good for me.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:20.00,0:10:24.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你打断的计划  我已筹划多年\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The plan you interrupted was years in the making.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:24.70,0:10:26.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-多年  -知道了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Years! - Okay, got it.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:26.41,0:10:28.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一启动时空器\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And as soon as I turn that TemPad back on,
Dialogue: 0,0:10:28.64,0:10:30.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就会马上回时管局\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm going straight back to the TVA
Dialogue: 0,0:10:30.87,0:10:32.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去了结我开始的战斗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}to finish what I started.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:32.52,0:10:33.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Good.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:33.94,0:10:36.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-到时我就杀了你  -或者是我杀了你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- I'll kill you then. - Or I'll kill you.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:37.98,0:10:38.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你去哪\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Where're you going?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:39.81,0:10:41.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这卫星上有电力\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}There's power somewhere on this moon.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:42.13,0:10:42.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们只需要足够电力\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We just need enough of it
Dialogue: 0,0:10:42.95,0:10:45.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,便可以穿越跨维度时空\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}to travel through inter-dimensional time and space.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:47.94,0:10:48.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Jeez!
Dialogue: 0,0:10:49.32,0:10:50.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yep.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:03.87,0:11:05.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么计划的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}So, what's the plan?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:06.07,0:11:09.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里附近有个镇  你能不能闭嘴\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}There's a town near here. And can you shut up?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:09.04,0:11:09.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然我不得不跟你合作\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Just because I have to work with you
Dialogue: 0,0:11:09.98,0:11:11.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不代表我想听到你的声音\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}doesn't mean I wanna hear your voice.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:11.75,0:11:15.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好啊  慢点  时间异体\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}All right, well... Slow down, Variant.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:15.48,0:11:18.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,即刻死亡你是哪里不懂\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What part of imminent death confuses you?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:19.23,0:11:20.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别喊我"时间异体"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And don't call me "Variant."
Dialogue: 0,0:11:21.11,0:11:25.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉  但我不会把我的褪色复印版称为"洛基"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm sorry, but I'm not calling some faded photocopy of me "Loki."
Dialogue: 0,0:11:25.56,0:11:28.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很好  因为我已经不是那个人了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Good. 'Cause that's not who I am anymore.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:28.01,0:11:29.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我现在是茜薇\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm Sylvie now.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:30.10,0:11:31.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你改了名字  太好了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You changed your name. Brilliant.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:31.62,0:11:32.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这叫假名\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's called an alias.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:32.70,0:11:33.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不怎么像洛基\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's not very Loki-like.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:33.65,0:11:37.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗  那怎么才算洛基行为\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yeah? What exactly makes a Loki a Loki?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:37.53,0:11:41.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,独立  权威  风格\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Independence, authority, style.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:41.21,0:11:42.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以自然而然地  你去为\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}So, naturally you went to work
Dialogue: 0,0:11:42.57,0:11:44.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无聊压迫的时间警察工作了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}for the boring, oppressive time police.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:44.16,0:11:46.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不为他们工作  我是个顾问\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I don't work for them. I'm a consultant.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:46.85,0:11:48.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你都不知道你想要什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You don't know what you want.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:48.41,0:11:49.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗  那你呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Oh, yeah? What about you?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:51.04,0:11:52.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你筹划了数年的计划\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Your years-in-the-making plan
Dialogue: 0,0:11:52.39,0:11:54.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是毁了那里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}was to tear the place down,
Dialogue: 0,0:11:54.22,0:11:55.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,创造一个终极权力真空\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}create the ultimate power vacuum,
Dialogue: 0,0:11:55.70,0:11:58.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后走开\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and then just walk away.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:59.07,0:12:00.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我绝不会那么做\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'd never have done that.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:00.22,0:12:02.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗  我可不是你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yeah? Well, I'm not you.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:03.27,0:12:04.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们能不能赶紧继续了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Can we get on with this now?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:15.19,0:12:17.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来大家都跑了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It looks like everyone already fled.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:17.57,0:12:19.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果是的话  那也是徒劳\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}If they did, it was in vain.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:20.65,0:12:22.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们还有多久\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}How long do we have?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:22.09,0:12:23.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,12小时左右\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Twelve hours or so.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:23.90,0:12:26.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里的情况只会更糟\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Things down here are only gonna get worse.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:26.02,0:12:28.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,更多陨石  重力地震\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}More meteors, gravity quakes,
Dialogue: 0,0:12:28.84,0:12:32.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然  还有面临毁灭时的社会崩溃\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and of course, the collapse of society in the face of annihilation.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:34.73,0:12:36.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个能给时空器充电吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Could that charge the TemPad?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:36.85,0:12:37.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或许吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Maybe.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:43.44,0:12:44.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我在查看耦合装置\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm just checking the coupling.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:44.99,0:12:46.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,确保连接好了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Making sure it can connect.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:46.60,0:12:47.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Right.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:48.24,0:12:49.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了  给我吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Okay. Hand it over.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:52.79,0:12:54.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真可悲  我才不会给你呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Pitiful. I'm not giving it to you.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:54.41,0:12:56.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还得更努力点\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You're gonna have to try harder than that.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:57.33,0:13:00.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那也别向我提你的"懂技术"的点子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Then don't give me your "Tech savvy" ideas either.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:01.00,0:13:03.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,时空器需要大量电力\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The TemPad requires a massive power source,
Dialogue: 0,0:13:03.33,0:13:04.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夜灯是不够的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}not a night light.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:33.08,0:13:37.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,蛮力不能替代交涉和诡计\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Brute force is no substitute for diplomacy and guile.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:37.66,0:13:38.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Noted.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:49.84,0:13:53.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你能走到这一步都令人惊叹\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's remarkable that you ever made it as far as you did.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:54.26,0:13:55.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Sorry about that.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:55.40,0:13:57.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不必  我可开心了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Don't be. I enjoyed it.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:57.95,0:14:00.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也是呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I did too.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:00.24,0:14:01.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但请相信我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}But I can assure you,
Dialogue: 0,0:14:01.33,0:14:05.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尽管我的...同伴行为粗暴\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}despite my acquaintance behaving like an animal...
Dialogue: 0,0:14:05.56,0:14:06.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们并无恶意\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}...uh, we mean you no harm.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:06.91,0:14:09.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们只是疲劳旅人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We're simply weary travelers.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:09.09,0:14:10.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Sure you are.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:25.64,0:14:26.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好  亲爱的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Hello, dear.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:28.07,0:14:29.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,帕崔斯\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Patrice?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:32.13,0:14:35.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好久没见\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It... It's been a long time.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:36.24,0:14:37.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还是那么美...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You're as beautiful as...
Dialogue: 0,0:14:44.98,0:14:48.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,帕崔斯30年来从没说过那么客气的话\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Patrice never said a thing that nice in 30 years.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:49.08,0:14:51.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们不是旅人  你们是魔鬼\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You're no travelers, you're devils.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:53.02,0:14:54.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那算什么  交涉吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Which one was that? Diplomacy?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:54.72,0:14:57.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-还是...  -别  别说了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Or... - Don't. Just don't.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:02.99,0:15:05.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们两个魔鬼想要什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What do you devils want with me?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:05.67,0:15:09.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们只想问你个问题  人都哪去了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We just wanna ask you a question. Where is everyone?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:10.49,0:15:11.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,方舟\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The ark.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:14.94,0:15:17.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,撤离船\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The evacuation vessel.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:18.42,0:15:19.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那样的东西就有足够给\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Something like that would have enough juice
Dialogue: 0,0:15:19.95,0:15:21.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,时空器充能的电力\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}to repower the TemPad.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:24.19,0:15:25.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们怎么过去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}How do we get there?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:27.04,0:15:29.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,火车站在镇边界\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Train station's the edge of town.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:30.00,0:15:31.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但你们别想买到票\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}But you'll never get a ticket.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:33.48,0:15:34.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们走吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Come on, let's go.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:54.58,0:15:55.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,安静\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Quiet down!
Dialogue: 0,0:15:58.53,0:15:59.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,退后\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Get back!
Dialogue: 0,0:16:00.00,0:16:00.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么回事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What's going on?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:01.71,0:16:02.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,方舟今晚就走\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The ark leaves tonight
Dialogue: 0,0:16:02.83,0:16:05.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们排队排了好几个小时了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and we've been waiting in line for hours.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:06.42,0:16:07.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好几个小时了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}For hours.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:09.68,0:16:11.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看上去真好玩\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Well, this looks fun.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:11.79,0:16:12.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Come on.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:13.60,0:16:15.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们别想打上火车\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We can't fight our way onto that train.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:15.01,0:16:16.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁说要打了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Who said anything about fighting?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:16.51,0:16:18.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你的计划都跟打有关  -这个没有\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- All your plans involve fighting. - Not this one.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:19.08,0:16:20.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我用魅术控制一个卫兵\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm going to enchant a guard,
Dialogue: 0,0:16:20.40,0:16:22.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让他带我们穿过人群\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}have him lead us through the crowd,
Dialogue: 0,0:16:22.52,0:16:24.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果有人敢找我们事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and if anyone gives us any trouble...
Dialogue: 0,0:16:24.52,0:16:26.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就让他开枪吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Make him start shooting?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:26.13,0:16:29.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后呢  杀了所有卫兵  然后劫持火车吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And then what, kill every guard and hijack the train?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:29.07,0:16:31.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要不要打  就看他们的了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Whether or not there's a fight is entirely up to them.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:32.63,0:16:35.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这次  我们按我的办法来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We're doing this one my way.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:38.41,0:16:40.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我看上去如何  -像是计划不怎么样的人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- How do I look? - Like someone with a shit plan.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:40.64,0:16:41.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这计划多好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's a great plan.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:42.65,0:16:44.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看我眼色行事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Just follow my lead.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:46.14,0:16:48.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我们为什么不能上  -让我们上去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Why can't we get on? - Let us in! Come on!
Dialogue: 0,0:16:48.61,0:16:50.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去苏鲁吗  这边请  先生\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}To Shuroo? This way, sir.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:50.41,0:16:53.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我们上去  女人和小孩\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Let us in! Women and children...
Dialogue: 0,0:16:54.13,0:16:57.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们只把票给有钱人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}They're only giving tickets out to the wealthy!
Dialogue: 0,0:16:57.45,0:16:59.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们怎么办\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What about us?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:03.18,0:17:04.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请出示车票\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Tickets?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:15.00,0:17:16.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要带这家伙去苏鲁\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Taking this one to Shuroo.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:16.64,0:17:19.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好啊  票呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Okay. And the tickets?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:19.38,0:17:21.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有来自上方的命令  要带她上车\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Orders come from the top to get her on this train.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:22.40,0:17:23.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,长官  他们...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Sir, this...
Dialogue: 0,0:17:25.99,0:17:27.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没什么事吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Everything okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:27.20,0:17:28.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  一切都好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yeah, everything's fine.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:28.37,0:17:31.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我刚记起来总部今早用无线电发来消息\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yeah, I just remembered that headquarters radioed in
Dialogue: 0,0:17:31.65,0:17:33.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要他们上车\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}their request for them this morning.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:38.90,0:17:39.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:41.28,0:17:42.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:45.41,0:17:46.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请出示车票\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Tickets?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:55.38,0:17:56.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,晚上好  乘客们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Good evening, passengers.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:02.90,0:18:04.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我坐火车不能坐逆行方向\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Um, uh, look, I can't go backwards on a train.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:04.16,0:18:06.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我从不背对门坐\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Well, I never sit with my back to a door.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:06.23,0:18:08.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么  两边都有门啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What? There are doors on both sides.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:08.74,0:18:10.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,坐下吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Oh, just sit down.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:13.69,0:18:15.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对了  那都不叫计划\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}FYI, that wasn't even a plan.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:15.31,0:18:16.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Oh, really?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:16.46,0:18:18.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,计划要分很多步\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Plans have multiple steps.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:18.03,0:18:19.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,假扮成卫兵\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Dressing as a guard
Dialogue: 0,0:18:19.27,0:18:21.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上火车只是做一件事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and getting on a train is just doing a thing.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:25.68,0:18:27.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你累了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Oh, you a bit tired?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:27.38,0:18:29.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尽管休息一下吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Feel free to, you know, get some rest.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:31.69,0:18:33.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我无法在这样的地方睡觉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I can't sleep in a place like this.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:34.43,0:18:35.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你无法在火车上睡觉吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You can't sleep on a train?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:35.82,0:18:38.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是  我不能在不可靠的人旁边睡觉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No. I can't sleep around untrustworthy people.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:38.52,0:18:40.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样啊  是说我吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Oh, right. That me?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:40.28,0:18:41.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但你可以打个盹\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}But you feel free to take a nap.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:42.60,0:18:43.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想得美\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Nice try.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:44.00,0:18:46.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不会浪费时间到处找时空器\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm not gonna waste my time rooting around for the TemPad
Dialogue: 0,0:18:46.83,0:18:49.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,显然有人教你魔法教得很好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}when someone taught you fairly decent magic.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:49.22,0:18:50.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是我妈妈\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}My mother.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:59.48,0:19:00.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她什么样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What was she like?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:03.63,0:19:06.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她是...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}She was, um...
Dialogue: 0,0:19:10.16,0:19:11.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿斯加德女王\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}A Queen of Asgard.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:13.38,0:19:17.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她很好  很正派\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}She was good. Purely decent.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:19.84,0:19:21.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你确定她是你母亲吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Are you sure she was your mother?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:21.23,0:19:23.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  其实她不是  我是领养的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Oh, no, she's not actually. I was adopted.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:23.66,0:19:25.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,剧透了吗  抱歉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Is that a bit of a spoiler for you? Sorry about that.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:25.47,0:19:27.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  我知道我是领养的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No, I knew I was adopted.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:27.03,0:19:29.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么  他们告诉你了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What? They told you?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:29.47,0:19:32.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-对  他们没告诉你吗  -没\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Yeah. Did they not tell you? - No.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:34.35,0:19:36.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们最终说了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I mean, they did, eventually.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:37.51,0:19:38.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Hang on a second.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:38.75,0:19:41.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟我说说你妈妈\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}So, tell... Tell me about your mother.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:42.39,0:19:43.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不怎么记得她了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I barely remember her.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:44.73,0:19:46.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到现在只剩梦的碎片了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Just blips of a dream at this point.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:53.10,0:19:54.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我小时候\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You know, when I was young,
Dialogue: 0,0:19:54.09,0:19:57.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她会为我施展小魔法\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}she'd do these little bits of magic for me.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:58.79,0:20:01.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比如把花变成青蛙\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Like turn a flower into a frog or
Dialogue: 0,0:20:02.34,0:20:04.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或在水上放烟花\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}cast fireworks over the water.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:05.42,0:20:06.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看上去那么不可思议\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It all seemed impossible.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:06.95,0:20:09.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但她跟我说  有一天我也能做到\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}But she told me that one day I'd be able to do it too because...
Dialogue: 0,0:20:11.28,0:20:12.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我什么都能做到\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Because I could do anything.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:16.14,0:20:17.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想看看吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You wanna see?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:25.62,0:20:26.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不赖\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Not bad.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:32.28,0:20:35.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她是那种  你希望她相信你的人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}She was the kinda person you'd want to believe in you.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:36.09,0:20:37.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听上去她是相信你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Sounds like she does.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:39.02,0:20:39.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她生前是相信我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Well, she did.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:42.96,0:20:46.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你怎么学会...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}So, where'd you learn to do the...
Dialogue: 0,0:20:46.93,0:20:50.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-就是...那个  -我自学的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- You know, the... Whatever it is? - I taught myself.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:50.34,0:20:52.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你自学了那样的魔法  -对\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- You taught yourself that magic? - Yeah, I did.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:54.27,0:20:55.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你怎么...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What, do you just...
Dialogue: 0,0:20:55.64,0:20:59.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你潜入他们的大脑  投射某种幻觉吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You just go into their minds and project some sort of illusion?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:59.83,0:21:00.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我直接施展一下更容易懂\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It'd be easier if I just show...
Dialogue: 0,0:21:00.98,0:21:02.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对我施魅术  让我交出时空器\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Enchanted me and make me give you the TemPad
Dialogue: 0,0:21:02.50,0:21:03.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好跳出行驶的货舱吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}so you can leap out the moving train?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:03.80,0:21:05.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-不了  谢谢  -那就别问\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- No, thank you. - Well then, don't ask.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:05.31,0:21:06.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-好啊  -香槟酒\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Okay. - Champagne?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:07.58,0:21:09.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好啊  非常感谢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Ah, yes. Thank you very much.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:10.02,0:21:11.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不了  谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No, I'm good, thanks.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:11.36,0:21:13.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那她的我拿了  谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Oh, I'll take hers. Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:15.31,0:21:16.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,干杯\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Cheers.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:18.06,0:21:19.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,敬世界末日\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}To the end of the world.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:23.33,0:21:25.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那老女人选择赴死好可惜啊  是吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}A pity the old woman chose to die, don't you think?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:25.99,0:21:28.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-她心里有爱  -她恨他\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- She was in love. - She hated him.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.40,0:21:29.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或许爱就是恨\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Maybe love is hate.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:32.02,0:21:33.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或许该记下来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Should probably remember that.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:34.52,0:21:36.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么来着  "爱是..."\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What was that? "Love is..."
Dialogue: 0,0:21:37.06,0:21:39.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-"爱是恨"  -滚吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- "Love is hate." - Oh, piss off!
Dialogue: 0,0:21:42.69,0:21:45.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说到爱\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}So, on the subject of love,
Dialogue: 0,0:21:46.31,0:21:48.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这场征途结束时\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}is there a lucky beau
Dialogue: 0,0:21:48.41,0:21:50.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会有哪个幸运情郎在等待你吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}waiting for you at the end of this crusade?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:51.06,0:21:52.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有  还真有\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yeah, there is, actually.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:52.95,0:21:53.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,奔波在\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Managed to maintain
Dialogue: 0,0:21:53.76,0:21:56.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一个又一个天启之间时\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}quite a serious long-distance relationship with a postman
Dialogue: 0,0:21:56.99,0:21:58.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还得以跟一个\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}whilst running across time...
Dialogue: 0,0:21:58.19,0:21:59.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,邮递员维系了一段认真的异地恋\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}...from one apocalypse to another.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:00.18,0:22:02.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如此有魅力  谁能抵挡你呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}With charm like that, who could resist you?
Dialogue: 0,0:22:03.03,0:22:06.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,面对必死命运的人  什么都愿意\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Well, people are quite willing in the face of certain doom.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.49,0:22:07.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm sure they are.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:09.19,0:22:11.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是为了有动力前进\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It was only ever just to keep me going.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:13.18,0:22:16.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你呢  你可是王子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}How about you? You're a prince.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:16.29,0:22:19.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肯定有准王妃吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Must've been would-be-princesses
Dialogue: 0,0:22:20.05,0:22:21.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或许  是另一位王子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}or perhaps, another prince.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:24.89,0:22:28.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都有吧  我猜你也是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}A bit of both. I suspect the same as you.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:28.43,0:22:29.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但没有过...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}But, nothing ever...
Dialogue: 0,0:22:30.39,0:22:31.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真正的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Real.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:37.17,0:22:39.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么爱是诡计咯\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Love is mischief, then.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:43.23,0:22:44.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:47.31,0:22:49.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爱是...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Love is...
Dialogue: 0,0:22:55.04,0:22:55.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}uh, something I
Dialogue: 0,0:22:56.65,0:22:59.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可能需要再喝一杯才能去想的事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}might have to have another drink to think about.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:00.61,0:23:02.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道我们打算劫持一个文明\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You do realize we're about to try and hijack
Dialogue: 0,0:23:02.35,0:23:05.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,仅剩希望的电力吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}the power source to a civilization's only hope?
Dialogue: 0,0:23:05.14,0:23:07.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-知道  -不会轻松的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- I do. - It's not gonna be easy.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:07.25,0:23:08.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们该休息一下\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We should rest.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:08.37,0:23:12.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好啊  你以你的方式放松  我也是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}All right. You relax your way and I'll relax mine.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:36.19,0:23:37.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她唱起歌  她歌唱回家\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}When she sings, she sings come home
Dialogue: 0,0:23:37.89,0:23:39.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她唱起歌  她歌唱回家\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}When she sings, she sings come home
Dialogue: 0,0:23:44.36,0:23:45.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的制服呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Where's your uniform?
Dialogue: 0,0:23:46.32,0:23:47.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她唱起歌  她歌唱回家\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}When she sings, she sings come home
Dialogue: 0,0:23:47.98,0:23:49.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她唱起歌  她歌唱回家\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}When she sings, she sings come home
Dialogue: 0,0:23:49.79,0:23:51.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她唱起歌  她歌唱回家\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}When she sings, she sings come home
Dialogue: 0,0:23:51.67,0:23:53.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她唱起歌  她歌唱回家\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}When she sings, she sings come home
Dialogue: 0,0:24:35.60,0:24:37.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她唱起歌  她歌唱回家\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}When she sings, she sings come home
Dialogue: 0,0:24:37.31,0:24:40.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她唱起歌  她歌唱回家\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}When she sings, she sings come home
Dialogue: 0,0:24:40.62,0:24:42.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-敬茜薇  各位  -好啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- To Sylvie, everybody! - Yeah!
Dialogue: 0,0:24:46.31,0:24:47.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再来一杯\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Another!
Dialogue: 0,0:24:52.37,0:24:53.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你喝醉了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You're drunk.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:53.46,0:24:54.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  我只是喝饱了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No, I'm just full.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:54.90,0:24:57.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,记住了  我喝得很饱\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}But bear in mind, I'm very full.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:57.66,0:25:00.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你来尝尝这个\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Now, I need you to try this.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:00.56,0:25:02.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟无花果酒特别搭\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It pairs very nicely with the Figgy Port.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:02.87,0:25:04.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有谁有无花果酒\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Who's got the Figgy Port?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:05.50,0:25:07.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你得相信我了  无花果酒真的好喝\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You have to take my word on the Figgy Port.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:07.26,0:25:09.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的制服呢  我们本该隐匿行事的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Where's your uniform? We're meant to be laying low.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:09.69,0:25:11.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没人在乎  这是世界末日\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Nobody cares. It's the end of the world.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:11.83,0:25:13.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我觉得出事了  -对\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- I think something's happening. - Yes.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:14.47,0:25:16.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那颗行星要撞上我们了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Uh, that planet is about to crash into us.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:16.26,0:25:19.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别犯浑  我看到有人用奇怪的目光打量你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Don't be an ass. I saw some people looking at you weirdly.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:19.13,0:25:20.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:22.48,0:25:23.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你怎么变得这么多疑\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}When did you get so paranoid?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:23.44,0:25:25.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大概是因为我这辈子都在逃避\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I guess it must have started when I spent my entire life
Dialogue: 0,0:25:25.54,0:25:28.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你为他们工作的无所不在的法西斯\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}running from the omniscient fascists you work for.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:29.99,0:25:31.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,浪费了那个好可惜\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's a shame to let that go to waste.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:33.17,0:25:35.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,换个话题  我想到答案了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Change of subject. I thought of an answer.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:35.72,0:25:36.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么的答案\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}To what?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:36.86,0:25:37.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的问题\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Your question.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:42.10,0:25:44.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爱是把匕首\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Love is a dagger.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:46.36,0:25:51.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是可以在远处  或在近处挥动的武器\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's a weapon to be wielded far away or up close.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:52.29,0:25:55.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你可以在其中看到自己  它很美\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You can see yourself in it. It's beautiful.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:57.77,0:25:59.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,直到它让你流血\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Until it makes you bleed.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:00.86,0:26:03.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但最终  你去抓时\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}But ultimately, when you reach for it...
Dialogue: 0,0:26:07.51,0:26:09.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-它不是真的  -对\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- It isn't real. - Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:09.54,0:26:11.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爱是把想象的匕首\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Love is an imaginary dagger.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:12.31,0:26:13.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说不通  是吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Doesn't make sense, does it?
Dialogue: 0,0:26:13.55,0:26:15.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对  这比喻烂透了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No. Terrible metaphor.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:15.23,0:26:17.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,该死  我还以为我想得挺好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Damn. I thought I had something there.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:19.45,0:26:20.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是他\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}That's him.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:20.12,0:26:21.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-淡定  -没事的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Stay cool. - It's gonna be fine.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:21.51,0:26:23.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先生  能出示车票吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Sir, can I see your tickets?
Dialogue: 0,0:26:26.53,0:26:28.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又是你  你好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You again. Hello.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:29.57,0:26:33.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,车票  当然  给你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Um, tickets. Yes, of course. Here they are.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:38.27,0:26:39.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是挺漂亮的  是吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Still, it looks lovely, doesn't it?
Dialogue: 0,0:26:40.29,0:26:41.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真有这个必要吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Look, is this really necessary?
Dialogue: 0,0:26:41.30,0:26:42.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这有个简单的解释\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}There is a simple explanation...
Dialogue: 0,0:26:44.85,0:26:45.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What?
Dialogue: 0,0:26:48.89,0:26:50.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让开\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Get out of the way.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:23.46,0:27:24.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,准头好差\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Awful throw.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:25.94,0:27:27.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能不能别闹了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Oh, will you stop it?
Dialogue: 0,0:27:32.04,0:27:32.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再见\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Bye.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:38.46,0:27:39.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,时空器\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}TemPad.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:00.03,0:28:01.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这可不理想\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Well, that's not ideal.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:01.90,0:28:05.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-把时空器给我  -好吧  好吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Give me the TemPad. - All right. All right. Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:13.75,0:28:15.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我结结实实地摔了一跤\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Well, I did take quite the tumble.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:15.65,0:28:17.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你个混蛋  你害死了我们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You asshole. You killed us.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:17.87,0:28:19.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许能修好它  好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Maybe we can fix it. Okay? Um...
Dialogue: 0,0:28:23.63,0:28:24.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你认真不起来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You're not a serious man.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:24.97,0:28:26.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说得对  我是神\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You're right. I'm a god.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:26.30,0:28:29.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是个小丑  你在火车上喝多了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You're a clown. You got drunk on the train.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:29.35,0:28:30.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是享乐主义者  享乐主义者就这样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm hedonistic. That's what I do.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:30.92,0:28:32.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我才是享乐主义者\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm hedonistic.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:32.16,0:28:33.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比你资深多了  我跟你保证\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}A lot more than you, I assure you.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:33.91,0:28:36.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我绝不会为此牺牲任务\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}But never at the expense of the mission.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:36.34,0:28:38.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,任务  还任务\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Oh, the mission? The mission?
Dialogue: 0,0:28:38.14,0:28:39.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的光荣使命吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What, your glorious purpose?
Dialogue: 0,0:28:39.64,0:28:41.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,省省吧  你打不过他们的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Give me a break. You can't beat them.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:00.14,0:29:01.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:39.16,0:29:42.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喊出来之后有没有好受点\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Did the, uh, scream make you feel better?
Dialogue: 0,0:29:47.77,0:29:49.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yes, it did.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:51.24,0:29:52.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你改天也应该试试\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You should try it sometime.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:58.21,0:29:59.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在怎么办\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What now?
Dialogue: 0,0:29:59.76,0:30:02.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我不知道  你把时空器弄坏了  -那个...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- I don't know. You broke the TemPad. - Well...
Dialogue: 0,0:30:02.26,0:30:05.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那颗行星即将撞上我们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And that planet is about to crash into us.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:06.11,0:30:08.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-是啊  但是...  -但是什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Well, yes, but... - Yes, but what?
Dialogue: 0,0:30:08.55,0:30:10.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但整个卫星不都被摧毁了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Well, the entire moon is destroyed, right?
Dialogue: 0,0:30:11.04,0:30:13.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对  上面的人都死了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yeah. And everyone on it is killed.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:13.50,0:30:15.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-也包括我们  -对  也包括我们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Including us. - Yes, including us.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:19.89,0:30:21.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那方舟呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What about the ark?
Dialogue: 0,0:30:22.35,0:30:24.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,方舟未能启航  因为它被毁了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The ark never leaves because it's destroyed.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:27.33,0:30:28.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们没登船\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Never had us on it.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:33.06,0:30:36.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那怎么  我们劫持方舟  确保它离开这卫星\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}So what? We hijack the ark and make sure it gets off this moon?
Dialogue: 0,0:30:39.48,0:30:41.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得是个好主意\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I mean, sounds like a good idea to me.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:45.12,0:30:45.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:48.15,0:30:49.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Really?
Dialogue: 0,0:31:05.25,0:31:09.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我这辈子好像都没走过这么多路\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You know, I don't think I've ever walked this much in my life.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:09.27,0:31:10.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你过得可真好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}That's a pretty good life.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:10.66,0:31:11.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,幸好你错过了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Well, you're lucky you missed it.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:12.80,0:31:15.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有个想法  你对我施魅术\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Here's an idea. What if you enchanted me
Dialogue: 0,0:31:15.77,0:31:17.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后你一个人走我俩的路\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and you could walk for both of us?
Dialogue: 0,0:31:17.71,0:31:19.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或者我在潜意识里小睡一觉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Or I take a nap in my subconscious,
Dialogue: 0,0:31:19.34,0:31:22.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后等我们到地方  你再叫醒我  行吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and then you could just wake me when we arrive. Yeah?
Dialogue: 0,0:31:22.09,0:31:24.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,魅术不是这样的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yeah, that's not how enchantment works.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:24.16,0:31:25.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  那魅术是什么样的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}All right, how does it work?
Dialogue: 0,0:31:25.83,0:31:26.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不重要了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Doesn't matter.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:27.52,0:31:31.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得我给你讲了太多关于我的事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You know, I feel like I've told you so much about me.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:32.04,0:31:33.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我对你一无所知\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I really don't know the first thing about you.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:33.68,0:31:35.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你给的战术优势\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Thanks for the tactical advantage.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:35.90,0:31:38.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以时管局一出现  你就想利用这一优势\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Ah, so, you want to use that tactical advantage to kill me
Dialogue: 0,0:31:38.98,0:31:40.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,干掉我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}when the TVA shows up.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:40.21,0:31:41.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你担心是吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Worried, are you?
Dialogue: 0,0:31:41.77,0:31:44.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就是想知道我能不能信任你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I just need to know if I can trust you.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:48.24,0:31:49.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Okay, fine.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:50.20,0:31:52.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想知道魅术是怎么回事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You want to know how enchantment works.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:53.08,0:31:55.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我得进行身体接触\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I have to make physical contact
Dialogue: 0,0:31:55.00,0:31:57.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后控制人的思维\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and then grab hold of their mind.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:58.20,0:31:59.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么做\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}How?
Dialogue: 0,0:31:59.52,0:32:00.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这取决于思维\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It depends on the mind.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:00.94,0:32:03.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大多数思维都很简单  我可以立即取得控制\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Most are easy and I can overtake them instantly.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:04.02,0:32:07.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其他更强大一些的就比较棘手\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Others, the stronger ones, it gets tricky.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:07.77,0:32:10.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然我能掌控  但他们的意识也在\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm in control, but they're there, too.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:10.92,0:32:12.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了保持连接\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}In order to preserve the connection,
Dialogue: 0,0:32:12.31,0:32:14.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我必须用他们的记忆创建出一个幻觉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I have to create a fantasy from their memories.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:17.69,0:32:19.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还说我是魔法师呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And you call me a magician.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:20.74,0:32:24.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,时管局的那个年轻士兵  她的大脑很混乱\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}That young soldier from the TVA, her mind was messed up.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:24.90,0:32:26.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一切都模糊不清\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Everything clouded.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:26.71,0:32:29.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不得不提取她几百年前的记忆\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I had to pull a memory from hundreds of years prior,
Dialogue: 0,0:32:29.42,0:32:30.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在她都还没为他们工作前\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}before she even fought for them.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:31.67,0:32:33.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么  你刚说什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What? What'd you just say?
Dialogue: 0,0:32:35.00,0:32:36.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在她加入时管局之前\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Before she joined the TVA?
Dialogue: 0,0:32:36.79,0:32:38.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的  那时她只是地球上的一个普通人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yeah. She was just a regular person on Earth.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:38.76,0:32:39.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一个普通人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}A regular person?
Dialogue: 0,0:32:39.97,0:32:41.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很喜欢喝玛格丽塔酒\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Loved margaritas.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:42.16,0:32:44.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我被告知  时管局的所有员工\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I was told that everyone who works for the TVA
Dialogue: 0,0:32:44.62,0:32:46.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都是由时间守护者创造出来的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}was created by the Time-Keepers.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:46.62,0:32:49.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太荒谬了  他们都是时间异体  和我们一样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}That's ridiculous. They're all Variants, just like us.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:50.31,0:32:51.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们并不知道\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}They don't know that.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:51.78,0:32:53.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所有持票乘客...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}All ticketed passengers...
Dialogue: 0,0:32:53.73,0:32:54.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是我们的飞船\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}That's our ride.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:55.45,0:32:57.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,十分钟后起飞\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Ten minutes until launch.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:02.01,0:33:03.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最后一次登船广播\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Final boarding call.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:05.73,0:33:07.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们信任彼此吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Do we trust each other?
Dialogue: 0,0:33:07.30,0:33:09.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的  你可以信任我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We do and you can.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:11.44,0:33:14.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很好  因为这会很糟\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Good. Because this is gonna suck.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:16.65,0:33:19.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,保持冷静  我们已达最大载客量\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Remain calm. We're now at capacity.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:19.38,0:33:21.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,各位请回家\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Please return to your homes.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:22.25,0:33:23.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,退后\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Stand back!
Dialogue: 0,0:33:23.42,0:33:25.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我们上船\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Let us on!
Dialogue: 0,0:33:25.25,0:33:25.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我们上船\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Let us on!
Dialogue: 0,0:33:25.94,0:33:27.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,五分钟后起飞\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Five minutes until launch.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:27.88,0:33:29.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们要任由这些人死去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}They're gonna let these people die.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:31.58,0:33:33.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,五分钟后起飞\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Five minutes until launch.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:33.68,0:33:35.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们必须上船  确保它起飞\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We have to get on and make sure it takes off.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:35.79,0:33:36.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么做\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}How?
Dialogue: 0,0:33:38.42,0:33:39.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我们绕过去  -好的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- We go around. - Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:47.04,0:33:48.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,各位请回家\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Return to your homes.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:50.71,0:33:51.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,退后\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Get back!
Dialogue: 0,0:33:53.83,0:33:54.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,退后\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Stand back!
Dialogue: 0,0:34:25.83,0:34:27.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你没事吧  -没事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- You okay? - Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:35.10,0:34:36.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等  站住\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Hold it! Stop right there.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:40.71,0:34:41.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快走\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Just go.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:51.19,0:34:52.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这边\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Over here!
Dialogue: 0,0:34:55.06,0:34:56.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不会有事的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You're gonna be okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:58.42,0:34:59.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  不  等等\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No! No, wait!
Dialogue: 0,0:35:11.55,0:35:12.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快跑\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Run!
Dialogue: 0,0:35:16.50,0:35:17.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当心\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Watch out!
Dialogue: 0,0:35:17.72,0:35:18.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I've got it!
Dialogue: 0,0:35:21.28,0:35:22.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快  我们走\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Come on. Let's go!
Dialogue: 0,0:35:25.48,0:35:26.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们仍能赶上\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We can still make it!
Dialogue: 0,0:35:35.33,0:35:36.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,茜薇  快\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Sylvie, come on!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:00.81,0:01:05.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,500)\bord0\shad0\blur5\t(0,500,\blur0)\b1\c&HECB000&\pos(124,202)\fs31}人人影视\N{\fs16}原创翻译  双语字幕
Dialogue: 0,0:01:01.31,0:01:05.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,500)\fn方正准圆_GBK\b1\bord0\shad0\fs17\pos(260,197)\K40}字幕组招新中\N请访问 {\c&H26F4FF&\fn方正综艺_GBK\K30}YYSubs.com
Dialogue: 0,0:01:00.83,0:01:05.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an4\fad(500,500)\fn方正大标宋_GBK\bord0\c&HECB000&\shad0\fs18\fsp-0.6\pos(67,235)}翻译   {\c&HFFFFFF&\fsp-0.2\fn方正清刻本悦宋简体}    恶作剧之{\c&H3CC43C&}草{\c&HFFFFFF&}        杏仁斯嘉丽          Eunice
Dialogue: 0,0:01:05.83,0:01:10.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an4\fad(500,500)\fn方正大标宋_GBK\bord0\shad0\fs18\fsp-0.6\pos(67,235)\c&HECB000&}时间轴   {\c&HFFFFFF&\fsp-0.2\fn方正清刻本悦宋简体} 大葱   DA      {\c&HECB000&\fn方正大标宋_GBK}后期   {\c&HFFFFFF&\fsp-0.8\fn方正清刻本悦宋简体}  吉吉         {\c&HECB000&\fn方正大标宋_GBK\fsp-2}校|监    {\c&HFFFFFF&\fsp-0.8\fn方正清刻本悦宋简体}   {\c&H3CC43C&}草草{\c&HFFFFFF&}
