stant screaming ]
Oh! Oh! Ah!
It's the crow man!
[ Crow cawing ]
[ Belches ]
Give it a second.
Maybe he's taking it out
to surrender.
[ Whooshing ]
[ Sword clangs ]
♪
He's anti-heroic.
Run!
[ Feet pattering ]
I don't understand.
He's only one man!
With the power
of a thousand crows.
[ Crows cawing ]
Oh, oh! Ooh!
[ Strained ]
Good luck.
Crows and owls
have always been at war,
but why do you care?
What's the point?
Here's two.
[ Grunts ]
[ Cheers and applause ]
Ha-ha! Yeah. Cool.
Morty?
Uh, h-hey, man!
Good to see you!
[ Crows cawing ]
Y-You're, like,
looking, like,
into crows...still.
Oh, uh, two crows,
you remember Morty.
Morty, two crows.
[ Crows caw ]
It's good to see you,
but if you'd given me
more of a heads up --
Well, I-I was just
in the neighborhood.
I-It wasn't like --
It's just that
the battle for crows
is kind of never-ending.
Huh. Right.
A little pointless,
then, right?
That came out wrong,
s-sounded judgy.
Crowhorse. Crowhorse.
Okay.
Looks like...
looks like they're
leading you to a thing.
Take care, Morty.
You -- You too!
I-I'm doing good,
by the way.
Oh, my dad was gonna eat that
yogurt you left in the fridge
but I-I told him --
♪
[ Insects chirping ]
[ Rick belches ]
♪
[ Indistinct talking ]
[ Thunder crashes ]
[ Clears throat ]
I'm looking for...
Crow Scare.
The scarecrow?
The evil scarecrow?
Come on. Whoever gives him up
first lives.
Fine, I can kill
an extra asshole.
Helps me get my steps in.
[ Whooshing ]
♪
Ah!
[ Clanging ]
Ahhh!
Rick!
Morty?
Wood?!
Aghhhh!
Uh, Morty, why are you
now like 40?
Th-That's how long
it's been, Rick.
Oh, uh, I guess we can have
a drink together, then.
Do you have
a rum and Coke?
What are you, 20?
[ Chuckling ]
Oh, bless your heart.
Time be goin' by,
don't she?
That's your reaction
to finding out
you wasted
your entire life?
I feel okay.
Well --
well, what about me?!
Whoa.
Excuse us, boys.
You don't wanna
be here for this.
[ Crows cawing ]
I thought if I gave you
enough space,
you'd outgrow this...
phase.
Here's your drink, poser.
Dad got sick, you know.
Stage 4.
You would've loved it.
Summer's a nurse --
well, pretty much a nurse.
She -- She married
a junkie.
Rick, come home,
while we still got
a little time.
Morty, what we had
wasn't healthy.
And this is?
Y-You've had a thousand
adventures with these crows.
When are you gonna
kill their big bad?
First off,
the "will they/kill they"
is everything to my guys.
And second, [bleep] you
for trying to undermine
my happiness.
This may be the last time
you ever lay eyes on me!
I hope that's not true,
Morty,
because you look like
s[burps]shit,
and this is not
how I wanna remember you.
♪
Crow Scare: Now that I have
his two crows,
nothing will stop me
from eliminating Crow Rick.
[ Crows cawing ]
Don't defend him to me.
I don't even get
what you see in him.
[ Crows cawing ]
You're right.
We should be enjoying
the time we have together.
Crow Rick!
Oh, I-I know what this
must look like, but --
It looks like
my arch nemesis, Crow Scare,
and my sidekicks
planning adventures together.
You are hardly
the victim here.
I was adventuring
with these two crows
before you ever
came along.
[ Crows cawing ]
What do you mean,
"using me as a rebound?"
[ Cawing ]
You feel like I was using you
as a rebound, too?
Well, [bleep],
this lost all meaning.
I guess it could have
been worse.
At least adventuring
was just a metaphor
for romantic partnership,
so it's not a real break-up.
Speak for yourself.
We immensely enjoy
each other's bodies.
What?!
Ugh! No!
Sounds like the man's
asking for proof.
Let's show him, fellas!
I-I asked for zero proof!
Ahh!
Zero proof!
[ Whoosh! ]
[ Metal clanging ]
I'm giving you free will.
Yah!
Crow Horse:
Submit to Crow Horse!
[ People screaming ]
Whoops.
[ Doorbell rings ]
Rick?
Wubba lubba dub dub!
I'm back, pal!
Jerry:
Morty, who's at the door?
Wait a minute.
I thought you died gruesomely?
W-what the hell's
going on here?
See, uh, the --
the thing is, uh...
Can you please
make Morty 14 again, Dad?
This is ridiculous.
Okay, look, I-I may have used
an aging serum
to kind of emotionally
blackmail you a little
I kind of figured,
and I totally get it, Morty,
I-I'm done
with the two crows.
Like, they were super clingy
and I'm ready to make this work.
Let's just hit
the reset button.
Well, no, honey,
not a reset, okay?
Tell your grandpa that
you're worthy of his respect
and you want to be treated
differently from now on.
I refuse to do that.
I-I'm desperate
to get back together.
Just like his old man.
Don't worry, honey.
That's just Morty's
middle age talking.
He'll be less codependent
once we get
more of his life
in front of him again.
Uh, I'd like him
to stay 40
so he can keep buying
my friends molly.
I'd rather
throw my vote away
than use it to support
a flawed system.
Can we make our first
adventure fixing this?
I keep thinking about
lawn care.
Okay, buddy.
Who sold you
this shitty aging serum?
What did he look like?
Just like you.
I-I got it
from the Citadel.
Hot damn.
Hittin' the ground running
with a Citadel episode.
See ya later,
masturbators.
[ Muzak playing ]
Hi! I'm Citadel's new mascot,
Andy,
because this place
wouldn't be home
without
Ricks "Andy" Mortys.
Dumb.
Ooh, what happened to
this place?
There's
a Morty president now.
Aw, that's cute. They rebuilt.
They made it nicer.
They made it Glendale.
God damn,
you are cantankerous.
Even pooping hurts now.
Yeah, well, this place
is gonna fix you right up.
Okay, so, we've got
a standard Morty
that's been aged to...40?
Can you reverse it?
Well, if you look at it
like a bone,
what we can do is
break his age in two places,
remove the middle, and graft
its ends back together.
Th-that sounds
really violent.
It's not a literal bone,
Morty.
Oh, okay.
Ah, brace yourself,
the process does also
break every bone
in your body.
Wait! Aah! Ooh! Ow!
I like crayons.
Girls are gross.
I-I think I feel
like myself again.
Uh, you look
a little weird.
Your skin's all pink
like a baby mouse.
I-Is that normal?
Probably.
Uh, sign here
for storage or disposal
of the 26 years
we removed.
Wait, what?
I ain't payin'
to store 26 years.
Well, then youe taking it
with you.
[ Rumbling ]
I'm almost ready
to sell out.
Alright,
what's disposal cost?
[ Rumbling and punching ]
Oh!
S-something unfair's
happening.
There's no escape.
No escape!
Let me help you!
This is not a good look.
Oh!
[ Gunshot ]
Oh, boy.
Hey!
They -- they shot me!
You are seriously hurting
the Citadel experience.
Listen to me!
Drop the gun!
Death is coming
for us all,
and the Citadel is
a weapon of mass des--
[ Gunshot ]
Woof. You're about to get
suspended with pay.
Come on, Morty, let's get outta
here before this gets political.
Oh! Was I...
influential?
Yeah, y-you were
influential.
Y-You had like seven --
seven blogs.
Tight. Oh.
Ugh. Too late.
Rick C-137,
President Morty requests
you join him for dinner.
Whoa! S-Seriously?
You know I destroyed
this place.
You've been paoned
for that, sir.
Rick! Let's have dinner
with the Morty President.
Morty, the idea was to get back
to simple adventures.
The Citadel runs
on canon.
Okay. I guess things really are
just going right back
to how they were.
Fine. I could eat.
But the second he reveals
he's evil, we're gone.
[ Ominous music playing ]
I dunno. It tastes...
pretty good.
Okay, let me know
if you start feeling poisony.
Good to have you back,
buddy.
Mmm!
Sorry I'm late.
Never really ends around here.
Look at this, Morty.
They really did make a you
the president.
And I hate 'em
every day for it.
But wow!
Rick C-137.
Now, that's a guy to move
your schedule around for.
Not -- Not here to blow
the place up again, I hope.
[ Chuckles ]
Ha! Not unless you try
to keep me here.
Ha-ha, geez.
Wouldn't dream of it.
But it's amazing
you dropped by
because I was eventually
gonna hunt you down.
There's the reveal.
Let's dance.
Ha! Geez.
Rick, come on, man.
The guy got elected president
by Ricks and Mortys.
He's being really nice.
All politicians are nice.
He's a hot bag of peanuts,
isn't he?
We've been through
a lot.
A-And he does not like --
Serialized drama.
Right, no drama.
Keep it episodic.
Ricks never look back.
Waste of a legend
in his case.
You know he practically
built this place?
Wait, what?
And now you're running
it squeaky clean, right?
That's why you got
deformed Mortys
coming up
through the sewer lines
talking about
hope and change?
Fair enough.
Good clapback, Rick.
What's the deal with that,
Mister P?
I got a little project
going on.
Required some
hands-on labor.
It would require less
if you were willing
to tell me how one might
bring down
the Central Finite Curve.
Alright,
time to go, Morty.
I want to know
what he's talking about.
Yeah, you've come
all this way.
Can you give me
10 more seconds?
Literally 10?
Because now it would be 6.
Oh, I'm fine with that.
Make it 2.
One.
[ Ding! ]
Like I said, would have been
a big help for you to tell me,
but I should have everything
I need from you now.
Let me just make sure.
You can't scan an entire brain
over appetizers.
Oh, most of yours got scanned
a long time ago.
You probably
don't remember.
Check out season 1,
episode 9, Rick Heads.
Excel[burps]sior!
Evil Rick.
We kicked his ass!
"Evil Rick."
I love it.
Smartest man
in the universe,
with an ego so big you can
just grab it like a joystick.
[ Whirring ]
Looks complete.
I was afraid I'd have to
kill every Rick
on the Citadel
to get what I needed.
You asshole!
I vouched for you!
He only came here
because I asked him to.
I'm sorry, Rick.
That apology and a screwdriver
in my hand
would be worth
a screwdriver.
You sellout Mortys kill me.
I'd hate you more than
the Ricks you worship
if there was any point.
But you can't help it.
You were bred for it.
Wanna see?
[ Whirring ]
You already know Rogue Ricks
used Mortys
to hide themselves
from the Citadel.
But you might not know
it worked so well
that the Citadel
became its own
Morty Market.
And I'm sure you don't know
how far they've gone
to help supply meet demand.
Sure, Ricks could
scour infinity
for naturally occurring
grandsons.
But why bother?
So much work.
Such an admission of need.
There aren't infinite versions
of our grandfather, Morty.
He's an infinite smear
of one shitty old man.
And he's attached to us
infinitely
through his weakness
and our forgiveness.
This is why
we're with him.
This is why we're alive.
What the [bleep]?
Rick,
say this isn't true.
It isn't the whole truth.
Both: Liar!
It's complicated!
I'm not busy.
Okay, Morty, remember when
I said all I need
was your apology
and a screwdriver in my hand?
Well, I forgot I literally
have a screwdriver in my hand.
I mean, duh-doy.
I'm basically Inspector Gadget.
Uh-oh.
It's okay.
He's free to go.
He's the Rickest Rick.
We'll never see him again.
Morty, when you came here
for that serum,
did you refill this gun?
Yeah.
Oh. Ooh!
Holy [bleep]
I only know one man that ever
hacked my portal gun,
and it turned out
it was evil you.
Yay!
He's all caught up.
Wait. Hold it.
Hold it.
Who -- Who's that?
Time for Big Boy. Duck!
Ohhhhhh! Ohhhhhh!
Ohhhhh!
Does he like it?
It's a metaphor
for capitalism, Morty.
What do you think?
Ohhhhhh! Ohhhhhh!
Ohhhhhh!
Ohh! Ohhhhhh!
[ Grunting ]
Ohhhhhh! Ohhhhhh!
Ohhhhh!
[ Grunts ]
Ohhhhhh! Ohhhhhh!
Ohhhhh!
Ohhhhhh!
Rick: Yoink!
You can't outrun your past,
Rick.
Did you think my force field
would be down the second time?
I was expressing disapproval
of your dialogue.
[ Chuckles ]
Disapprove all you want.
Tonight, the quality of dialogue
stops mattering.
Tonight, I do that thing
I want to do
with the curve thing.
Loudspeaker: Nobody leave.
Everybody stay.
Nobody leave.
Everody stay.
[ Mortys screaming ]
Aaaaaaah!
[ Gunfire ]
Nobody leave.
Everybody stay.
In uncertain times like these,
I think it's important for me
to say, eat shit, [bleep] you.
The drug companies paid for me
to say every word.
I have millions of dollars,
and I don't care if you live --
oh, God!
Oh, [bleep]! No! Aah!
And I'd just like to say that
prescription drugs are great,
and you should buy them now.
Morty:
What's happening, Rick?
He hacked the entire city's
portal supply.
Come on, there still might be
one way out of here --
out the bottom.
♪
What do you think he needed
from your brain?
I assume schematics for the
Citadel's dimensional drive.
If he's gonna use it
to blow the curve,
we do not want to be here.
What is
the Central Finite Curve?
Q&A after our survival.
Hopefully we can snag some
untainted fluid at the source
and get the [bleep]
out of here.
Or not.
Wow. I thought my capitalism
metaphor was on the nose.
Ow! Oh!
So did you help build
the Citadel?
Do you just lie to me
about everything?
Can't we just sneak
through the cave base?
We turned a new leaf, Morty.
We're back to simple adventures.
It's not a new leaf
until you tell me everything.
Morty, we really don't
have time for this.
The whole place
isonna blow.
No, I-I don't trust you.
I-I don't want to
do this anymore
if I'm not gonna get
straight answers from you.
God damn it!
Here's my [bleep]
downloaded brain, Morty.
You want to
jump the shark?
You want to know my stupid
crybaby backstory?
Knock yourself out.
Not -- not now!
♪
[ Explosion ]
[ Whirring ]
♪
[ Laughing ]
[ Laughter ]
-Boo ya, Rick.
-Nice one, Morty!
Whoa. Dead wife?
Yes, now everyone
can shut up about it.
Wow, Rick, I feel a lot better
having seen all that.
[ Chuckles ]
Of course that's the case.
In their minds,
they're the underdogs.
And that's how
they justify this.
[ Whirring ]
Rick: Morty,
I'm not responsible
for every [bleep]-up Rick
out there.
They literally all
say that.
They all have that excuse.
It's part of their system.
None of them have to be
responsible.
They're all victims
of themselves.
Oh, it's so hard to be a genius.
Couldn't you just die?
Well, what are you
doing about it?
Jack [bleep]
I'm leaving.
Do you know what
the Central Finite Curve is?
They built a wall
around infinity.
They separated all
the infinite universes
from all
where he's the smartest man
in the universe.
Every version of us
has spent every version
of all of our lives
in one infinite crib
built around
an infinite [bleep] baby.
And I'm leaving it.
That's what makes me evil --
being sick of him.
If you've ever been sick of him,
you've been evil, too.
Rick, did you really leave
the crows for me?
Or did you come back
because they dumped you?
There you go, kid.
Now you're Evil Morty, too.
Sooner or later
we all are,
on this side
of the curve.
[ Whirring ]
♪
-Ah!
Don't worry, Morty.
We still got a way out
they never thought of --
Operation Phoenix.
Doesn't that still mean,
like, death?
Sure, but the joke's
on them,
'cause we just found a backdoor
to getting off this rock.
[ Gunshot ]
REROUTED.
A.I.: Rerouted.
Rerouted. Rerouted.
[ All screaming ]
Rerouted.
[ Explosion ]
Oh, my [bleep] God!
Come on, Morty.
We gotta go.
Evil Morty:
You can come if you want.
Don't blame me
if you don't.
Ugh! From where I sit,
Morty,
that's the best deal
on the table.
I-I don't have
a real plan.
[ Grunts ]
Thanks, pal. I-I'm glad
you ignored my advice.
It's just as well.
I lied.
That second seat's
a toilet.
Oh.
Super dick move.
But weirdly kind of cool
to admit it.
Geez, you guys really are
bred for forgiveness.
Let's go.
♪
[ All exclaiming ]
Say goodbye to the Citadel,
fellas.
[ Rumbling ]
♪
[ Rocket fires ]
[ Both screaming ]
♪
[ Sighs ]
[ Slurping and zapping ]
♪
Ooowee! Evil Morty.
That was quite a scheme.
Makes me wonder if there's
an evil me out there.
But I guess sometimes
I look at my life,
and I may not even need him,
'cause, well,
guess I've made a pretty big
mess of things myself.
Ooowee.
Never got my job
at the university back.
Remember that?
Rick made me do karate.
It -- It was kinda funny.
But I guess things
went downhill from there.
Started isolating myself
from Amy.
Used to tell her
everything I was feeling,
but then I guess I stopped,
'cause I wanted her to love
who she thought I was,
not who I felt myself becoming.
Ever think about how horrified
the people we love would be
if they found out
who we truly are?
So we just dig ourselves deeper
into our lies every day,
ultimately hurting the only
people brave enough to love us.
Wish I didn't do that.
Wish I was brave enough
to love them back.
I don't know.
Maybe you should try it.
We don't have as much time
as we think.
Ooowee.
Man:
Did you get any of that?